<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 17:16:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Insider Threat: Cybersecurity Pros Charged in BlackCat Ransomware Spree</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cybersecurity-professionals-indicted-for-blackcat-ransomware-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cybersecurity-professionals-indicted-for-blackcat-ransomware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Insider Threat: Cybersecurity Pros Charged in BlackCat Ransomware Spree</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>In a shocking case of insider threat, U.S. federal prosecutors have indicted two cybersecurity professionals, Ryan Clifford Goldberg and Kevin Tyler Martin, for their role in a series of ALPHV/BlackCat ransomware attacks. The individuals, who worked in incident response and ransomware negotiation, allegedly used their specialized knowledge to extort at least five U.S. companies between May and November 2023. The attacks targeted organizations across multiple sectors, including healthcare and manufacturing, with one victim paying over $1.2 million in ransom. This case highlights the grave risks posed by malicious insiders within the cybersecurity industry itself.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Federal prosecutors charge two cybersecurity professionals, Ryan Clifford Goldberg and Kevin Tyler Martin, for deploying ALPHV/BlackCat ransomware against U.S. companies.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cybersecurity-professionals-indicted-for-blackcat-ransomware-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cybersecurity-professionals-indicted-for-blackcat-ransomware-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Patch Now: Critical Zero-Click RCE Flaw Hits Billions of Android Devices</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-android-zero-click-rce-flaw-cve-2025-48593/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-android-zero-click-rce-flaw-cve-2025-48593/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Patch Now: Critical Zero-Click RCE Flaw Hits Billions of Android Devices</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Google's November 2025 Android Security Bulletin has put users on high alert with the disclosure of CVE-2025-48593, a critical zero-click remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability. The flaw, residing in the Android System component, affects Android versions 13, 14, 15, and 16. Its most dangerous characteristic is that it can be exploited remotely without any user interaction, potentially allowing an attacker to take full control of a device. Google has released patches, and users are urged to update their devices to the 2025-11-01 security patch level or later immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Mobile Security, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Google's November 2025 Android Security Bulletin reveals a critical zero-click RCE vulnerability, CVE-2025-48593, affecting Android versions 13 through 16.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> critical-android-zero-click-rce-flaw-cve-2025-48593</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-android-zero-click-rce-flaw-cve-2025-48593/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Millions of Devs at Risk: Critical RCE Flaw in Popular React Native Package</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-rce-vulnerability-in-react-native-npm-package-cve-2025-11953/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-rce-vulnerability-in-react-native-npm-package-cve-2025-11953/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Millions of Devs at Risk: Critical RCE Flaw in Popular React Native Package</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability, CVE-2025-11953, has been discovered in a popular React Native command-line tool, putting millions of developers at risk. The flaw, rated 9.8 on the CVSS scale, exists in the '@react-native-community/cli' NPM package and allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on a developer's machine by sending a malicious request to the Metro development server. This could lead to source code theft, malware injection, or a full-blown supply chain attack. Meta has released a patch, and developers are strongly urged to update their dependencies.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Supply Chain Attack, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A critical remote code execution vulnerability (CVE-2025-11953) with a 9.8 CVSS score has been found in a widely used React Native NPM package, affecting millions of developers.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> critical-rce-vulnerability-in-react-native-npm-package-cve-2025-11953</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-rce-vulnerability-in-react-native-npm-package-cve-2025-11953/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Conti's Ghost: New 'DragonForce' Ransomware Adopts Cartel Model</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/dragonforce-ransomware-emerges-from-leaked-conti-code-with-cartel-model/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/dragonforce-ransomware-emerges-from-leaked-conti-code-with-cartel-model/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Conti's Ghost: New 'DragonForce' Ransomware Adopts Cartel Model</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new ransomware operation named DragonForce has been identified by security researchers, notable for its use of leaked source code from the infamous Conti ransomware. Instead of a traditional Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) model, DragonForce operates with a 'cartel-like' structure, providing affiliates with a builder to create their own branded ransomware variants. This approach facilitates the rapid proliferation of new threats, with groups like 'Devman' already seen deploying malware created with the DragonForce builder. The core malware retains Conti's technical features, including its encryption scheme and ability to spread via SMB.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Security researchers uncover DragonForce, a new ransomware group using leaked Conti source code and a novel 'cartel-style' model to recruit affiliates and build custom malware variants.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> dragonforce-ransomware-emerges-from-leaked-conti-code-with-cartel-model</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/dragonforce-ransomware-emerges-from-leaked-conti-code-with-cartel-model/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: SK Telecom Profit Plummets 90% After Data Breach Hits 27M Customers</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sk-telecom-profits-plummet-90-percent-after-massive-data-breach/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sk-telecom-profits-plummet-90-percent-after-massive-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> SK Telecom Profit Plummets 90% After Data Breach Hits 27M Customers</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>South Korean telecommunications giant SK Telecom has suffered a catastrophic financial blow, reporting a 90% drop in its third-quarter operating profit. The dramatic decline is a direct result of a massive data breach disclosed in April, which compromised the sensitive personal data of approximately 27 million customers. The costs, stemming from a record regulatory fine of $96.5 million and a $349 million 'customer appreciation package,' underscore the devastating and long-lasting financial consequences of major cybersecurity failures.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Cyberattack, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> South Korean telecom giant SK Telecom suffers a 90% drop in operating profit due to the immense costs of a data breach that compromised the personal data of 27 million customers.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> sk-telecom-profits-plummet-90-percent-after-massive-data-breach</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sk-telecom-profits-plummet-90-percent-after-massive-data-breach/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Everest Ransomware Claims Hits on AT&amp;T, Dublin Airport, and Swedish Power Grid</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/everest-ransomware-claims-attacks-on-att-dublin-airport-and-svenska-kraftnat/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/everest-ransomware-claims-attacks-on-att-dublin-airport-and-svenska-kraftnat/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Everest Ransomware Claims Hits on AT&amp;T, Dublin Airport, and Swedish Power Grid</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Everest ransomware group has made bold claims of responsibility for a series of high-profile cyberattacks, alleging the theft of massive amounts of data from major international entities. The targets reportedly include U.S. telecom giant AT&amp;T, Dublin Airport, the airline Air Arabia, and Sweden's power grid operator, Svenska kraftnät. The group claims to have exfiltrated millions of customer and employee records and hundreds of gigabytes of internal data, highlighting a focus on critical infrastructure and data-rich organizations.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Everest ransomware group has claimed responsibility for a series of high-profile attacks, allegedly stealing data from AT&amp;T, Dublin Airport, Air Arabia, and Sweden's power grid operator.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> everest-ransomware-claims-attacks-on-att-dublin-airport-and-svenska-kraftnat</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/everest-ransomware-claims-attacks-on-att-dublin-airport-and-svenska-kraftnat/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: EU Stress-Tests Cyber Defenses in Large-Scale Crisis Simulation</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/eu-tests-joint-cyber-crisis-response-in-blueolex-2025-exercise/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/eu-tests-joint-cyber-crisis-response-in-blueolex-2025-exercise/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> EU Stress-Tests Cyber Defenses in Large-Scale Crisis Simulation</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The European Union has concluded its 2025 'Blueprint Operational Level Exercise' (BlueOLEx), a large-scale simulation designed to test and improve the bloc's collective response to major cybersecurity crises. Hosted in Cyprus with support from the EU's cybersecurity agency, ENISA, the exercise brought together senior officials from all member states to role-play a significant cyber incident affecting critical sectors. The drill was the first to test the new EU Cyber Blueprint, which aims to clarify roles and streamline coordination between national authorities and the European Commission during a cross-border attack.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Security Operations</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The European Union tests its collective cybersecurity crisis response mechanisms in the 2025 'Blueprint Operational Level Exercise' (BlueOLEx), simulating a major incident affecting critical sectors.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> eu-tests-joint-cyber-crisis-response-in-blueolex-2025-exercise</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/eu-tests-joint-cyber-crisis-response-in-blueolex-2025-exercise/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Philippine Police Brace for Coordinated DDoS Attacks on Government Websites</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/philippine-police-on-high-alert-for-anticipated-ddos-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/philippine-police-on-high-alert-for-anticipated-ddos-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Philippine Police Brace for Coordinated DDoS Attacks on Government Websites</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Philippine National Police (PNP) has mobilized its cybersecurity units and placed them on high alert in anticipation of a potential large-scale distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) campaign targeting government websites. According to intelligence, the attacks are slated to begin on November 5, 2025. The PNP is coordinating with the Department of Information and Communications Technology (DICT) and other national agencies to harden critical digital infrastructure and prepare rapid response teams to mitigate any disruption to public services.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cyberattack, Security Operations, Policy and Compliance</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Philippine National Police (PNP) heightens its cybersecurity defenses in anticipation of a potential wave of distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks targeting government websites.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> philippine-police-on-high-alert-for-anticipated-ddos-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/philippine-police-on-high-alert-for-anticipated-ddos-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Cl0p Ransomware Exploits Oracle E-Business Suite Zero-Day, Hits Major Corporations</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cl0p-ransomware-exploits-oracle-e-business-suite-zero-day-cve-2025-61882/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cl0p-ransomware-exploits-oracle-e-business-suite-zero-day-cve-2025-61882/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Cl0p Ransomware Exploits Oracle E-Business Suite Zero-Day, Hits Major Corporations</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The notorious Cl0p ransomware gang is the primary suspect behind a new wave of attacks exploiting a zero-day remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in Oracle E-Business Suite. The flaw, tracked as CVE-2025-61882, affects the Oracle Concurrent Processing component and has allegedly been used to breach several major corporations. Victims include mining company Pan American Silver, energy giant Schneider Electric, and communications conglomerate Cox Enterprises. Data from the latter two has already been leaked on Cl0p's dark web site, demonstrating the group's continued proficiency in weaponizing zero-day vulnerabilities in enterprise software.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Vulnerability, Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Cl0p ransomware gang is believed to be exploiting a zero-day RCE vulnerability, CVE-2025-61882, in Oracle E-Business Suite to breach major corporations and leak data.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cl0p-ransomware-exploits-oracle-e-business-suite-zero-day-cve-2025-61882</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cl0p-ransomware-exploits-oracle-e-business-suite-zero-day-cve-2025-61882/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Homeland Security Warns Gov't Shutdown and Lapsed Law Cripple U.S. Cyber Defenses</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-homeland-security-warns-of-rising-cyber-threats-amid-shutdown/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-homeland-security-warns-of-rising-cyber-threats-amid-shutdown/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Homeland Security Warns Gov't Shutdown and Lapsed Law Cripple U.S. Cyber Defenses</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. House Committee on Homeland Security has issued a stark warning in its latest 'Cyber Threat Snapshot,' stating that the nation's ability to defend against cyber threats is being severely hampered. The report cites a dual crisis: a federal government shutdown that furloughs key cybersecurity personnel, and the lapse of the Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act of 2015. This creates 'dangerous blind spots' at a time of heightened threat activity from nation-state actors like China and Iran, and a surge in attacks against U.S. critical infrastructure.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The U.S. House Committee on Homeland Security's 'Cyber Threat Snapshot' warns that a federal shutdown and lapsed information-sharing laws are weakening the nation's cyber defenses.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> us-homeland-security-warns-of-rising-cyber-threats-amid-shutdown</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-homeland-security-warns-of-rising-cyber-threats-amid-shutdown/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: US Cyber Threat Sharing Law 'CISA 2015' Expires, Creating Potential Intelligence Gap</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/key-us-cyber-information-sharing-law-expires-sparking-concerns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/key-us-cyber-information-sharing-law-expires-sparking-concerns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> US Cyber Threat Sharing Law 'CISA 2015' Expires, Creating Potential Intelligence Gap</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act of 2015 (CISA 2015), a foundational U.S. law that provided liability protections to encourage private companies to share cyber threat data with the government, expired on October 1, 2025. Amidst a government shutdown and a block by Senator Rand Paul, lawmakers failed to reauthorize the act. Security and legal experts warn this could have a chilling effect on threat intelligence sharing, with one law firm predicting a potential 80% drop. The lapse creates uncertainty and could hinder national cybersecurity efforts. In response, new legislation, the PACT Act, has been introduced to retroactively restore and extend the protections, but its future is uncertain.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> CISA 2015, Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act, PACT Act, threat intelligence sharing, cybersecurity policy, US law, liability protection</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act of 2015 (CISA 2015) has expired, removing key liability protections and sparking fears of a dramatic drop in public-private cyber threat intelligence sharing.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> key-us-cyber-information-sharing-law-expires-sparking-concerns</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/key-us-cyber-information-sharing-law-expires-sparking-concerns/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Chinese APT 'Airstalk' Malware Abuses MDM APIs in BPO Supply Chain Attacks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/chinese-apt-airstalk-malware-bpo-supply-chain-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/chinese-apt-airstalk-malware-bpo-supply-chain-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Chinese APT 'Airstalk' Malware Abuses MDM APIs in BPO Supply Chain Attacks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new malware family named 'Airstalk', attributed to the suspected Chinese state-sponsored group CL-STA-1009, is being used in sophisticated supply chain attacks against the Business Process Outsourcing (BPO) industry. The malware, with both PowerShell and .NET variants, uniquely abuses the AirWatch/Workspace ONE MDM API for covert command-and-control (C2) communications and data exfiltration. It is designed for long-term persistence and targets browser data from Chrome, Edge, and the Island Browser, posing a significant risk of access to BPO clients' systems.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Malware, Supply Chain Attack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Analysis of the new 'Airstalk' malware used by Chinese APT group CL-STA-1009 in supply chain attacks against the BPO sector, leveraging MDM APIs for C2.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> chinese-apt-airstalk-malware-bpo-supply-chain-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/chinese-apt-airstalk-malware-bpo-supply-chain-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Insider Threat Shocker: Cybersecurity Pros Indicted for Wielding ALPHV/BlackCat Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/incident-responders-indicted-for-alphv-blackcat-ransomware-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/incident-responders-indicted-for-alphv-blackcat-ransomware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Insider Threat Shocker: Cybersecurity Pros Indicted for Wielding ALPHV/BlackCat Ransomware</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>In a severe breach of trust, two cybersecurity professionals, Ryan Clifford Goldberg and Kevin Tyler Martin, have been indicted for allegedly conducting ALPHV/BlackCat ransomware attacks against at least five U.S. companies. The individuals, who held roles in incident response and ransomware negotiation, are accused of conspiring to extort nearly $1.3 million from a Florida medical company. This case highlights a critical insider threat risk within the cybersecurity industry itself, where trusted professionals abuse their knowledge and access for criminal gain.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Incident Response</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Two cybersecurity professionals from Sygnia and DigitalMint have been indicted for using ALPHV/BlackCat ransomware to attack and extort U.S. businesses.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> incident-responders-indicted-for-alphv-blackcat-ransomware-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/incident-responders-indicted-for-alphv-blackcat-ransomware-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Incident Response</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Sophisticated Phishing Attacks on LinkedIn Bypass MFA Using Google &amp; Microsoft Redirects</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/linkedin-dm-phishing-attacks-abuse-google-microsoft-services/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/linkedin-dm-phishing-attacks-abuse-google-microsoft-services/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Sophisticated Phishing Attacks on LinkedIn Bypass MFA Using Google &amp; Microsoft Redirects</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A sophisticated phishing campaign is using LinkedIn direct messages to initiate attacks that steal Microsoft session tokens, effectively bypassing multi-factor authentication (MFA). The attack leverages a complex redirect chain using trusted services like Google Sites, Firebase, and Microsoft Dynamics to evade detection before presenting an adversary-in-the-middle (AiTM) phishing page. This page is further protected by a Cloudflare Turnstile challenge, hindering automated analysis and increasing the campaign's success rate.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Phishing, Cyberattack, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Analysis of a new AiTM phishing campaign using LinkedIn DMs and redirect chains through Google and Microsoft services to bypass MFA and steal session credentials.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> linkedin-dm-phishing-attacks-abuse-google-microsoft-services</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/linkedin-dm-phishing-attacks-abuse-google-microsoft-services/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Cl0p Ransomware Exploits Oracle E-Business Suite Zero-Day in Attacks on Major Corporations</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cl0p-ransomware-exploits-oracle-zero-day-cve-2025-61882/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cl0p-ransomware-exploits-oracle-zero-day-cve-2025-61882/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Cl0p Ransomware Exploits Oracle E-Business Suite Zero-Day in Attacks on Major Corporations</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Cl0p ransomware group is actively exploiting a zero-day remote code execution vulnerability (CVE-2025-61882) in Oracle's E-Business Suite. The attacks have targeted major corporations including Schneider Electric, Cox Enterprises, and Pan American Silver Corp, with data from the first two already leaked on Cl0p's extortion site. This campaign underscores the group's continued strategy of leveraging unpatched flaws in critical, widely-used enterprise software for initial access and data exfiltration.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Vulnerability, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Cl0p ransomware is exploiting a zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2025-61882, in Oracle E-Business Suite to attack Schneider Electric, Cox Enterprises, and others.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cl0p-ransomware-exploits-oracle-zero-day-cve-2025-61882</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cl0p-ransomware-exploits-oracle-zero-day-cve-2025-61882/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Everest Ransomware Claims Massive Data Breaches at AT&amp;T, Dublin Airport, and Swedish Power Grid</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/everest-ransomware-group-claims-multiple-high-profile-breaches/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/everest-ransomware-group-claims-multiple-high-profile-breaches/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Everest Ransomware Claims Massive Data Breaches at AT&amp;T, Dublin Airport, and Swedish Power Grid</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Everest ransomware group has claimed responsibility for a series of high-profile cyberattacks, alleging the theft of vast amounts of data. Victims reportedly include AT&amp;T (576,000 applicant records), Dublin Airport (1.5 million passenger files), Air Arabia (18,000 employee records), and, most critically, Sweden's national power grid operator, Svenska kraftnät (280 GB of internal data). These unverified claims highlight a significant and widespread threat to critical infrastructure and major multinational corporations.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach, Industrial Control Systems</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Everest ransomware group claims major data breaches, alleging theft of millions of records from AT&amp;T, Dublin Airport, Air Arabia, and Swedish power grid operator Svenska kraftnät.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> everest-ransomware-group-claims-multiple-high-profile-breaches</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/everest-ransomware-group-claims-multiple-high-profile-breaches/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: SK Telecom Profit Plummets 90% Following Massive Data Breach Affecting 27 Million Customers</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sk-telecom-profit-drops-90-percent-after-massive-data-breach/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sk-telecom-profit-drops-90-percent-after-massive-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> SK Telecom Profit Plummets 90% Following Massive Data Breach Affecting 27 Million Customers</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>South Korean telecom giant SK Telecom has reported a catastrophic 90% drop in its Q3 operating profit, directly attributing the loss to the massive costs of a data breach that exposed the personal data of 27 million customers. The breach, which went undetected for nearly three years, involved 25 different malware types and led to a record $96.5 million (134 billion won) fine from regulators. This incident serves as a stark illustration of the severe and tangible financial consequences of long-term cybersecurity failures and inadequate threat detection.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Cyberattack, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> SK Telecom's Q3 operating profit fell by 90% due to the high costs associated with a data breach that exposed data from 27 million customers and resulted in a massive fine.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> sk-telecom-profit-drops-90-percent-after-massive-data-breach</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sk-telecom-profit-drops-90-percent-after-massive-data-breach/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: China Amends Cybersecurity Law, Massively Increasing Fines and Adding AI Governance Clause</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-amends-cybersecurity-law-massively-increasing-penalties/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-amends-cybersecurity-law-massively-increasing-penalties/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> China Amends Cybersecurity Law, Massively Increasing Fines and Adding AI Governance Clause</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>China has passed major amendments to its 2016 Cybersecurity Law, set to take effect on January 1, 2026. The changes dramatically increase financial penalties for non-compliance, raising the maximum fine for Critical Information Infrastructure Operators (CIIOs) tenfold to RMB 10 million (approx. $1.41M) and for non-CIIOs to RMB 2 million. The amendments also introduce a new, general clause on Artificial Intelligence governance, signaling tighter regulatory control over technology and data security within the country.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> China has amended its Cybersecurity Law, effective January 1, 2026, to significantly increase financial penalties for non-compliance and introduce new rules for AI governance.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> china-amends-cybersecurity-law-massively-increasing-penalties</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-amends-cybersecurity-law-massively-increasing-penalties/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Microsoft Discovers 'SesameOp' Backdoor Using OpenAI API for Covert C2</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-uncovers-sesameop-backdoor-using-openai-api-for-c2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-uncovers-sesameop-backdoor-using-openai-api-for-c2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Microsoft Discovers 'SesameOp' Backdoor Using OpenAI API for Covert C2</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Microsoft's Detection and Response Team (DART) has discovered a novel backdoor named 'SesameOp' that uniquely uses the OpenAI Assistants API for its command-and-control (C2) communications. Found during an espionage investigation, the malware hides its malicious traffic within legitimate API calls to the OpenAI platform, making it extremely difficult to detect. The attackers also used .NET AppDomainManager injection by compromising Microsoft Visual Studio utilities to achieve persistence.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Threat Actor, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Microsoft researchers have discovered 'SesameOp,' a new backdoor that abuses the OpenAI Assistants API for stealthy command-and-control in a targeted espionage campaign.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> microsoft-uncovers-sesameop-backdoor-using-openai-api-for-c2</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-uncovers-sesameop-backdoor-using-openai-api-for-c2/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Unpatched Windows LNK Flaw (CVE-2025-9491) Actively Exploited by APTs to Deploy PlugX</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/unpatched-windows-lnk-flaw-cve-2025-9491-actively-exploited/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/unpatched-windows-lnk-flaw-cve-2025-9491-actively-exploited/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Unpatched Windows LNK Flaw (CVE-2025-9491) Actively Exploited by APTs to Deploy PlugX</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A long-standing and unpatched vulnerability in how Windows handles .LNK shortcut files (CVE-2025-9491) is being actively exploited by threat actors, including the APT group UNC6384, to deliver the PlugX RAT. The flaw allows attackers to hide malicious commands within a shortcut's properties, tricking users into execution. Despite ongoing exploitation and a public disclosure in March 2025, Microsoft has reiterated its position not to issue a direct patch, instead advising customers to rely on existing defenses like Microsoft Defender and to avoid opening files from unknown sources.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Threat Actor, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> An unpatched Windows LNK vulnerability, CVE-2025-9491, is being actively exploited by APTs to deliver malware. Microsoft has declined to issue a specific patch for the flaw.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> unpatched-windows-lnk-flaw-cve-2025-9491-actively-exploited</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/unpatched-windows-lnk-flaw-cve-2025-9491-actively-exploited/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Europe Now #2 Global Ransomware Target, Attacks Accelerating to 24-Hour Deployments</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/europe-is-2-global-ransomware-target-attacks-accelerating-crowdstrike-report/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/europe-is-2-global-ransomware-target-attacks-accelerating-crowdstrike-report/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Europe Now #2 Global Ransomware Target, Attacks Accelerating to 24-Hour Deployments</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Europe is now the second-largest global target for ransomware, accounting for 22% of all victims, according to CrowdStrike's 2025 European Threat Landscape Report. The report highlights a dramatic increase in attack speed, with groups like SCATTERED SPIDER now able to deploy ransomware in just 24 hours from initial access. The threat is fueled by a thriving initial access broker (IAB) market and escalating geopolitical tensions involving Russian, Chinese, and North Korean state-sponsored actors targeting critical sectors.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Intelligence, Ransomware, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CrowdStrike's 2025 European Threat Landscape Report finds Europe is the second-largest target for ransomware, with attacks accelerating and fueled by geopolitical conflict.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> europe-is-2-global-ransomware-target-attacks-accelerating-crowdstrike-report</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/europe-is-2-global-ransomware-target-attacks-accelerating-crowdstrike-report/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Cl0p Ransomware Exploits Oracle EBS Zero-Day in Active Attacks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/clop-ransomware-exploits-oracle-e-business-suite-zero-day/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/clop-ransomware-exploits-oracle-e-business-suite-zero-day/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Cl0p Ransomware Exploits Oracle EBS Zero-Day in Active Attacks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The notorious Cl0p ransomware gang is actively exploiting a critical zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2025-61882, in Oracle's E-Business Suite (EBS) to gain initial access to corporate networks. The complex flaw, which allows for remote code execution, has already been linked to at least two major security incidents, including a breach at Harvard University. With mass exploitation now being reported, organizations using Oracle EBS are at immediate and significant risk and are urged to apply mitigations immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Ransomware, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 8 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Cl0p ransomware gang is exploiting a zero-day RCE vulnerability (CVE-2025-61882) in Oracle E-Business Suite, leading to active breaches and mass exploitation.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> clop-ransomware-exploits-oracle-e-business-suite-zero-day</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 12:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/clop-ransomware-exploits-oracle-e-business-suite-zero-day/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Everest Ransomware Hits Swedish Power Grid Operator, Steals 280GB of Data</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/swedish-power-grid-operator-svenska-kraftnat-hit-by-everest-ransomware/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/swedish-power-grid-operator-svenska-kraftnat-hit-by-everest-ransomware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Everest Ransomware Hits Swedish Power Grid Operator, Steals 280GB of Data</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Sweden's national electricity operator, Svenska kraftnät, has confirmed a data breach following a claim by the Everest ransomware group. The attackers alleged on their dark web leak site that they had stolen 280 GB of internal data. Svenska kraftnät stated that the attack was confined to an external file transfer system and that the nation's core power grid operations and electricity supply were not affected. An investigation is underway to determine the scope of the compromised data.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cyberattack, Data Breach, Industrial Control Systems</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Everest ransomware group has claimed a data breach against Sweden's national power grid operator, Svenska kraftnät, allegedly stealing 280 GB of data from an external system.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> swedish-power-grid-operator-svenska-kraftnat-hit-by-everest-ransomware</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/swedish-power-grid-operator-svenska-kraftnat-hit-by-everest-ransomware/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>