<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 16:13:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Data Catastrophe: Unsecured 16TB Database Leaks 4.3 Billion Professional Records</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/massive-16tb-mongodb-database-exposes-4-3-billion-professional-records/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/massive-16tb-mongodb-database-exposes-4-3-billion-professional-records/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Data Catastrophe: Unsecured 16TB Database Leaks 4.3 Billion Professional Records</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A monumental data exposure event was uncovered involving a 16-terabyte unsecured MongoDB database containing approximately 4.3 billion professional records. Discovered by security researcher Bob Diachenko, the database is believed to belong to a lead generation company and exposed a vast trove of personally identifiable information (PII), including names, emails, phone numbers, and detailed employment history scraped from sources like LinkedIn. The exposure, which was secured on November 25, 2025, presents a severe risk for global, large-scale social engineering, phishing, and credential-stuffing campaigns. The incident highlights the persistent danger of misconfigured cloud databases and the immense value such datasets provide to malicious actors for crafting highly sophisticated attacks.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 7 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A massive 16TB unsecured MongoDB database was found to have exposed 4.3 billion professional records, including names, emails, and employment history, posing a significant global risk for social engineering and credential stuffing attacks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> massive-16tb-mongodb-database-exposes-4-3-billion-professional-records</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/massive-16tb-mongodb-database-exposes-4-3-billion-professional-records/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: 700Credit Data Breach Exposes PII of 5.6 Million Individuals</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fintech-firm-700credit-discloses-data-breach-affecting-5-6-million/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fintech-firm-700credit-discloses-data-breach-affecting-5-6-million/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> 700Credit Data Breach Exposes PII of 5.6 Million Individuals</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. fintech company 700Credit, a major provider of credit reports and data services to the automotive industry, has disclosed a data breach affecting at least 5.6 million individuals. The incident, which occurred in October 2025, resulted in an unauthorized actor gaining access to and stealing a significant amount of personally identifiable information (PII). The compromised data includes names, addresses, dates of birth, and Social Security numbers. 700Credit serves approximately 18,000 auto dealerships, and the breach involved data collected between May and October 2025. The company is providing credit monitoring services to affected individuals, and authorities are urging victims to consider credit freezes to prevent identity theft and fraud.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Phishing, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> U.S. fintech firm 700Credit has suffered a data breach impacting 5.6 million individuals, with sensitive data including Social Security numbers exposed. The company serves the automotive industry.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> fintech-firm-700credit-discloses-data-breach-affecting-5-6-million</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fintech-firm-700credit-discloses-data-breach-affecting-5-6-million/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: ZERO-DAY ALERT: Apple and Google Scramble to Patch Actively Exploited Flaws</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apple-and-google-patch-actively-exploited-webkit-and-chrome-zero-day-vulnerabilities/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apple-and-google-patch-actively-exploited-webkit-and-chrome-zero-day-vulnerabilities/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> ZERO-DAY ALERT: Apple and Google Scramble to Patch Actively Exploited Flaws</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Apple and Google have issued urgent security updates to address multiple zero-day vulnerabilities being actively exploited in the wild. Apple patched two flaws, CVE-2025-43529 and CVE-2025-14174, both affecting the WebKit browser engine used in iOS, macOS, and Safari. The vulnerabilities were reportedly used in highly targeted spyware attacks. Concurrently, Google patched CVE-2025-14174 in its Chrome browser, a high-severity out-of-bounds memory access flaw in the ANGLE graphics library that could lead to remote code execution. Due to evidence of active exploitation, the U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added CVE-2025-14174 to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, mandating immediate patching for federal agencies.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Apple and Google release emergency security updates to patch actively exploited zero-day vulnerabilities CVE-2025-43529 and CVE-2025-14174 in WebKit and Chrome, which could lead to remote code execution.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> apple-and-google-patch-actively-exploited-webkit-and-chrome-zero-day-vulnerabilities</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apple-and-google-patch-actively-exploited-webkit-and-chrome-zero-day-vulnerabilities/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA KEV Alert: Actively Exploited RCE Flaw in Sierra Wireless Routers</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-sierra-wireless-router-flaw/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-sierra-wireless-router-flaw/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA KEV Alert: Actively Exploited RCE Flaw in Sierra Wireless Routers</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a high-severity vulnerability, CVE-2018-4063, affecting Sierra Wireless AirLink routers to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, indicating it is under active attack. The flaw, with a CVSS score up to 9.9, is an unrestricted file upload vulnerability in the device's ACEManager interface that can be exploited by an authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution (RCE) with root privileges. The affected devices, specifically the AirLink ES450 model, have reached end-of-support, making them a significant risk. CISA has directed federal agencies to either upgrade or decommission the vulnerable products by January 2, 2026.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Industrial Control Systems, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA adds CVE-2018-4063, a critical remote code execution vulnerability in end-of-support Sierra Wireless AirLink routers, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog due to active attacks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-sierra-wireless-router-flaw</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-sierra-wireless-router-flaw/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New 'Gentlemen' Ransomware Group Deploys Advanced GPO and BYOVD Attacks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-gentlemen-ransomware-group-emerges-with-double-extortion-tactics/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-gentlemen-ransomware-group-emerges-with-double-extortion-tactics/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New 'Gentlemen' Ransomware Group Deploys Advanced GPO and BYOVD Attacks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new ransomware operation, identifying itself as the "Gentlemen" group, has been observed conducting double-extortion attacks against corporate networks. The group employs sophisticated techniques to achieve its objectives, including the manipulation of Group Policy Objects (GPOs) for wide-scale ransomware deployment across victim networks. Additionally, the threat actor leverages the 'Bring Your Own Vulnerable Driver' (BYOVD) technique to escalate privileges and disable or bypass endpoint security solutions. The emergence of the Gentlemen group highlights the continued evolution in ransomware tactics, combining data theft with advanced defense evasion and lateral movement strategies.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new ransomware group known as 'Gentlemen' is conducting double-extortion attacks using advanced techniques like Group Policy Object (GPO) modification and Bring Your Own Vulnerable Driver (BYOVD).</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> new-gentlemen-ransomware-group-emerges-with-double-extortion-tactics</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-gentlemen-ransomware-group-emerges-with-double-extortion-tactics/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CVSS 10.0: Atlassian Patches Critical RCE Flaw in Apache Tika Dependency</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/atlassian-patches-critical-cvss-10-flaw-in-apache-tika-dependency/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/atlassian-patches-critical-cvss-10-flaw-in-apache-tika-dependency/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CVSS 10.0: Atlassian Patches Critical RCE Flaw in Apache Tika Dependency</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Atlassian has issued security updates for a critical vulnerability, CVE-2025-66516, in the Apache Tika parser library, a third-party dependency used in many of its products. The flaw, which carries a perfect CVSS score of 10.0, is an XML External Entity (XXE) injection vulnerability. It can be exploited by uploading a specially crafted file, such as a PDF containing a malicious XFA, potentially leading to information disclosure, server-side request forgery (SSRF), or even remote code execution (RCE). The vulnerability affects a wide range of Atlassian's server and data center products, including Jira, Confluence, and Bamboo. Customers are urged to apply the patches immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Atlassian patches a critical CVSS 10.0 vulnerability, CVE-2025-66516, an XXE flaw in Apache Tika that affects Jira, Confluence, and other products and can lead to remote code execution.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> atlassian-patches-critical-cvss-10-flaw-in-apache-tika-dependency</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/atlassian-patches-critical-cvss-10-flaw-in-apache-tika-dependency/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: xHunt Espionage Group Returns, Targeting Kuwait with New PowerShell Backdoors</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/xhunt-cyber-espionage-group-resurfaces-targeting-kuwaiti-organizations/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/xhunt-cyber-espionage-group-resurfaces-targeting-kuwaiti-organizations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> xHunt Espionage Group Returns, Targeting Kuwait with New PowerShell Backdoors</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The cyber-espionage threat actor known as xHunt has resumed operations with a new campaign targeting organizations in Kuwait. Active since at least 2018, the group is focusing its latest attacks on the shipping, transportation, and government sectors. Researchers have observed xHunt infiltrating networks by targeting Microsoft Exchange and IIS web servers. Once inside, the group deploys a family of custom PowerShell-based backdoors, with tool names like 'Hisoka' and 'Netero' derived from the anime 'Hunter x Hunter'. The campaign's objective appears to be long-term intelligence collection and espionage, leveraging stealthy techniques to maintain persistence.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Cyberattack, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The cyber-espionage group xHunt has resurfaced with a new campaign targeting Kuwaiti organizations in government and shipping, using custom PowerShell backdoors after compromising Exchange and IIS servers.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> xhunt-cyber-espionage-group-resurfaces-targeting-kuwaiti-organizations</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/xhunt-cyber-espionage-group-resurfaces-targeting-kuwaiti-organizations/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New '01flip' Ransomware, Written in Rust, Targets Critical Infrastructure in APAC</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-cross-platform-01flip-ransomware-in-rust-targets-critical-infrastructure/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-cross-platform-01flip-ransomware-in-rust-targets-critical-infrastructure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New '01flip' Ransomware, Written in Rust, Targets Critical Infrastructure in APAC</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new and stealthy cross-platform ransomware strain named "01flip" has been discovered targeting critical infrastructure organizations in the Asia-Pacific region. The malware is written in the Rust programming language, enabling it to be compiled for both Windows and Linux systems and enhancing its ability to evade detection. Attackers have been observed exploiting exposed services for initial access, then deploying the open-source Sliver command-and-control (C2) framework for reconnaissance and lateral movement before executing the 01flip ransomware. The campaign highlights a growing trend of threat actors using modern, memory-safe languages like Rust to develop more sophisticated and evasive malware.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Malware, Industrial Control Systems</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new cross-platform ransomware named '01flip', written in Rust for stealth, is targeting critical infrastructure in the Asia-Pacific region, using the Sliver C2 framework for post-exploitation.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> new-cross-platform-01flip-ransomware-in-rust-targets-critical-infrastructure</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-cross-platform-01flip-ransomware-in-rust-targets-critical-infrastructure/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: LastPass Fined £1.2M by UK Regulator Over 2022 Security Failures</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-regulator-fines-lastpass-1-2-million-for-2022-data-breach/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-regulator-fines-lastpass-1-2-million-for-2022-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> LastPass Fined £1.2M by UK Regulator Over 2022 Security Failures</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The UK's Information Commissioner's Office (ICO) has fined password manager provider LastPass £1.2 million (approximately $1.6 million) for significant security failures that led to a major data breach in 2022. The regulator found that LastPass failed to implement adequate technical and security measures to protect its users' data. The 2022 incident resulted in a threat actor gaining unauthorized access to a backup database, which contained the data of 1.6 million UK users, including encrypted password vaults. The fine highlights the serious regulatory consequences for security companies that do not meet their data protection obligations.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Regulatory, Data Breach, Policy and Compliance</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The UK's Information Commissioner's Office (ICO) has fined LastPass £1.2 million over the 2022 data breach, citing inadequate security measures that exposed the data of 1.6 million users.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> uk-regulator-fines-lastpass-1-2-million-for-2022-data-breach</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-regulator-fines-lastpass-1-2-million-for-2022-data-breach/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: India Confirms GPS Spoofing Attacks Targeted Seven Major Airports</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/indian-government-confirms-gps-spoofing-at-major-airports/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/indian-government-confirms-gps-spoofing-at-major-airports/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> India Confirms GPS Spoofing Attacks Targeted Seven Major Airports</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Indian government has officially confirmed that a series of cyber incidents involving GPS spoofing have occurred at seven of the nation's major airports. The attacks, which targeted airports in Delhi, Mumbai, Kolkata, and Bengaluru among others, disrupted navigation data for aircraft utilizing GPS-based landing procedures. Despite the signal manipulation, government officials reported that no flights were canceled or diverted. The successful handling of the incidents was attributed to the implementation of contingency measures and robust safeguards by Air Traffic Control, which allowed for safe operations using alternative navigation aids. The events underscore the growing vulnerability of critical transportation infrastructure to cyberattacks.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cyberattack, Industrial Control Systems, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Indian government has confirmed that GPS spoofing attacks occurred at seven major airports, disrupting aircraft navigation systems, though no flights were ultimately diverted due to contingency measures.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> indian-government-confirms-gps-spoofing-at-major-airports</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/indian-government-confirms-gps-spoofing-at-major-airports/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Apple Rushes iOS 26.2 Update to Patch Two Actively Exploited Zero-Days</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apple-patches-two-actively-exploited-zero-days-in-ios-26-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apple-patches-two-actively-exploited-zero-days-in-ios-26-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Apple Rushes iOS 26.2 Update to Patch Two Actively Exploited Zero-Days</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Apple has released an emergency security update, iOS 26.2 and iPadOS 26.2, to address 26 vulnerabilities. Among these are two critical zero-day flaws, CVE-2025-43529 and CVE-2025-14174, both residing in the WebKit browser engine. The company confirmed reports that these vulnerabilities have been actively exploited in sophisticated, targeted spyware campaigns, potentially allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code on unpatched devices. The update also patches a severe kernel vulnerability, CVE-2025-46285, that could grant an attacker root privileges. All iPhone and iPad users are urged to update their devices immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Mobile Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Apple has released an emergency security update, iOS 26.2, to patch two actively exploited zero-day vulnerabilities in WebKit (CVE-2025-43529, CVE-2025-14174) that could lead to arbitrary code execution.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> apple-patches-two-actively-exploited-zero-days-in-ios-26-2</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apple-patches-two-actively-exploited-zero-days-in-ios-26-2/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA KEV Alert: Actively Exploited RCE Flaw in Sierra Wireless Routers</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-flaw-in-sierra-wireless-routers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-flaw-in-sierra-wireless-routers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA KEV Alert: Actively Exploited RCE Flaw in Sierra Wireless Routers</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a critical vulnerability in Sierra Wireless AirLink routers, CVE-2018-4063, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog. The flaw, which has a CVSS score as high as 9.9, is an unrestricted file upload vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution (RCE). Due to evidence of active exploitation, CISA has mandated that all Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies patch the vulnerability by a specified deadline, highlighting the severe risk it poses to network infrastructure.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Industrial Control Systems</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA has added CVE-2018-4063, a critical remote code execution vulnerability in Sierra Wireless AirLink routers, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog due to active exploitation.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-flaw-in-sierra-wireless-routers</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-flaw-in-sierra-wireless-routers/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Germany Summons Russian Ambassador Over Suspected Air Traffic Control Cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/germany-summons-russian-ambassador-over-air-traffic-control-hack-allegations/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/germany-summons-russian-ambassador-over-air-traffic-control-hack-allegations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Germany Summons Russian Ambassador Over Suspected Air Traffic Control Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>In a significant diplomatic escalation, the German government has summoned the Russian Ambassador to Berlin following allegations of a cyberattack targeting the nation's air traffic control (ATC) systems. The incident, reported on December 13, 2025, has raised grave concerns about the security of Germany's critical national infrastructure and points towards a potential act of state-sponsored cyber-espionage or disruption. While technical details remain undisclosed, the move underscores the high stakes of cyber hostilities between Western nations and Russia.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cyberattack, Threat Actor, Industrial Control Systems</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The German government has summoned the Russian Ambassador following allegations of a state-sponsored cyberattack targeting the country's critical air traffic control systems.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> germany-summons-russian-ambassador-over-air-traffic-control-hack-allegations</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/germany-summons-russian-ambassador-over-air-traffic-control-hack-allegations/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: KillSec Ransomware Hits U.S. Financial Firm Daba Finance in Data Extortion Attack</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/killsec-ransomware-group-attacks-daba-finance/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/killsec-ransomware-group-attacks-daba-finance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> KillSec Ransomware Hits U.S. Financial Firm Daba Finance in Data Extortion Attack</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The ransomware group known as KillSec has claimed responsibility for a cyberattack against Daba Finance Inc., a financial services company in the United States. On December 14, 2025, the group listed the company on its data leak site, employing a double-extortion tactic by threatening to release sensitive stolen data if a ransom is not paid. This incident underscores the persistent threat that data extortion gangs pose to the financial sector, which remains a high-value target due to the sensitive customer and corporate information it handles.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The KillSec ransomware group has claimed a data breach attack against Daba Finance Inc., a U.S. financial services company, threatening to leak stolen data on its extortion site.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> killsec-ransomware-group-attacks-daba-finance</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/killsec-ransomware-group-attacks-daba-finance/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Massive Data Leak: Unsecured 16TB Database Exposes 4.3 Billion Professional Records</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/unsecured-16tb-mongodb-database-exposes-4-3-billion-professional-records/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/unsecured-16tb-mongodb-database-exposes-4-3-billion-professional-records/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Massive Data Leak: Unsecured 16TB Database Exposes 4.3 Billion Professional Records</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A colossal 16-terabyte MongoDB database containing approximately 4.3 billion professional records was discovered publicly exposed on the internet. The data, largely scraped from LinkedIn, includes full names, email addresses, phone numbers, work histories, and social media profiles. Security researcher Bob Diachenko found the database in late November 2025, and it was secured shortly after. The owner is suspected to be a lead-generation company. This exposure creates a massive risk for sophisticated, AI-driven phishing and social engineering campaigns on a global scale.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Cloud Security, Phishing</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A publicly accessible 16TB MongoDB database was discovered containing 4.3 billion professional records, including names, emails, and job histories, largely scraped from LinkedIn.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> unsecured-16tb-mongodb-database-exposes-4-3-billion-professional-records</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/unsecured-16tb-mongodb-database-exposes-4-3-billion-professional-records/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: WestJet Data Breach Exposes Info of 1.2 Million Passengers; Scattered Spider Suspected</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/westjet-discloses-data-breach-affecting-1-2-million-customers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/westjet-discloses-data-breach-affecting-1-2-million-customers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> WestJet Data Breach Exposes Info of 1.2 Million Passengers; Scattered Spider Suspected</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Canadian airline WestJet has disclosed a significant data breach that occurred in June 2025, impacting approximately 1.2 million passengers. The compromised data includes sensitive personal information such as names, contact details, and travel documentation. While investigations are ongoing, some reports suggest the notorious Scattered Spider hacking group, known for its social engineering prowess, may be behind the attack. The breach poses a serious risk of identity theft and fraud for the affected customers.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Threat Actor, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Canadian airline WestJet disclosed a data breach affecting 1.2 million passengers, exposing names, contact details, and travel documents, with the Scattered Spider hacking group potentially responsible.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> westjet-discloses-data-breach-affecting-1-2-million-customers</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/westjet-discloses-data-breach-affecting-1-2-million-customers/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: "Catastrophic" Data Breach at Norwegian News Agency NTB Exposes Customer Data</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/norwegian-news-agency-ntb-suffers-major-data-breach/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/norwegian-news-agency-ntb-suffers-major-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> "Catastrophic" Data Breach at Norwegian News Agency NTB Exposes Customer Data</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>NTB (Norsk Telegrambyrå), Norway's leading news and content provider, has disclosed what it calls a "catastrophic" data breach that occurred in early December 2025. The company announced on December 13 that attackers exploited vulnerabilities in its systems to gain unauthorized access to its customer database, exposing sensitive personal information, detailed customer profiles, and internal communications for thousands of users. NTB is now undertaking a major overhaul of its security infrastructure in response.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Cyberattack, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Norwegian news agency NTB has disclosed a 'catastrophic' data breach where attackers exploited security vulnerabilities to expose sensitive personal information of thousands of users.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> norwegian-news-agency-ntb-suffers-major-data-breach</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/norwegian-news-agency-ntb-suffers-major-data-breach/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Eswatini Faces Cybersecurity Crisis as Government Fails to Act on Rising Threats</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/eswatini-cybersecurity-crisis-amidst-government-inaction/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/eswatini-cybersecurity-crisis-amidst-government-inaction/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Eswatini Faces Cybersecurity Crisis as Government Fails to Act on Rising Threats</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A report published on December 13, 2025, reveals a deepening cybersecurity crisis in the Kingdom of Eswatini. The nation is experiencing a significant increase in cyberattacks targeting citizens, businesses, and government bodies. This surge is compounded by a lack of effective government response, characterized by outdated laws, minimal funding for cybersecurity initiatives, a severe shortage of skilled personnel, and a failure to implement its own national cybersecurity strategy. As a result, the country's digital infrastructure remains highly vulnerable to escalating threats.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Other</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A December 2025 report details a cybersecurity crisis in Eswatini, where rising cyberattacks are met with government inaction, outdated laws, and a severe lack of resources and skilled personnel.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> eswatini-cybersecurity-crisis-amidst-government-inaction</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/eswatini-cybersecurity-crisis-amidst-government-inaction/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Other</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Qilin Ransomware Continues Global Spree, Hits Greek Firm Vlp Hellas</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-group-targets-greek-firm-vlp-hellas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-group-targets-greek-firm-vlp-hellas/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Qilin Ransomware Continues Global Spree, Hits Greek Firm Vlp Hellas</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The prolific Qilin ransomware group has expanded its list of victims, claiming an attack on Vlp Hellas, a business services firm in Greece, on December 14, 2025. This incident is part of a broader, ongoing campaign by the group, which also recently claimed attacks on Nepes in South Korea, Spitzer Auto Group in the U.S., and Dan Technologies in Denmark. Operating a double-extortion model, Qilin exfiltrates sensitive data and threatens to leak it if the ransom is not paid, demonstrating its continued threat to organizations across various industries worldwide.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Qilin ransomware group (also known as Agenda) has claimed a cyberattack on the Greek business services firm Vlp Hellas, threatening to leak data in a double-extortion attack.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> qilin-ransomware-group-targets-greek-firm-vlp-hellas</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-group-targets-greek-firm-vlp-hellas/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: 2025: The Year Cybersecurity 'Crossed the AI Rubicon'</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/2025-the-year-ai-redefines-cyberattacks-and-defense/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/2025-the-year-ai-redefines-cyberattacks-and-defense/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> 2025: The Year Cybersecurity 'Crossed the AI Rubicon'</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>According to analysis published on December 14, 2025, the year 2025 represents a fundamental and irreversible turning point for the cybersecurity industry. The widespread integration of Artificial Intelligence (AI) into both offensive and defensive strategies has permanently altered the threat landscape. Key trends include the rise of 'agentic AI' capable of autonomous attacks, adaptive threats that change tactics in real-time, and a surge in highly convincing, AI-generated phishing and deepfake content. While defenders are also adopting AI, the 'great acceleration' in threat complexity is forcing a complete rethink of security playbooks.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Intelligence, Other</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A 2025 year-in-review analysis concludes that the integration of artificial intelligence into both cyberattacks and defense strategies has permanently altered the threat landscape.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> 2025-the-year-ai-redefines-cyberattacks-and-defense</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/2025-the-year-ai-redefines-cyberattacks-and-defense/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Other</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Qilin Ransomware Gang Adds Business Services Firm B Dynamic to Leak Site</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-group-claims-b-dynamic-as-new-victim/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-group-claims-b-dynamic-as-new-victim/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Qilin Ransomware Gang Adds Business Services Firm B Dynamic to Leak Site</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Qilin ransomware group, a prominent ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) operation, has listed business services company 'B Dynamic' as its latest victim on its dark web data leak site. The December 1, 2025, posting indicates that the company has suffered a network compromise and data exfiltration. By publicizing the breach, the Qilin group is employing its standard double-extortion tactic to pressure the victim into paying a ransom to prevent the public release of stolen data. This incident highlights the persistent threat from established ransomware gangs.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Qilin ransomware group has listed B Dynamic on its data leak site, indicating a successful breach and data exfiltration as part of its double-extortion campaign.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> qilin-ransomware-group-claims-b-dynamic-as-new-victim</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-group-claims-b-dynamic-as-new-victim/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>