<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:07:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: React2Shell Nightmare: CVSS 10.0 Flaw Under Mass Exploitation, CISA Issues Emergency Directive</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/react2shell-critical-rce-flaw-mass-exploited-by-chinese-apts/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/react2shell-critical-rce-flaw-mass-exploited-by-chinese-apts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> React2Shell Nightmare: CVSS 10.0 Flaw Under Mass Exploitation, CISA Issues Emergency Directive</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A critical remote code execution vulnerability with a CVSS score of 10.0, dubbed 'React2Shell' and tracked as CVE-2025-55182, is being actively and widely exploited. The flaw resides in the React Server Components (RSC) 'Flight' protocol and allows unauthenticated attackers to take complete control of vulnerable servers. Within hours of its public disclosure on December 3, 2025, China-nexus threat actors, including Earth Lamia and Jackpot Panda, began mass scanning and exploitation. The vulnerability affects React 19.x and popular frameworks like Next.js 15.x/16.x. In response to the widespread attacks, CISA has added CVE-2025-55182 to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, mandating immediate patching for federal agencies.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Cyberattack, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A critical 10.0 CVSS RCE vulnerability, React2Shell (CVE-2025-55182), is being mass-exploited in React and Next.js applications. Learn about the threat, IOCs, and mitigation steps.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> react2shell-critical-rce-flaw-mass-exploited-by-chinese-apts</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/react2shell-critical-rce-flaw-mass-exploited-by-chinese-apts/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Android Under Attack: Google Patches Two Actively Exploited Zero-Days in Massive December Update</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/android-patches-two-actively-exploited-zero-days-in-december-update/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/android-patches-two-actively-exploited-zero-days-in-december-update/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Android Under Attack: Google Patches Two Actively Exploited Zero-Days in Massive December Update</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Google has released its December 2025 Android Security Bulletin, patching 107 security flaws, including two high-severity zero-day vulnerabilities that are being actively exploited in limited, targeted attacks. The zero-days, CVE-2025-48633 (information disclosure) and CVE-2025-48572 (privilege escalation), both reside in the Android Framework. CISA has promptly added both vulnerabilities to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, requiring federal agencies to patch by December 23, 2025. The update also fixes seven critical-severity bugs, one of which could lead to remote denial-of-service. Android users are urged to apply the update as soon as it becomes available from their device manufacturer.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Mobile Security, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Google's December 2025 Android update patches 107 vulnerabilities, including two actively exploited zero-days (CVE-2025-48633, CVE-2025-48572) added to CISA's KEV catalog. Update your device now.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> android-patches-two-actively-exploited-zero-days-in-december-update</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/android-patches-two-actively-exploited-zero-days-in-december-update/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: FinCEN: Ransomware Payments Skyrocket Past $2.1 Billion, Bitcoin Remains King</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fincen-report-ransomware-payments-top-2-1-billion-since-2022/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fincen-report-ransomware-payments-top-2-1-billion-since-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> FinCEN: Ransomware Payments Skyrocket Past $2.1 Billion, Bitcoin Remains King</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new report from the U.S. Treasury's Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN) indicates that ransomware payments reported under the Bank Secrecy Act (BSA) totaled more than $2.1 billion between January 2022 and December 2024. The analysis shows a significant peak in 2023, with $1.1 billion paid across 1,512 incidents. Despite law enforcement actions against major groups like ALPHV/BlackCat and LockBit, activity remained high in 2024. Bitcoin was the payment method in 97% of cases, with the manufacturing, financial services, and healthcare sectors being the most frequent targets. The report underscores the persistent and lucrative nature of the ransomware ecosystem.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Regulatory, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A FinCEN report details over $2.1 billion in ransomware payments from 2022-2024, with a peak of $1.1 billion in 2023. Bitcoin dominates as the payment method, and top targets include manufacturing and healthcare.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> fincen-report-ransomware-payments-top-2-1-billion-since-2022</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fincen-report-ransomware-payments-top-2-1-billion-since-2022/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Cl0p Implicated in Oracle Zero-Day Attacks, Breaching UPenn and University of Phoenix</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/clop-suspected-in-oracle-zero-day-attacks-on-upenn-and-university-of-phoenix/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/clop-suspected-in-oracle-zero-day-attacks-on-upenn-and-university-of-phoenix/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Cl0p Implicated in Oracle Zero-Day Attacks, Breaching UPenn and University of Phoenix</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The University of Pennsylvania and the University of Phoenix have both reported data breaches resulting from the exploitation of zero-day vulnerabilities in their Oracle E-Business Suite servers. The attacks have compromised the personal information of at least 1,488 individuals at UPenn and a much larger, unspecified number of students, alumni, and staff at the University of Phoenix. Security researchers suspect the notorious Cl0p ransomware gang is behind the campaign, continuing their pattern of exploiting vulnerabilities in widely used enterprise software for large-scale data theft and extortion. Both institutions are currently notifying affected individuals.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Threat Actor, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Cl0p ransomware gang is suspected of exploiting Oracle E-Business Suite zero-day vulnerabilities to breach the University of Pennsylvania and University of Phoenix, compromising sensitive personal data.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> clop-suspected-in-oracle-zero-day-attacks-on-upenn-and-university-of-phoenix</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/clop-suspected-in-oracle-zero-day-attacks-on-upenn-and-university-of-phoenix/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Supply Chain Attack: Marquis Software Breach Hits 74 Banks, Akira Ransomware Suspected</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/marquis-software-breach-exposes-data-from-74-banks-and-credit-unions/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/marquis-software-breach-exposes-data-from-74-banks-and-credit-unions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Supply Chain Attack: Marquis Software Breach Hits 74 Banks, Akira Ransomware Suspected</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Marquis Software Solutions, a U.S.-based financial software provider, has suffered a major data breach, compromising the sensitive information of over 400,000 customers across 74 client banks and credit unions. This significant supply chain attack is suspected to be the work of the Akira ransomware gang. According to investigators, the threat actors likely gained initial access by exploiting vulnerabilities in SonicWall firewall devices on Marquis's network. This incident highlights the cascading risk in the financial sector, where a compromise at a single software vendor can have widespread consequences for numerous downstream institutions and their customers.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Data Breach, Ransomware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Financial software provider Marquis Software Solutions suffers a major data breach affecting 74 banks and credit unions. The Akira ransomware gang is suspected of exploiting SonicWall vulnerabilities in the attack.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> marquis-software-breach-exposes-data-from-74-banks-and-credit-unions</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/marquis-software-breach-exposes-data-from-74-banks-and-credit-unions/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Chinese APTs Deploy 'BRICKSTORM' Backdoor to Infiltrate VMware Environments</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-linked-hackers-use-stealthy-brickstorm-backdoor-in-vmware-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-linked-hackers-use-stealthy-brickstorm-backdoor-in-vmware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Chinese APTs Deploy 'BRICKSTORM' Backdoor to Infiltrate VMware Environments</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A joint advisory from U.S. and Canadian cybersecurity agencies has exposed a sophisticated backdoor named 'BRICKSTORM,' which is being used by Chinese state-affiliated hackers to target VMware vSphere environments. The malware is part of a long-running espionage campaign tracked as 'Salt Typhoon' and provides attackers with stealthy, long-term persistence. BRICKSTORM's capabilities include creating hidden virtual machines, stealing credentials by snapshotting active VMs, and evading detection. The campaign has primarily targeted government and IT sector organizations, demonstrating the adversary's deep expertise in virtualized infrastructure.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Malware, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A joint U.S. and Canadian advisory details BRICKSTORM, a new backdoor used by Chinese hackers (Salt Typhoon) to attack VMware vSphere for long-term espionage, credential theft, and persistence.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> china-linked-hackers-use-stealthy-brickstorm-backdoor-in-vmware-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-linked-hackers-use-stealthy-brickstorm-backdoor-in-vmware-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New Android Banking Trojan 'Albiriox' Targets 400+ Finance Apps via MaaS Model</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/albiriox-new-android-banking-trojan-sold-as-maas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/albiriox-new-android-banking-trojan-sold-as-maas/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New Android Banking Trojan 'Albiriox' Targets 400+ Finance Apps via MaaS Model</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new, highly sophisticated Android banking trojan named 'Albiriox' has been discovered by security researchers. It is being sold on a Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) basis, enabling widespread distribution by various cybercriminals. The malware is designed to target over 400 distinct financial and cryptocurrency applications worldwide. Albiriox employs advanced techniques to commit on-device fraud, including abusing Android's accessibility services, using VNC for full remote device control, and deploying dynamic overlay attacks to steal credentials. A notable feature is its 'black-screen masking' capability, which conceals the attacker's remote actions from the user, allowing them to perform fraudulent transactions undetected.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Mobile Security, Phishing</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Researchers have discovered Albiriox, a new Android banking trojan sold as Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) that targets over 400 financial apps using VNC, overlays, and black-screen masking.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> albiriox-new-android-banking-trojan-sold-as-maas</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/albiriox-new-android-banking-trojan-sold-as-maas/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: White House Sets 2025 Deadline for Post-Quantum Crypto Readiness</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/white-house-eo-sets-new-deadlines-for-post-quantum-crypto-transition/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/white-house-eo-sets-new-deadlines-for-post-quantum-crypto-transition/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> White House Sets 2025 Deadline for Post-Quantum Crypto Readiness</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The White House has issued a new Executive Order to accelerate the U.S. federal government's transition to post-quantum cryptography (PQC). The order sets a critical deadline of December 1, 2025, for several key initiatives. It directs CISA and the NSA to create and maintain a list of commercially available products that support PQC standards, guiding federal procurement. It also mandates the development of new requirements for federal agencies to support TLS 1.3, a necessary precursor for PQC integration. Additionally, NIST is tasked with updating its Secure Software Development Framework (SSDF) to include practices for developing quantum-resistant software.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new White House Executive Order sets a December 1, 2025 deadline for key federal actions on post-quantum cryptography (PQC), including a list of PQC-ready products and TLS 1.3 support.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> white-house-eo-sets-new-deadlines-for-post-quantum-crypto-transition</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/white-house-eo-sets-new-deadlines-for-post-quantum-crypto-transition/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: WhatsApp Worm Spreads Astaroth Banking Trojan in New Brazilian Campaign</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/astaroth-banking-trojan-spreads-via-whatsapp-worm-in-brazil/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/astaroth-banking-trojan-spreads-via-whatsapp-worm-in-brazil/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> WhatsApp Worm Spreads Astaroth Banking Trojan in New Brazilian Campaign</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new malware campaign, tracked as STAC3150, is targeting banking users in Brazil by using WhatsApp Web as a distribution vector for the Astaroth banking trojan. The attack begins with a social engineering lure sent via WhatsApp, which persuades the victim to download a malicious ZIP archive. The archive contains a VBS or HTA file that, when executed, initiates a multi-stage infection process to deploy the Astaroth trojan. Astaroth is a well-known information stealer designed to capture banking credentials and other sensitive data. This campaign highlights the increasing use of popular messaging platforms for malware delivery.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Phishing, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A malware campaign in Brazil, tracked as STAC3150, is using a WhatsApp worm to spread the Astaroth banking trojan, tricking users into executing malicious VBS and HTA files.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> astaroth-banking-trojan-spreads-via-whatsapp-worm-in-brazil</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/astaroth-banking-trojan-spreads-via-whatsapp-worm-in-brazil/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: SharePoint Flaw Chain Exploited to Deploy Warlock Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sharepoint-flaws-chained-to-deliver-warlock-ransomware/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sharepoint-flaws-chained-to-deliver-warlock-ransomware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> SharePoint Flaw Chain Exploited to Deploy Warlock Ransomware</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new attack campaign attributed to the threat actor Storm-2603 is exploiting a chain of Microsoft SharePoint vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704) for initial access. Post-exploitation, the attackers deploy Velociraptor, a legitimate digital forensics and incident response (DFIR) tool, for reconnaissance and persistence. By abusing a trusted tool, the attackers blend in with normal administrative activity, evading detection. In several confirmed incidents, this attack chain culminates in the deployment of the Warlock ransomware. This 'living-off-the-land' technique highlights a sophisticated approach to facilitating ransomware attacks.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Vulnerability, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Threat actor Storm-2603 is exploiting SharePoint vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704) and abusing the Velociraptor DFIR tool to deploy Warlock ransomware.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> sharepoint-flaws-chained-to-deliver-warlock-ransomware</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sharepoint-flaws-chained-to-deliver-warlock-ransomware/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Supply Chain Breach at Vendor Marquis Exposes Data From Dozens of US Banks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/marquis-software-supply-chain-breach-hits-dozens-of-us-banks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/marquis-software-supply-chain-breach-hits-dozens-of-us-banks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Supply Chain Breach at Vendor Marquis Exposes Data From Dozens of US Banks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A ransomware attack on Marquis Software Solutions, a marketing and data analytics vendor for the financial industry, has resulted in a significant supply chain data breach affecting dozens of U.S. banks and credit unions. Marquis began notifying its clients on November 26, 2025, about the incident, which was first detected in August. The breach exposed highly sensitive customer information, including names, Social Security numbers, taxpayer IDs, and financial account details, that the financial institutions had entrusted to the vendor. While the banks' internal systems were not compromised, the incident highlights the profound risks associated with third-party vendors. At least 42,000 individuals in Maine alone have been affected, and Marquis is offering credit monitoring services to impacted customers.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Data Breach, Ransomware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A ransomware attack on vendor Marquis Software Solutions has led to a major supply chain data breach, exposing sensitive customer data from dozens of U.S. banks and credit unions.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> marquis-software-supply-chain-breach-hits-dozens-of-us-banks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 2</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 2 updates recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/marquis-software-supply-chain-breach-hits-dozens-of-us-banks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: React2Shell Added to CISA's KEV Catalog After Widespread Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-react2shell-to-kev-catalog-amidst-active-exploitation-surge/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-react2shell-to-kev-catalog-amidst-active-exploitation-surge/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> React2Shell Added to CISA's KEV Catalog After Widespread Exploitation</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added the critical React2Shell vulnerability, CVE-2025-55182, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog following a surge in active and widespread attacks. The flaw, a CVSS 10.0 remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in Meta's React Server Components, is being exploited by Chinese state-sponsored groups like Earth Lamia and UNC5174, as well as botnets such as Mirai and RondoDox. Attackers are deploying a range of payloads including the SNOWLIGHT and VShell backdoors, cryptocurrency miners, and Cobalt Strike beacons. The vulnerability's ease of exploitation via a single HTTP request puts millions of services using frameworks like Next.js at risk, prompting CISA to set a December 26, 2025, patching deadline for federal agencies.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Cyberattack, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA adds critical RCE vulnerability CVE-2025-55182 (React2Shell) to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog due to active exploitation by Chinese APTs. Federal agencies must patch by Dec 26.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-adds-react2shell-to-kev-catalog-amidst-active-exploitation-surge</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-react2shell-to-kev-catalog-amidst-active-exploitation-surge/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Clop Ransomware Breaches Barts Health NHS Trust via Oracle Zero-Day</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/barts-health-nhs-trust-hit-by-clop-ransomware-via-oracle-zero-day/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/barts-health-nhs-trust-hit-by-clop-ransomware-via-oracle-zero-day/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Clop Ransomware Breaches Barts Health NHS Trust via Oracle Zero-Day</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Clop ransomware gang has claimed responsibility for a significant data breach at Barts Health NHS Trust, one of England's largest healthcare providers. The attack, which occurred in August 2025, leveraged a zero-day vulnerability in Oracle E-Business Suite. The threat actors exfiltrated files from an invoice database containing the names and addresses of patients and former staff. This data was later published on Clop's dark web leak site. While core clinical systems were reportedly unaffected, the compromised information poses a serious risk for follow-on social engineering and fraud attacks. The incident is part of a wider campaign by Clop targeting the now-patched Oracle vulnerability.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Clop ransomware gang breaches Barts Health NHS Trust by exploiting a zero-day in Oracle E-Business Suite, leading to the theft and publication of patient and staff data.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> barts-health-nhs-trust-hit-by-clop-ransomware-via-oracle-zero-day</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/barts-health-nhs-trust-hit-by-clop-ransomware-via-oracle-zero-day/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Malicious Go Packages Impersonating Google UUID Library Steal Data</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/malicious-go-packages-impersonate-google-uuid-library-in-supply-chain-attack/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/malicious-go-packages-impersonate-google-uuid-library-in-supply-chain-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Malicious Go Packages Impersonating Google UUID Library Steal Data</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A sophisticated and long-running supply chain attack targeting Go developers has been discovered, active since at least May 2021. The attack involves two malicious packages, `github.com/bpoorman/uuid` and `github.com/bpoorman/uid`, which impersonate a popular Google UUID library using a typosquatting technique. The counterfeit packages are fully functional to avoid suspicion but contain a hidden backdoor. A specific function, `Valid`, is weaponized to secretly encrypt and exfiltrate any data passed to it, such as user IDs or session tokens, to an external paste site. This stealthy method allows the attacker, 'bpoorman', to siphon sensitive information from compromised applications.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Malware, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A four-year-long supply chain attack using malicious Go packages that impersonate Google's UUID library has been discovered, designed to steal sensitive developer data.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> malicious-go-packages-impersonate-google-uuid-library-in-supply-chain-attack</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/malicious-go-packages-impersonate-google-uuid-library-in-supply-chain-attack/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: US &amp; Canada Warn of Chinese 'Brickstorm' Malware Targeting Critical Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-canada-warn-of-chinese-brickstorm-malware-targeting-vmware/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-canada-warn-of-chinese-brickstorm-malware-targeting-vmware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> US &amp; Canada Warn of Chinese 'Brickstorm' Malware Targeting Critical Infrastructure</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The United States and Canada have issued a joint cybersecurity advisory regarding 'Brickstorm,' a sophisticated malware backdoor attributed to state-sponsored hackers from the People's Republic of China (PRC). The malware specifically targets Broadcom's VMware vSphere, a ubiquitous virtualization platform. Brickstorm is designed to establish long-term, stealthy persistence within government and information technology networks. Its primary functions are to steal login credentials and other sensitive data, providing attackers with deep access that could be used for espionage or future disruptive and destructive attacks.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Malware, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A joint advisory from the US and Canada warns of 'Brickstorm', a sophisticated malware backdoor used by Chinese state-sponsored hackers to target VMware vSphere for espionage.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> us-canada-warn-of-chinese-brickstorm-malware-targeting-vmware</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-canada-warn-of-chinese-brickstorm-malware-targeting-vmware/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: WhatsApp Flaw Leads to Surge in No-Click Account Hijackings</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/whatsapp-flaw-sparks-surge-in-no-click-account-hijackings/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/whatsapp-flaw-sparks-surge-in-no-click-account-hijackings/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> WhatsApp Flaw Leads to Surge in No-Click Account Hijackings</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A technical vulnerability in WhatsApp is being actively exploited to conduct 'no-click' account takeovers, according to warnings from Kuwait's National Cyber Security Center and security experts. Unlike typical phishing attacks, this method allows threat actors to hijack a user's account without any interaction from the victim, such as clicking a link. The attacks have led to a sharp increase in compromised social media accounts in Kuwait and are believed to be occurring globally. While technical details of the flaw are sparse, officials and experts are urgently advising all WhatsApp users to enable two-factor authentication (2FA) as the most effective defense against this specific attack vector.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Mobile Security, Vulnerability, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 3 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A vulnerability in WhatsApp is being actively exploited in no-click attacks to hijack user accounts, with a surge reported in Kuwait. Users are urged to enable 2FA.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> whatsapp-flaw-sparks-surge-in-no-click-account-hijackings</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/whatsapp-flaw-sparks-surge-in-no-click-account-hijackings/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: 2025 Government Shutdown Exposed Critical Federal Cybersecurity Gaps</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/2025-government-shutdown-exposed-critical-federal-cyber-gaps/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/2025-government-shutdown-exposed-critical-federal-cyber-gaps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> 2025 Government Shutdown Exposed Critical Federal Cybersecurity Gaps</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A Forbes analysis published on December 6, 2025, reveals that the record-breaking 43-day U.S. government shutdown created severe gaps in national cybersecurity. The shutdown led to widespread furloughs and operational disruptions at the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), significantly impairing the federal government's ability to perform threat hunting and network monitoring. The timing was especially poor, as it coincided with the Department of Defense implementing new, mandatory Cybersecurity Maturity Model Certification (CMMC) rules for defense contractors, creating a paradox of weakened federal defenses alongside stricter private sector requirements.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Security Operations</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 3 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The 2025 US government shutdown severely weakened federal cybersecurity operations at CISA, creating dangerous gaps in threat monitoring and response capabilities.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> 2025-government-shutdown-exposed-critical-federal-cyber-gaps</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/2025-government-shutdown-exposed-critical-federal-cyber-gaps/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Mexico's Maguen Group Launches Global Cybersecurity Brand 'Fortem'</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/maguen-group-launches-fortem-cybersecurity-to-global-market/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/maguen-group-launches-fortem-cybersecurity-to-global-market/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Mexico's Maguen Group Launches Global Cybersecurity Brand 'Fortem'</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Maguen Group, a leading private security firm based in Mexico, has officially launched Fortem Cybersecurity, its new global cybersecurity brand, on December 7, 2025. The new entity is an evolution of the company's existing cybersecurity arm, MT Cyber, which it acquired in 2019. With Fortem, Maguen Group aims to 'democratize cybersecurity' by offering enterprise-level protection to companies of all sizes. The launch marks a strategic push for global expansion, leveraging its existing presence in Mexico, Ecuador, and Germany, with the United States targeted as the next major market.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Other</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 2 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Maguen Group, a leading Mexican security company, has launched Fortem Cybersecurity, a new global brand aimed at expanding its cybersecurity services worldwide.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> maguen-group-launches-fortem-cybersecurity-to-global-market</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/maguen-group-launches-fortem-cybersecurity-to-global-market/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Other</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Malicious Rust Package 'evm-units' Targets Web3 Developers</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/malicious-rust-package-evm-units-targets-web3-developers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/malicious-rust-package-evm-units-targets-web3-developers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Malicious Rust Package 'evm-units' Targets Web3 Developers</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A malicious software package named 'evm-units' has been discovered and removed from Rust's official crates.io registry. The package, downloaded over 7,200 times, targeted Web3 developers by impersonating a legitimate utility for the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM). While appearing functional, the crate contained a stealthy, multi-stage loader designed to download and execute operating system-specific malware. The malware included code to specifically evade 360 Total Security, a popular antivirus in China, suggesting the threat actor's focus was on stealing cryptocurrency from developers, likely in the Asian market. A second package, 'uniswap-utils', was also removed for depending on the malicious crate.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Malware, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Malicious Rust package 'evm-units' found on crates.io impersonated an Ethereum utility to target Web3 developers with malware designed for cryptocurrency theft.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> malicious-rust-package-evm-units-targets-web3-developers</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/malicious-rust-package-evm-units-targets-web3-developers/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Indonesian Gambling Network Abused as Malicious C2 Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/indonesian-gambling-network-doubles-as-malicious-c2-infrastructure/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/indonesian-gambling-network-doubles-as-malicious-c2-infrastructure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Indonesian Gambling Network Abused as Malicious C2 Infrastructure</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Researchers have uncovered a vast, dual-use cybercrime infrastructure in Indonesia. A sprawling network, primarily created to support illegal online gambling, is also being rented out or used as a command-and-control (C2) and anonymity service for malware operators. By routing their malicious traffic through the high-volume gambling network, threat actors can effectively hide their C2 communications and obscure their origins. This co-opting of a gray-market infrastructure presents a significant and complex challenge for threat detection and attribution, providing a resilient and hidden platform for various malware campaigns.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Intelligence, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 3 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A vast online gambling network in Indonesia has been found to be serving as a command-and-control and anonymity infrastructure for malware operators.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> indonesian-gambling-network-doubles-as-malicious-c2-infrastructure</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/indonesian-gambling-network-doubles-as-malicious-c2-infrastructure/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Wireshark Vulnerabilities Create Denial-of-Service Risk for Security Teams</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/wireshark-vulnerabilities-pose-denial-of-service-risk/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/wireshark-vulnerabilities-pose-denial-of-service-risk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Wireshark Vulnerabilities Create Denial-of-Service Risk for Security Teams</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>France's national cybersecurity agency, CERT-FR, has issued a security advisory for two critical vulnerabilities in Wireshark, the world's most popular network protocol analyzer. The flaws, identified as CVE-2025-13945 and CVE-2025-13946, can be exploited by a remote attacker to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition. This poses a significant risk to security operations, as an attacker could crash the tool during a live incident investigation, effectively blinding security analysts. Users are urged to update to the patched versions (4.4.12 and 4.6.2) to mitigate the risk.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Security Operations</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 3 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CERT-FR has issued a warning for two critical denial-of-service vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-13945, CVE-2025-13946) in the Wireshark network protocol analyzer.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> wireshark-vulnerabilities-pose-denial-of-service-risk</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/wireshark-vulnerabilities-pose-denial-of-service-risk/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Washington Post Breached by Clop Ransomware via Oracle Flaws</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/washington-post-confirms-breach-in-massive-oracle-software-attack/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/washington-post-confirms-breach-in-massive-oracle-software-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Washington Post Breached by Clop Ransomware via Oracle Flaws</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Washington Post has officially confirmed it was a victim of a large-scale cyberattack orchestrated by the Clop ransomware group. The threat actors exploited vulnerabilities in Oracle's E-Business Suite, compromising over 100 organizations globally. The campaign involves data exfiltration followed by aggressive extortion tactics, with Clop publicly naming victims on its dark web leak site to pressure them into paying ransoms reportedly as high as $50 million. This incident underscores the significant risk posed by vulnerabilities in widely used enterprise software and the sophisticated, multi-faceted extortion methods employed by modern ransomware gangs.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Clop ransomware, Washington Post breach, Oracle E-Business Suite vulnerability, data extortion, cyberattack, TA505, ransomware campaign</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Clop ransomware group has breached The Washington Post and over 100 other organizations by exploiting vulnerabilities in Oracle's E-Business Suite, leading to massive data theft and extortion.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> washington-post-confirms-breach-in-massive-oracle-software-attack</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 5</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 5 updates recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/washington-post-confirms-breach-in-massive-oracle-software-attack/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: CISA: Commercial Spyware Hijacking Signal &amp; WhatsApp via Zero-Clicks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-commercial-spyware-targets-signal-whatsapp-users/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-commercial-spyware-targets-signal-whatsapp-users/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA: Commercial Spyware Hijacking Signal &amp; WhatsApp via Zero-Clicks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has issued a critical alert regarding active campaigns using commercial spyware to compromise the Signal and WhatsApp accounts of high-value targets. Attackers are employing sophisticated methods including social engineering, malicious QR codes for device linking, and zero-click exploits that require no user interaction. The campaigns are reportedly targeting current and former government officials, military personnel, and civil society organizations across the U.S., Europe, and the Middle East. CISA warns that initial access to messaging apps is often used as a beachhead to deploy further malware and achieve full device compromise.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Mobile Security, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA warns that threat actors are using commercial spyware with sophisticated techniques like zero-click exploits to hijack Signal and WhatsApp accounts of high-value targets, including government officials.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-warns-commercial-spyware-targets-signal-whatsapp-users</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 10:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-commercial-spyware-targets-signal-whatsapp-users/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Global Coalition Targets 'Bulletproof' Hosting Services Fueling Cybercrime</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/global-agencies-launch-effort-against-bulletproof-hosting-providers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/global-agencies-launch-effort-against-bulletproof-hosting-providers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Global Coalition Targets 'Bulletproof' Hosting Services Fueling Cybercrime</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>An international coalition of cybersecurity agencies, including the NSA, CISA, and the FBI, has launched a coordinated effort to combat 'bulletproof' hosting (BPH) providers. These services knowingly lease infrastructure to cybercriminals for activities like ransomware and phishing. A new joint advisory urges Internet Service Providers (ISPs) and network defenders to adopt strategies to identify, block, and report these malicious hosts. The guidance focuses on a nuanced approach, including creating high-confidence blocklists and improving 'know your customer' processes, to disrupt the foundational infrastructure of cybercrime.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Threat Intelligence, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A global coalition of agencies including the NSA, CISA, and FBI have released joint guidance to help ISPs and network defenders identify and dismantle criminal 'bulletproof' hosting (BPH) services.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> global-agencies-launch-effort-against-bulletproof-hosting-providers</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/global-agencies-launch-effort-against-bulletproof-hosting-providers/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>