<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 20:13:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Microsoft Patches Actively Exploited Windows Kernel Zero-Day in November Patch Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-windows-kernel-zero-day-in-november-2025-patch-tuesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-windows-kernel-zero-day-in-november-2025-patch-tuesday/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Microsoft Patches Actively Exploited Windows Kernel Zero-Day in November Patch Tuesday</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Microsoft's November 2025 Patch Tuesday update addresses 63 vulnerabilities, including a critical Windows Kernel privilege escalation zero-day (CVE-2025-62215) that is being actively exploited in the wild. The flaw, which has a CVSS score of 7.0, allows a local attacker to gain SYSTEM-level privileges. The release also includes patches for four other critical vulnerabilities, notably a remote code execution flaw in the Microsoft Graphics Component (GDI+) with a CVSS score of 9.8 (CVE-2025-60724). Other significant fixes address high-severity issues in Windows Kerberos, Microsoft Office, and Visual Studio, requiring immediate attention from administrators to prevent potential system compromise and supply chain attacks.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Patch Management, Vulnerability, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Microsoft's November 2025 Patch Tuesday fixes 63 vulnerabilities, including an actively exploited Windows Kernel zero-day (CVE-2025-62215) and a critical GDI+ RCE flaw (CVE-2025-60724). Learn about the risks and apply patches now.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-windows-kernel-zero-day-in-november-2025-patch-tuesday</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-windows-kernel-zero-day-in-november-2025-patch-tuesday/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Advanced Threat Actor Exploits Cisco and Citrix Zero-Days in Targeted Attacks on Network Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/advanced-threat-actor-exploits-cisco-ise-and-citrix-netscaler-zero-days/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/advanced-threat-actor-exploits-cisco-ise-and-citrix-netscaler-zero-days/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Advanced Threat Actor Exploits Cisco and Citrix Zero-Days in Targeted Attacks on Network Infrastructure</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Amazon's threat intelligence team has discovered an advanced threat actor actively exploiting two previously undisclosed zero-day vulnerabilities in Cisco Identity Service Engine (ISE) and Citrix NetScaler Application Delivery Controllers (ADC). The vulnerabilities, now tracked as CVE-2025-20337 (Cisco) and CVE-2025-5777 (Citrix), are being used to target critical identity and network access control infrastructure. The attackers are leveraging custom malware to gain initial access and establish persistence on these edge devices. Both Cisco and Citrix have been notified and are working on patches, which security teams are urged to apply immediately upon release.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Threat Actor, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> An advanced threat actor is actively exploiting two new zero-day vulnerabilities, CVE-2025-20337 in Cisco ISE and CVE-2025-5777 in Citrix NetScaler, to compromise network access control systems.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> advanced-threat-actor-exploits-cisco-ise-and-citrix-netscaler-zero-days</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/advanced-threat-actor-exploits-cisco-ise-and-citrix-netscaler-zero-days/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: UK Introduces Sweeping Cyber Security and Resilience Bill to Regulate MSPs and Mandate Stricter Breach Reporting</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-introduces-sweeping-cyber-security-and-resilience-bill/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-introduces-sweeping-cyber-security-and-resilience-bill/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> UK Introduces Sweeping Cyber Security and Resilience Bill to Regulate MSPs and Mandate Stricter Breach Reporting</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The UK government has introduced the Cyber Security and Resilience Bill to Parliament, a landmark piece of legislation set to replace the 2018 NIS Regulations. This new bill significantly expands the regulatory landscape by bringing Managed Service Providers (MSPs) into scope for the first time, a move impacting up to 1,100 firms. It also imposes stricter incident reporting rules, requiring an initial report within 24 hours and a full report within 72 hours. The legislation aims to bolster national security by strengthening supply chain resilience and aligning the UK with updated international standards like the EU's NIS2 Directive.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Supply Chain Attack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The UK government has introduced the Cyber Security and Resilience Bill, a new law to replace the NIS Regulations, bringing MSPs into scope and enforcing stricter 24-hour incident reporting rules.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> uk-introduces-sweeping-cyber-security-and-resilience-bill</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-introduces-sweeping-cyber-security-and-resilience-bill/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Asahi Breweries Crippled by Ransomware Attack, Shipments Plummet to 10% Ahead of Peak Holiday Season</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-attack-cripples-asahi-breweries-operations-ahead-of-peak-season/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-attack-cripples-asahi-breweries-operations-ahead-of-peak-season/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Asahi Breweries Crippled by Ransomware Attack, Shipments Plummet to 10% Ahead of Peak Holiday Season</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Japan's largest brewer, Asahi Group Holdings Ltd., is facing severe operational paralysis more than a month after a devastating ransomware attack. The attack disabled the company's core order and shipment management system, forcing a regression to manual processes like phone calls and faxes. As a result, shipments are at only 10% of normal levels, a critical blow as the company enters its busiest sales month. The incident, which has also forced Asahi to postpone its Q3 earnings report, highlights the extreme vulnerability of complex supply chains and legacy IT systems to modern cyber threats.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Cyberattack, Supply Chain Attack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Japan's Asahi Breweries is suffering a massive operational disruption from a ransomware attack, with shipments down 90% and its supply chain paralyzed ahead of the peak holiday season.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ransomware-attack-cripples-asahi-breweries-operations-ahead-of-peak-season</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-attack-cripples-asahi-breweries-operations-ahead-of-peak-season/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Clop Ransomware Gang Claims Attack on Dartmouth College, Threatens to Leak Data</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/clop-ransomware-gang-claims-attack-on-dartmouth-college/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/clop-ransomware-gang-claims-attack-on-dartmouth-college/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Clop Ransomware Gang Claims Attack on Dartmouth College, Threatens to Leak Data</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The notorious Clop ransomware gang has claimed responsibility for a cyberattack against Dartmouth College, an Ivy League university in the U.S. On November 11, 2025, the group added the institution to its dark web leak site, threatening to publish exfiltrated data if the university does not enter negotiations. This incident highlights the increasing trend of ransomware attacks targeting the education sector, which holds vast amounts of sensitive personal data. Dartmouth College has not yet issued a public statement on the alleged breach, but the threat from Clop is considered highly credible due to the group's track record.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The notorious Clop ransomware gang has listed Dartmouth College as its latest victim, threatening to publish stolen data in a double-extortion attack targeting the education sector.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> clop-ransomware-gang-claims-attack-on-dartmouth-college</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/clop-ransomware-gang-claims-attack-on-dartmouth-college/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Massive Phishing Campaign Abuses Facebook's Own Email Domain to Bypass Security Filters</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/facebook-business-suite-abused-in-large-scale-phishing-campaign/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/facebook-business-suite-abused-in-large-scale-phishing-campaign/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Massive Phishing Campaign Abuses Facebook's Own Email Domain to Bypass Security Filters</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Security researchers at Check Point have uncovered a large-scale phishing campaign that cleverly abuses Meta's own infrastructure to deliver highly convincing malicious emails. By using the legitimate 'Business invitation feature' in Facebook Business Suite, attackers are sending phishing emails from the authentic `facebookmail.com` domain, allowing them to bypass standard email security filters. The campaign has already targeted over 5,000 businesses, primarily SMBs, with over 40,000 emails. The attack aims to trick employees who are accustomed to receiving genuine Meta notifications into giving up their credentials or other sensitive information.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Phishing, Cyberattack, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A massive phishing campaign is abusing Facebook's legitimate email domain and Business Suite to send convincing malicious notifications to thousands of businesses, bypassing traditional security.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> facebook-business-suite-abused-in-large-scale-phishing-campaign</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/facebook-business-suite-abused-in-large-scale-phishing-campaign/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: ICS Patch Tuesday: Siemens, Schneider Electric Address Critical Flaws in Industrial Control Systems</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ics-patch-tuesday-siemens-schneider-electric-address-critical-flaws-november-2025/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ics-patch-tuesday-siemens-schneider-electric-address-critical-flaws-november-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> ICS Patch Tuesday: Siemens, Schneider Electric Address Critical Flaws in Industrial Control Systems</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The November 2025 Industrial Control Systems (ICS) Patch Tuesday includes a series of important security advisories from major operational technology (OT) vendors, including Siemens, Schneider Electric, Aveva, and Rockwell Automation. The patches address numerous vulnerabilities in products used across critical infrastructure sectors like manufacturing and energy. Notably, a critical flaw in Aveva software also affects Schneider Electric products, highlighting supply chain complexities in the OT space. The coordinated disclosure aims to improve security posture and mitigate risks of remote code execution and denial-of-service attacks in sensitive industrial environments.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Industrial Control Systems, Patch Management, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The November 2025 ICS Patch Tuesday features critical security updates from Siemens, Schneider Electric, and others to address vulnerabilities in industrial control systems.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ics-patch-tuesday-siemens-schneider-electric-address-critical-flaws-november-2025</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ics-patch-tuesday-siemens-schneider-electric-address-critical-flaws-november-2025/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Google Sues Operators of 'Lighthouse' Phishing-as-a-Service Platform Used in Massive Smishing Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-sues-operators-of-lighthouse-phishing-as-a-service-platform/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-sues-operators-of-lighthouse-phishing-as-a-service-platform/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Google Sues Operators of 'Lighthouse' Phishing-as-a-Service Platform Used in Massive Smishing Campaigns</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Google has filed a civil lawsuit in New York against the alleged China-based operators of 'Lighthouse,' a large-scale Phishing-as-a-Service (PhaaS) platform. The platform enabled cybercriminals to launch SMS phishing (smishing) campaigns that have targeted over one million users in 120 countries. The service provided toolkits for impersonating trusted brands like E-ZPass and the USPS to harvest financial information. The threat group, dubbed 'Smishing Triad,' used over 194,000 malicious domains. Google's legal action aims to dismantle the platform's infrastructure, marking another instance of a major tech company using lawsuits to combat cybercrime.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Phishing, Threat Actor, Policy and Compliance</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Google has filed a lawsuit against the operators of the 'Lighthouse' Phishing-as-a-Service (PhaaS) platform, a criminal enterprise enabling smishing attacks at a global scale.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> google-sues-operators-of-lighthouse-phishing-as-a-service-platform</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-sues-operators-of-lighthouse-phishing-as-a-service-platform/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Iranian APT 'Ferocious Kitten' Continues to Target Dissidents With Custom MarkiRAT Surveillance Malware</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/iranian-apt-ferocious-kitten-targets-dissidents-with-markirat-malware/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/iranian-apt-ferocious-kitten-targets-dissidents-with-markirat-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Iranian APT 'Ferocious Kitten' Continues to Target Dissidents With Custom MarkiRAT Surveillance Malware</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Iranian-aligned APT group 'Ferocious Kitten' continues its long-running cyber-espionage campaign against Iranian dissidents and activists, according to new research from Picus Security. Active since at least 2015, the group uses spear-phishing emails with malicious Office documents to deploy its custom remote access trojan (RAT), MarkiRAT. This malware is a sophisticated surveillance tool, featuring an advanced keylogger that activates only when password managers are not in use, clipboard hijacking, and data exfiltration over HTTP/S. The group also employs various defense evasion techniques, including the use of BITS and the RTLO trick to disguise malicious files.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Malware, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Iranian APT group Ferocious Kitten is using a custom RAT called MarkiRAT in an ongoing cyber-espionage campaign targeting dissidents, employing advanced surveillance and evasion tactics.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> iranian-apt-ferocious-kitten-targets-dissidents-with-markirat-malware</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/iranian-apt-ferocious-kitten-targets-dissidents-with-markirat-malware/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: NYDFS Part 500 Final Rules on MFA and Asset Inventory Now in Effect for Financial Firms</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/nydfs-part-500-cybersecurity-rules-on-mfa-and-asset-inventory-take-effect/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/nydfs-part-500-cybersecurity-rules-on-mfa-and-asset-inventory-take-effect/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> NYDFS Part 500 Final Rules on MFA and Asset Inventory Now in Effect for Financial Firms</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>As of November 1, 2025, the final provisions of the amended New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) Part 500 cybersecurity regulation are now in force. Financial entities regulated by NYDFS must now comply with stricter requirements for implementing multi-factor authentication (MFA) across their information systems and maintaining a comprehensive, detailed asset inventory. These rules, part of a major update from 2023, conclude a two-year transition period. Firms must certify their compliance for the first time in their annual reports due by April 15, 2026, and are also guided to enforce similar MFA standards on their third-party vendors.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Regulatory, Policy and Compliance, Security Operations</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The final provisions of the NYDFS Part 500 cybersecurity regulation are now in effect, mandating multi-factor authentication (MFA) and comprehensive asset inventory for all regulated financial firms.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> nydfs-part-500-cybersecurity-rules-on-mfa-and-asset-inventory-take-effect</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/nydfs-part-500-cybersecurity-rules-on-mfa-and-asset-inventory-take-effect/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Critical Triofox Zero-Day Actively Exploited for System-Level Access</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/triofox-zero-day-exploited-by-unc6485-for-system-level-access/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/triofox-zero-day-exploited-by-unc6485-for-system-level-access/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Critical Triofox Zero-Day Actively Exploited for System-Level Access</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A critical, unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability (CVE-2025-12480) in Gladinet's Triofox file-sharing platform is being actively exploited by a threat group tracked as UNC6485. The attackers are bypassing authentication by spoofing HTTP Host headers to 'localhost', allowing them to create rogue administrator accounts. They then abuse a built-in antivirus feature to execute malicious code with SYSTEM-level privileges, leading to full system compromise. Post-exploitation activity includes the deployment of commercial remote access tools like Zoho UEMS and AnyDesk to maintain persistence. Gladinet has released a patch, and organizations are urged to update immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Cyberattack, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A critical zero-day (CVE-2025-12480) in Gladinet Triofox is being actively exploited by the UNC6485 threat group to achieve remote code execution and full system compromise. Learn how to detect and mitigate this threat.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> triofox-zero-day-exploited-by-unc6485-for-system-level-access</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/triofox-zero-day-exploited-by-unc6485-for-system-level-access/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: KONNI APT Weaponizes Google's Find Hub for Destructive Attacks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/konni-apt-abuses-google-find-hub-for-remote-data-wipes/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/konni-apt-abuses-google-find-hub-for-remote-data-wipes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> KONNI APT Weaponizes Google's Find Hub for Destructive Attacks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The North Korea-linked threat group KONNI has been observed in a novel campaign targeting individuals in South Korea. The attackers use social engineering to deploy PC malware that steals Google account credentials. With these credentials, they access the victim's Google account and abuse the legitimate 'Find Hub' service (formerly Find My Device) to track the real-time location of the victim's Android phone and remotely trigger a factory reset, wiping all data. This campaign highlights the group's creativity in weaponizing legitimate services for destructive purposes.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Cyberattack, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The North Korean threat actor KONNI is exploiting Google's Find Hub service to remotely track and wipe data from Android devices after stealing credentials via a sophisticated PC malware campaign targeting users in South Korea.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> konni-apt-abuses-google-find-hub-for-remote-data-wipes</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/konni-apt-abuses-google-find-hub-for-remote-data-wipes/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: 'Fantasy Hub' Android MaaS Sells Full-Service Spyware on Telegram</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fantasy-hub-android-malware-as-a-service-emerges-on-telegram/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fantasy-hub-android-malware-as-a-service-emerges-on-telegram/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> 'Fantasy Hub' Android MaaS Sells Full-Service Spyware on Telegram</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new Android Remote Access Trojan (RAT) named 'Fantasy Hub' is being sold as a Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) on Russian-speaking Telegram channels. For a subscription fee starting at $200/week, the service provides novice attackers with a full suite of tools for device espionage, including live audio/video streaming, data theft, and credential harvesting from major Russian financial apps using overlay attacks. The service even includes tools for creating fake Google Play Store pages to distribute the malware, significantly lowering the barrier to entry for mobile-focused cybercrime.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Mobile Security, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new Android RAT called 'Fantasy Hub' is being sold as a Malware-as-a-Service on Telegram, offering tools for device espionage, data theft, and financial credential harvesting from Russian banking apps.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> fantasy-hub-android-malware-as-a-service-emerges-on-telegram</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fantasy-hub-android-malware-as-a-service-emerges-on-telegram/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Pentagon Overhauls Cyber Force Model to Boost USCYBERCOM Readiness</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pentagon-unveils-new-cyber-force-generation-model/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pentagon-unveils-new-cyber-force-generation-model/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Pentagon Overhauls Cyber Force Model to Boost USCYBERCOM Readiness</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Department of War (DoW) has announced a new cyber force generation model aimed at enhancing the operational effectiveness, specialization, and lethality of forces assigned to U.S. Cyber Command (USCYBERCOM). The revised plan is designed to create a more integrated and agile cyber force by streamlining the processes of recruiting, training, and retaining personnel across all military branches. This strategic shift seeks to address emerging cyber threats and deter aggression in the cyber domain more effectively.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Security Operations</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 3 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The U.S. Department of War has unveiled a new cyber force generation model to enhance the recruiting, training, and operational effectiveness of forces assigned to U.S. Cyber Command (USCYBERCOM).</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> pentagon-unveils-new-cyber-force-generation-model</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pentagon-unveils-new-cyber-force-generation-model/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CMMC Enforcement Officially Begins, Mandating Compliance for DoD Contractors</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/dod-cmmc-program-enforcement-officially-begins-for-defense-contractors/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/dod-cmmc-program-enforcement-officially-begins-for-defense-contractors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CMMC Enforcement Officially Begins, Mandating Compliance for DoD Contractors</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Department of Defense's (DoD) Cybersecurity Maturity Model Certification (CMMC) program officially entered its enforcement phase on November 10, 2025. Defense industrial base (DIB) contractors are now required to meet specific, verifiable cybersecurity standards to be eligible for new contracts. The program, which will be rolled out in phases over three years, aims to protect Federal Contract Information (FCI) and Controlled Unclassified Information (CUI) across the defense supply chain. Companies that fail to achieve the required certification level risk being excluded from future DoD contracts.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Supply Chain Attack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The DoD's Cybersecurity Maturity Model Certification (CMMC) program has officially entered its enforcement phase, requiring defense contractors to verify specific cybersecurity standards to be eligible for new contracts.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> dod-cmmc-program-enforcement-officially-begins-for-defense-contractors</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/dod-cmmc-program-enforcement-officially-begins-for-defense-contractors/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA Adds Actively Exploited Samsung Zero-Day to KEV Catalog</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-actively-exploited-samsung-mobile-zero-day-to-kev-catalog/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-actively-exploited-samsung-mobile-zero-day-to-kev-catalog/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Adds Actively Exploited Samsung Zero-Day to KEV Catalog</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a critical vulnerability in Samsung mobile devices, CVE-2025-21042, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog. The flaw, an out-of-bounds write issue in the image processing library, is being actively exploited in zero-click attacks to deploy spyware named 'LANDFALL' on Samsung Galaxy devices. The attack requires no user interaction, allowing for remote code execution and full device compromise. Federal agencies are mandated to patch the vulnerability, and all organizations are strongly urged to apply updates immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Mobile Security, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA has added CVE-2025-21042, a critical zero-day vulnerability in Samsung mobile devices actively exploited to deploy spyware in zero-click attacks, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-adds-actively-exploited-samsung-mobile-zero-day-to-kev-catalog</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-actively-exploited-samsung-mobile-zero-day-to-kev-catalog/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Nikkei Slack Breach Exposes Data of 17,000 Users via Stolen Credentials</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/nikkei-discloses-slack-breach-exposing-data-of-17000-users/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/nikkei-discloses-slack-breach-exposing-data-of-17000-users/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Nikkei Slack Breach Exposes Data of 17,000 Users via Stolen Credentials</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Japanese media giant Nikkei Inc., owner of the Financial Times, has disclosed a significant data breach affecting its internal Slack workspace. An attacker gained access using authentication credentials stolen from an employee's personal computer, which was infected with infostealer malware. The incident, which was detected in September 2025, exposed the names, email addresses, and chat histories of 17,368 employees and business partners. The breach highlights the persistent threat of infostealer malware and the security risks associated with credentials stored in web browsers.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Cyberattack, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Nikkei Inc. has disclosed a data breach of its internal Slack workspace, exposing the data of 17,368 users after an attacker gained access using credentials stolen by infostealer malware from an employee's computer.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> nikkei-discloses-slack-breach-exposing-data-of-17000-users</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/nikkei-discloses-slack-breach-exposing-data-of-17000-users/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Hyundai IT Affiliate Discloses Major Data Breach Exposing PII and SSNs</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/hyundai-autoever-notifies-customers-of-major-data-breach/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/hyundai-autoever-notifies-customers-of-major-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Hyundai IT Affiliate Discloses Major Data Breach Exposing PII and SSNs</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Hyundai AutoEver America, the IT services subsidiary of the Hyundai Group, has begun notifying customers of a major data breach that occurred between late February and early March 2025. The incident involved unauthorized access to the company's IT environment, exposing highly sensitive personally identifiable information (PII), including full names, driver's license numbers, and Social Security numbers. While the exact number of victims is unconfirmed, the company's software is used in up to 2.7 million vehicles in North America, indicating a potentially massive scale.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Cyberattack, Other</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Hyundai AutoEver America is notifying customers of a major data breach that exposed sensitive personally identifiable information (PII), including Social Security numbers and driver's license numbers, for potentially millions of customers.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> hyundai-autoever-notifies-customers-of-major-data-breach</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/hyundai-autoever-notifies-customers-of-major-data-breach/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Other</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New DoS Attack Variant Targets Unpatched Cisco Firewalls</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisco-warns-of-new-dos-attack-variant-targeting-firewalls/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisco-warns-of-new-dos-attack-variant-targeting-firewalls/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New DoS Attack Variant Targets Unpatched Cisco Firewalls</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Cisco has updated its security advisory to warn of a new attack variant actively exploiting two previously disclosed vulnerabilities, CVE-2025-20333 and CVE-2025-20362, in its Secure Firewall ASA and FTD software. The new variant causes unpatched devices to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition. These flaws were originally exploited as zero-days in the 'ArcaneDoor' campaign attributed to a state-sponsored actor. Despite patches being available since September, many devices remain vulnerable, and all customers are urged to apply updates immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Cyberattack, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Cisco is warning of a new denial-of-service (DoS) attack variant that actively exploits vulnerabilities CVE-2025-20333 and CVE-2025-20362 in its ASA and FTD firewall software, causing devices to reboot.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisco-warns-of-new-dos-attack-variant-targeting-firewalls</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisco-warns-of-new-dos-attack-variant-targeting-firewalls/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Cisco Firewalls Under Renewed Assault as New DoS Attack Variant Emerges</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisco-warns-new-attack-variant-exploiting-critical-firewall-vulnerabilities/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisco-warns-new-attack-variant-exploiting-critical-firewall-vulnerabilities/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Cisco Firewalls Under Renewed Assault as New DoS Attack Variant Emerges</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Cisco has issued an urgent security warning about a new denial-of-service (DoS) attack variant that is actively exploiting two previously patched vulnerabilities, CVE-2025-20333 and CVE-2025-20362, in its Secure Firewall ASA and FTD software. The campaign, which began on November 5, 2025, causes unpatched devices to enter a continuous reload loop, rendering them inoperable. This follows months of active exploitation by advanced threat actors, including a compromise of at least one US government agency. Cisco strongly urges all customers to apply the available patches immediately, as no effective workarounds exist.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Cyberattack, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Cisco warns of a new denial-of-service (DoS) attack variant actively exploiting vulnerabilities CVE-2025-20333 and CVE-2025-20362 in ASA and FTD firewalls. Learn how to patch and protect your network.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisco-warns-new-attack-variant-exploiting-critical-firewall-vulnerabilities</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 12:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisco-warns-new-attack-variant-exploiting-critical-firewall-vulnerabilities/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>