<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 14:42:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CodeRED Emergency Alert System Crippled by 'Inc Ransom' Attack, Disrupting US Public Safety</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-emergency-alert-system-codered-crippled-by-inc-ransom-attack/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-emergency-alert-system-codered-crippled-by-inc-ransom-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CodeRED Emergency Alert System Crippled by 'Inc Ransom' Attack, Disrupting US Public Safety</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The OnSolve CodeRED emergency alert system, a critical communication tool for hundreds of U.S. municipalities, has been taken offline following a ransomware attack claimed by the 'Inc Ransom' group. The attack, which began on November 1, 2025, resulted in the encryption of systems and the exfiltration of user data, including names, addresses, and contact information. After failed ransom negotiations, the vendor was forced to decommission the legacy platform, causing significant service disruptions for local governments in numerous states and leaving them unable to issue vital public safety notifications.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Cyberattack, Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> CodeRED ransomware attack, Inc Ransom, OnSolve data breach, emergency alert system hack, US public safety cyberattack, Crisis24, ransomware negotiation, critical infrastructure security</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A ransomware attack by the 'Inc Ransom' group has disabled the OnSolve CodeRED emergency alert system, impacting public safety notifications across the United States and resulting in a user data breach.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> us-emergency-alert-system-codered-crippled-by-inc-ransom-attack</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-emergency-alert-system-codered-crippled-by-inc-ransom-attack/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Major Wall Street Banks Exposed in SitusAMC Supply Chain Data Breach</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/situsamc-supply-chain-breach-exposes-major-us-banks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/situsamc-supply-chain-breach-exposes-major-us-banks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Major Wall Street Banks Exposed in SitusAMC Supply Chain Data Breach</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>SitusAMC, a key technology vendor for the real-estate finance industry, has suffered a significant data breach, exposing sensitive data belonging to some of America's largest banks. The attack, which occurred on November 12, 2025, compromised corporate data such as accounting records and legal agreements. Breach notifications have reportedly been sent to major financial institutions including JPMorgan Chase, Citi, and Morgan Stanley. The incident was a data theft attack, with no ransomware deployed, highlighting the severe supply-chain risks facing the financial sector. An investigation is underway to determine the full extent of the breach, which may also include customer data from the affected banks.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Supply Chain Attack, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> SitusAMC data breach, supply chain attack finance, JPMorgan Chase breach, Citi data breach, Morgan Stanley security, Wall Street cyber attack, financial services breach, third-party risk</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Financial technology vendor SitusAMC suffered a major data breach, impacting top Wall Street banks like JPMorgan Chase, Citi, and Morgan Stanley through a supply chain attack.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> situsamc-supply-chain-breach-exposes-major-us-banks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/situsamc-supply-chain-breach-exposes-major-us-banks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA Warns: Spyware Actively Hijacking Signal and WhatsApp Accounts of High-Value Targets</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-spyware-targeting-signal-and-whatsapp-users/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-spyware-targeting-signal-and-whatsapp-users/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Warns: Spyware Actively Hijacking Signal and WhatsApp Accounts of High-Value Targets</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has issued an alert about active campaigns targeting high-value individuals through the Signal and WhatsApp messaging apps. Threat actors, including state-aligned groups, are using commercial spyware and Remote Access Trojans (RATs) to gain full access to victims' devices and communications. Attack vectors include sophisticated phishing, malicious QR codes for device linking, spoofed application downloads, and even zero-click exploits. The targets primarily consist of government officials, military personnel, and civil society organizations in the U.S., Europe, and the Middle East, prompting CISA to urge heightened mobile security awareness.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Threat Intelligence, Mobile Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> CISA spyware warning, Signal security, WhatsApp hack, zero-click exploit, mobile spyware, LANDFALL malware, high-value targets, encrypted messaging</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA warns that threat actors are actively using spyware, RATs, and zero-click exploits to compromise the Signal and WhatsApp accounts of government officials and other high-value targets.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-warns-of-spyware-targeting-signal-and-whatsapp-users</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-spyware-targeting-signal-and-whatsapp-users/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Geopolitical Shift: Russian and North Korean State Hackers Found Sharing Attack Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/unprecedented-collaboration-found-between-russian-gamaredon-and-north-korean-lazarus-apts/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/unprecedented-collaboration-found-between-russian-gamaredon-and-north-korean-lazarus-apts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Geopolitical Shift: Russian and North Korean State Hackers Found Sharing Attack Infrastructure</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>In a rare and alarming discovery, security researchers have found evidence of operational collaboration between two of the world's most prolific state-sponsored hacking groups: Russia's Gamaredon (Pitty Tiger) and North Korea's Lazarus. The evidence centers on a shared command-and-control (C2) server IP address that was used by both groups within days of each other to deliver their respective malware payloads. This convergence of TTPs and infrastructure signals a potential new phase of cyber operations where geopolitical alliances between Moscow and Pyongyang are extending into direct, cooperative attacks, potentially amplifying the threat level for defenders globally.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Threat Intelligence, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Gamaredon Lazarus collaboration, Russian North Korean hackers, APT collaboration, shared C2 infrastructure, InvisibleFerret malware, Pitty Tiger, state-sponsored hacking, geopolitical cyber threats</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Security researchers have uncovered a rare collaboration between Russian state-sponsored hackers Gamaredon and North Korea's Lazarus group, who were observed using shared command-and-control infrastructure.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> unprecedented-collaboration-found-between-russian-gamaredon-and-north-korean-lazarus-apts</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/unprecedented-collaboration-found-between-russian-gamaredon-and-north-korean-lazarus-apts/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Water Gamayun APT Exploits Novel 'MSC EvilTwin' Windows Flaw in Stealthy Attacks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/water-gamayun-apt-exploits-windows-msc-eviltwin-vulnerability/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/water-gamayun-apt-exploits-windows-msc-eviltwin-vulnerability/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Water Gamayun APT Exploits Novel 'MSC EvilTwin' Windows Flaw in Stealthy Attacks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Russia-aligned APT group Water Gamayun is actively exploiting a novel vulnerability in the Windows Microsoft Management Console (MMC), tracked as CVE-2025-26633. The attack, analyzed by Zscaler and dubbed 'MSC EvilTwin,' uses a malicious .msc file to proxy code execution through the trusted mmc.exe binary, making it difficult to detect. The multi-stage campaign begins with a malicious download and uses embedded commands to execute hidden PowerShell payloads. This technique allows the attackers to install backdoors and information stealers while evading traditional security measures, showcasing the group's continued sophistication in developing stealthy intrusion methods.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Vulnerability, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Water Gamayun, CVE-2025-26633, MSC EvilTwin, mmc.exe exploit, signed binary proxy execution, PowerShell attack, Zscaler threat hunting, Russia APT</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Russia-aligned APT group Water Gamayun is exploiting a new Windows Microsoft Management Console vulnerability, CVE-2025-26633, to deliver stealthy PowerShell payloads.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> water-gamayun-apt-exploits-windows-msc-eviltwin-vulnerability</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/water-gamayun-apt-exploits-windows-msc-eviltwin-vulnerability/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Shai-Hulud 2.0: Destructive NPM Worm Compromises 25K+ GitHub Repos, Wipes Dev Systems</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/shai-hulud-2-npm-attack-intensifies-with-destructive-capabilities/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/shai-hulud-2-npm-attack-intensifies-with-destructive-capabilities/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Shai-Hulud 2.0: Destructive NPM Worm Compromises 25K+ GitHub Repos, Wipes Dev Systems</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A second, more aggressive wave of the 'Shai-Hulud' supply chain attack is devastating the npm ecosystem. Dubbed 'Shai-Hulud 2.0,' this variant has already compromised hundreds of npm packages, including those from major organizations like Zapier and Postman, and led to the creation of over 25,000 malicious GitHub repositories containing stolen developer secrets. The new version executes during the 'preinstall' phase, bypassing some scanners, and introduces a dangerous destructive capability: if it fails to exfiltrate stolen credentials, it attempts to wipe the user's entire home directory, escalating the threat from espionage to outright sabotage.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Malware, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Shai-Hulud 2.0, npm supply chain attack, GitHub secrets leak, preinstall script exploit, destructive malware, Zapier compromised, Postman compromised, Wiz research</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new, more aggressive 'Shai-Hulud 2.0' npm supply chain attack is compromising thousands of GitHub repositories and includes a destructive payload to wipe developer systems.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> shai-hulud-2-npm-attack-intensifies-with-destructive-capabilities</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/shai-hulud-2-npm-attack-intensifies-with-destructive-capabilities/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA Warns of Critical Flaws in Industrial Control Systems, Including CVSS 10.0 Bug</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-issues-seven-advisories-for-critical-ics-vulnerabilities/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-issues-seven-advisories-for-critical-ics-vulnerabilities/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Warns of Critical Flaws in Industrial Control Systems, Including CVSS 10.0 Bug</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>On November 25, 2025, CISA issued seven new advisories for vulnerabilities in Industrial Control Systems (ICS) from multiple vendors, including Rockwell Automation, Opto 22, and Zenitel. The flaws affect equipment used globally in critical manufacturing and communications sectors. The most severe vulnerability, CVE-2025-64130, is a critical OS command injection flaw in Zenitel communications equipment with a CVSS score of 10.0, which could allow for remote code execution. Other advisories cover flaws leading to denial-of-service and information exposure, prompting CISA to urge immediate review and mitigation by asset owners.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Industrial Control Systems, Vulnerability, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> CISA ICS advisories, CVE-2025-64130, Zenitel vulnerability, Rockwell Automation security, Opto 22 groov View, industrial control systems, OT security, critical manufacturing</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA has issued seven new advisories for critical vulnerabilities in industrial control systems (ICS), including a CVSS 10.0 flaw (CVE-2025-64130) in Zenitel products.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-issues-seven-advisories-for-critical-ics-vulnerabilities</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-issues-seven-advisories-for-critical-ics-vulnerabilities/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: US Cyber Strategy Shifts to APTs as CISA Faces 17% Budget Cut, Staffing Crisis</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-cyber-policy-shifts-amid-cisa-budget-cuts-and-staffing-concerns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-cyber-policy-shifts-amid-cisa-budget-cuts-and-staffing-concerns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> US Cyber Strategy Shifts to APTs as CISA Faces 17% Budget Cut, Staffing Crisis</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. federal cybersecurity strategy is undergoing a major recalibration, shifting its focus toward high-end threats from state actors and APTs. However, this strategic pivot is overshadowed by a draft 2026 budget that proposes a severe 17% cut for CISA, amounting to nearly $495 million and the elimination of over 1,000 positions. This reduction threatens to weaken state and local cyber capacity and vital programs like MS-ISAC. The news comes as CISA already struggles with a reported 40% vacancy rate in key mission areas, raising concerns about the nation's ability to defend against both sophisticated intrusions and common cyber threats like ransomware.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Security Operations</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> CISA budget cut, US cybersecurity policy, federal cybersecurity, CISA staffing crisis, MS-ISAC funding, Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act, national cyber defense, SLTT cybersecurity</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A shift in U.S. cyber policy to focus on state actors is clashing with a proposed 17% budget cut for CISA, threatening the agency's ability to support state and local cyber defenses.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> us-cyber-policy-shifts-amid-cisa-budget-cuts-and-staffing-concerns</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-cyber-policy-shifts-amid-cisa-budget-cuts-and-staffing-concerns/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New 'ShinySp1d3r' RaaS Emerges from Alliance of ShinyHunters and Scattered Spider</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/shinysp1d3r-raas-emerges-from-shinyhunters-and-scattered-spider-alliance/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/shinysp1d3r-raas-emerges-from-shinyhunters-and-scattered-spider-alliance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New 'ShinySp1d3r' RaaS Emerges from Alliance of ShinyHunters and Scattered Spider</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) operation named 'ShinySp1d3r' is being developed by 'SLSH,' a new cybercrime collective formed by members of the infamous ShinyHunters, Scattered Spider, and Lapsus$ groups. An early Windows build of the ransomware has been analyzed, revealing capabilities like ChaCha20 encryption, service termination, and shadow copy deletion. The group also plans to create Linux and ESXi versions, signaling an intent to target high-value enterprise environments. This development marks a significant shift, as these historically distinct extortion groups are now pooling their resources to create their own ransomware weapon.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> ShinySp1d3r ransomware, Ransomware-as-a-Service, ShinyHunters, Scattered Spider, Lapsus$, SLSH threat actor, ESXi ransomware, cybercrime collective</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) called ShinySp1d3r is being developed by a collective of notorious threat actors from ShinyHunters, Scattered Spider, and Lapsus$.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> shinysp1d3r-raas-emerges-from-shinyhunters-and-scattered-spider-alliance</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/shinysp1d3r-raas-emerges-from-shinyhunters-and-scattered-spider-alliance/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: NVIDIA AI Toolkit and WordPress Plugins Hit with High-Severity Flaws</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/nvidia-and-wordpress-plugins-hit-with-ssrf-and-xss-vulnerabilities/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/nvidia-and-wordpress-plugins-hit-with-ssrf-and-xss-vulnerabilities/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> NVIDIA AI Toolkit and WordPress Plugins Hit with High-Severity Flaws</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>On November 25, 2025, several new software vulnerabilities were disclosed, including a high-severity Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) flaw in NVIDIA's NeMo Agent Toolkit (CVE-2025-33203) used for AI development. This flaw could lead to information disclosure and denial of service. Concurrently, vulnerabilities were found in popular WordPress plugins. The 'Just Highlight' plugin is affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) bug (CVE-2025-13311), while the 'Locker Content' plugin has a sensitive information exposure flaw (CVE-2025-12525) that could allow unauthenticated attackers to bypass content restrictions.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> NVIDIA vulnerability, CVE-2025-33203, NeMo Agent Toolkit, WordPress plugin vulnerability, CVE-2025-13311, CVE-2025-12525, SSRF exploit, Stored XSS</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> New vulnerabilities disclosed in NVIDIA's NeMo Agent Toolkit (CVE-2025-33203) and several WordPress plugins, exposing users to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) and Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> nvidia-and-wordpress-plugins-hit-with-ssrf-and-xss-vulnerabilities</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/nvidia-and-wordpress-plugins-hit-with-ssrf-and-xss-vulnerabilities/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Homeland Security Warns Gov't Shutdown and Lapsed Law Cripple U.S. Cyber Defenses</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-homeland-security-warns-of-rising-cyber-threats-amid-shutdown/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-homeland-security-warns-of-rising-cyber-threats-amid-shutdown/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Homeland Security Warns Gov't Shutdown and Lapsed Law Cripple U.S. Cyber Defenses</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. House Committee on Homeland Security has issued a stark warning in its latest 'Cyber Threat Snapshot,' stating that the nation's ability to defend against cyber threats is being severely hampered. The report cites a dual crisis: a federal government shutdown that furloughs key cybersecurity personnel, and the lapse of the Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act of 2015. This creates 'dangerous blind spots' at a time of heightened threat activity from nation-state actors like China and Iran, and a surge in attacks against U.S. critical infrastructure.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The U.S. House Committee on Homeland Security's 'Cyber Threat Snapshot' warns that a federal shutdown and lapsed information-sharing laws are weakening the nation's cyber defenses.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> us-homeland-security-warns-of-rising-cyber-threats-amid-shutdown</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-homeland-security-warns-of-rising-cyber-threats-amid-shutdown/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Sha1-Hulud: Destructive Supply Chain Attack Hits 25,000+ Repos via npm</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sha1-hulud-supply-chain-attack-compromises-25000-github-repos-via-npm/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sha1-hulud-supply-chain-attack-compromises-25000-github-repos-via-npm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Sha1-Hulud: Destructive Supply Chain Attack Hits 25,000+ Repos via npm</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A sophisticated and self-propagating software supply chain attack, dubbed 'Sha1-Hulud,' has compromised over 25,000 GitHub repositories since November 21, 2025. The attack leverages hundreds of malicious npm packages that execute code during the `preinstall` phase to steal developer credentials, GitHub tokens, and cloud secrets. The malware exfiltrates stolen data to public GitHub repositories and includes a destructive 'scorched earth' component that wipes the victim's home directory if data theft fails, turning it into a denial-of-service attack. The campaign has impacted packages from major organizations like Zapier, Postman, and ENS Domains, highlighting a severe threat to the open-source ecosystem.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Malware, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A massive software supply chain attack dubbed 'Sha1-Hulud' has compromised over 25,000 GitHub repositories by using malicious npm packages to steal developer credentials and secrets during the preinstall phase.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> sha1-hulud-supply-chain-attack-compromises-25000-github-repos-via-npm</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sha1-hulud-supply-chain-attack-compromises-25000-github-repos-via-npm/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA: Commercial Spyware Hijacking Signal &amp; WhatsApp via Zero-Clicks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-commercial-spyware-targets-signal-whatsapp-users/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-commercial-spyware-targets-signal-whatsapp-users/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA: Commercial Spyware Hijacking Signal &amp; WhatsApp via Zero-Clicks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has issued a critical alert regarding active campaigns using commercial spyware to compromise the Signal and WhatsApp accounts of high-value targets. Attackers are employing sophisticated methods including social engineering, malicious QR codes for device linking, and zero-click exploits that require no user interaction. The campaigns are reportedly targeting current and former government officials, military personnel, and civil society organizations across the U.S., Europe, and the Middle East. CISA warns that initial access to messaging apps is often used as a beachhead to deploy further malware and achieve full device compromise.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Mobile Security, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA warns that threat actors are using commercial spyware with sophisticated techniques like zero-click exploits to hijack Signal and WhatsApp accounts of high-value targets, including government officials.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-warns-commercial-spyware-targets-signal-whatsapp-users</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-commercial-spyware-targets-signal-whatsapp-users/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Patch Now: Critical 9.8 RCE Flaw in Oracle Identity Manager Under Active Attack</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-orders-patch-for-critical-oracle-identity-manager-rce-flaw-cve-2025-61757/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-orders-patch-for-critical-oracle-identity-manager-rce-flaw-cve-2025-61757/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Patch Now: Critical 9.8 RCE Flaw in Oracle Identity Manager Under Active Attack</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability, CVE-2025-61757, in Oracle Identity Manager is being actively exploited by threat actors. The flaw, which has a CVSS score of 9.8, allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain complete control over vulnerable systems via a specially crafted HTTP request. The vulnerability stems from a missing authentication check in the product's REST WebServices component. Due to evidence of in-the-wild exploitation, CISA has added the bug to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog and mandated that all U.S. federal agencies apply the patch by December 12, 2025.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA has added a critical, actively exploited RCE vulnerability (CVE-2025-61757) in Oracle Identity Manager to its KEV catalog, ordering federal agencies to patch the 9.8 CVSS flaw by December 12, 2025.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-orders-patch-for-critical-oracle-identity-manager-rce-flaw-cve-2025-61757</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-orders-patch-for-critical-oracle-identity-manager-rce-flaw-cve-2025-61757/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Akira Ransomware Targets M&amp;A Blind Spots, Breaching Firms via Inherited SonicWall Devices</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/akira-ransomware-exploits-unpatched-sonicwall-devices-during-ma/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/akira-ransomware-exploits-unpatched-sonicwall-devices-during-ma/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Akira Ransomware Targets M&amp;A Blind Spots, Breaching Firms via Inherited SonicWall Devices</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Akira ransomware group is exploiting security blind spots created during corporate mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;A). According to research by ReliaQuest, Akira affiliates are gaining initial access to acquiring companies by compromising vulnerable SonicWall SSL VPN appliances inherited from smaller, acquired firms. Attackers leverage the fact that the acquiring organizations are often unaware of these unpatched, legacy devices on their new network. Once inside, they use zombie credentials and move laterally, with the time from lateral movement to ransomware deployment averaging less than one hour, highlighting a rapid and effective attack chain.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Akira ransomware group is exploiting security gaps during corporate mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;A) by compromising vulnerable SonicWall VPNs inherited from acquired firms to breach the parent company.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> akira-ransomware-exploits-unpatched-sonicwall-devices-during-ma</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/akira-ransomware-exploits-unpatched-sonicwall-devices-during-ma/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Google Patches Actively Exploited Chrome Zero-Day in V8 Engine</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-v8-zero-day-cve-2025-13223/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-v8-zero-day-cve-2025-13223/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Google Patches Actively Exploited Chrome Zero-Day in V8 Engine</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Google has released an emergency security update for its Chrome web browser to fix a high-severity zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2025-13223, that is being actively exploited. The flaw is a type confusion vulnerability in the V8 JavaScript engine, which could allow a remote attacker to achieve arbitrary code execution by tricking a user into visiting a malicious website. The patch has been released for Chrome version 142.0.7444.175 on Windows, macOS, and Linux. Users of other Chromium-based browsers like Microsoft Edge and Brave are also urged to update immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Google has released an emergency patch for CVE-2025-13223, a high-severity, actively exploited zero-day type confusion vulnerability in the Chrome V8 JavaScript engine that allows for remote code execution.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-v8-zero-day-cve-2025-13223</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-v8-zero-day-cve-2025-13223/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Supply Chain Breach at Banking Vendor SitusAMC Exposes Client Financial Data</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/banking-vendor-situsamc-hit-by-supply-chain-attack-client-data-stolen/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/banking-vendor-situsamc-hit-by-supply-chain-attack-client-data-stolen/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Supply Chain Breach at Banking Vendor SitusAMC Exposes Client Financial Data</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>SitusAMC, a major third-party technology and services provider for the banking and real estate finance industry, has disclosed a cyberattack that occurred on November 12, 2025. The attackers breached SitusAMC's systems and exfiltrated sensitive data belonging to its banking clients, including accounting records and legal agreements. Personal data of the banks' customers was also compromised. The incident, which did not involve ransomware, is being investigated with the assistance of the FBI. It serves as a stark reminder of the significant supply chain risks within the heavily regulated financial services sector.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Data Breach, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> SitusAMC, a major vendor for the banking industry, has suffered a supply chain cyberattack, resulting in the theft of sensitive data from its clients and their customers, highlighting major third-party risks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> banking-vendor-situsamc-hit-by-supply-chain-attack-client-data-stolen</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/banking-vendor-situsamc-hit-by-supply-chain-attack-client-data-stolen/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Fortinet Warns of Actively Exploited Zero-Day in FortiWeb WAF Appliances</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fortinet-warns-of-actively-exploited-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fortinet-warns-of-actively-exploited-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Fortinet Warns of Actively Exploited Zero-Day in FortiWeb WAF Appliances</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Fortinet has revealed that a command injection vulnerability in its FortiWeb web application firewall (WAF), CVE-2025-58034, was exploited as a zero-day before a patch was available. The flaw, rated medium severity (CVSS 6.7), allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code. However, its risk is significantly elevated as it can be chained with another recently disclosed path-traversal zero-day (CVE-2025-64446). This combination allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to bypass authentication, create an admin account, and achieve full remote code execution. Patches are available and should be applied immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Cyberattack, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Fortinet warns of an actively exploited zero-day command injection flaw (CVE-2025-58034) in FortiWeb that can be chained with another vulnerability for unauthenticated RCE. Immediate patching is required.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> fortinet-warns-of-actively-exploited-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fortinet-warns-of-actively-exploited-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Black Friday Phishing Attacks Surge Over 600%; Amazon is Top Impersonated Brand</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/black-friday-phishing-attacks-skyrocket-620-percent-amazon-impersonated/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/black-friday-phishing-attacks-skyrocket-620-percent-amazon-impersonated/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Black Friday Phishing Attacks Surge Over 600%; Amazon is Top Impersonated Brand</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>As the Black Friday shopping season approaches, a new analysis from Darktrace reveals a massive 620% increase in phishing attacks since the beginning of November 2025. Attacks impersonating major retailers like Walmart and Macy's have jumped 54% in the last week alone. Amazon is the most abused brand, featuring in 80% of all major brand impersonation phishing attempts. Researchers warn that attack volumes are expected to climb another 20-30% during the peak shopping week, with cybercriminals using fake 'deal' websites and social engineering to lure victims into giving up personal data and payment information.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Phishing, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new report shows Black Friday phishing attacks have surged by 620% in November, with Amazon being impersonated in 80% of brand-related phishing scams designed to steal shopper data.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> black-friday-phishing-attacks-skyrocket-620-percent-amazon-impersonated</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/black-friday-phishing-attacks-skyrocket-620-percent-amazon-impersonated/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: UK Bill to Regulate Critical Infrastructure Supply Chain for First Time</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-introduces-cyber-security-and-resilience-bill-to-regulate-critical-suppliers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-introduces-cyber-security-and-resilience-bill-to-regulate-critical-suppliers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> UK Bill to Regulate Critical Infrastructure Supply Chain for First Time</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The United Kingdom has introduced the Cyber Security and Resilience Bill, a new law that will, for the first time, regulate the cybersecurity practices of suppliers to the nation's critical infrastructure. The bill aims to prevent supply chain attacks by legally requiring companies deemed 'critical suppliers'—such as IT management firms and data centers serving entities like the NHS and energy companies—to meet minimum security standards. These suppliers will also be mandated to report significant breaches to the government and the National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) and demonstrate robust incident response capabilities.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Supply Chain Attack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The UK government has introduced the Cyber Security and Resilience Bill, a new law that will regulate suppliers to critical infrastructure for the first time to prevent supply chain attacks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> uk-introduces-cyber-security-and-resilience-bill-to-regulate-critical-suppliers</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-introduces-cyber-security-and-resilience-bill-to-regulate-critical-suppliers/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Flaw in Chinese Electric Buses Allowing Remote Disabling Sparks European Security Probes</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/remote-disabling-flaw-in-chinese-electric-buses-sparks-european-security-probes/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/remote-disabling-flaw-in-chinese-electric-buses-sparks-european-security-probes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Flaw in Chinese Electric Buses Allowing Remote Disabling Sparks European Security Probes</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A software vulnerability discovered in Chinese-made electric buses operating in Oslo, Norway, has raised significant security alarms across Europe. The flaw could reportedly allow the vehicles to be remotely disabled, prompting authorities in the UK and Denmark to launch their own investigations into similar bus fleets. This incident has intensified concerns about potential backdoors and kill switches in Chinese technology embedded in critical public infrastructure. The finding comes amid heightened warnings from security agencies about pre-positioned threats in Western networks, such as the 'Volt Typhoon' campaign.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Industrial Control Systems, Vulnerability, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A software vulnerability in Chinese-made electric buses that could allow for remote disabling has been found in Norway, prompting security investigations in the UK and Denmark amid fears of backdoors in critical infrastructure.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> remote-disabling-flaw-in-chinese-electric-buses-sparks-european-security-probes</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/remote-disabling-flaw-in-chinese-electric-buses-sparks-european-security-probes/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: URGENT: CISA Orders 7-Day Patch for Actively Exploited FortiWeb Zero-Day</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> URGENT: CISA Orders 7-Day Patch for Actively Exploited FortiWeb Zero-Day</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Fortinet has disclosed a critical OS command injection zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2025-58034, in its FortiWeb Web Application Firewall (WAF) that is being actively exploited in the wild. The flaw allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying system. In response to observed attacks, the U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added the vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog and issued an emergency directive mandating federal agencies apply patches within an accelerated seven-day window, by November 25, 2025. Researchers have detected approximately 2,000 attacks leveraging the flaw and warn it could potentially be chained with a recently disclosed authentication bypass vulnerability (CVE-2025-64446) to achieve unauthenticated remote code execution.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Fortinet discloses and CISA mandates urgent patching for CVE-2025-58034, a critical OS command injection zero-day in FortiWeb WAFs that is under active exploitation. Learn about the risks and mitigation steps.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 2</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 2 updates recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>