<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:50:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Massive NPM Supply Chain Attack Spreads Self-Replicating "Shai-Hulud" Worm</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/massive-npm-supply-chain-attack-spreads-shai-hulud-worm/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/massive-npm-supply-chain-attack-spreads-shai-hulud-worm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Massive NPM Supply Chain Attack Spreads Self-Replicating "Shai-Hulud" Worm</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A significant, ongoing supply chain attack is targeting the NPM JavaScript ecosystem, where a self-replicating worm dubbed "Shai-Hulud" has infected over 400 software packages. The attack has a substantial impact on the cryptocurrency sector, compromising at least 10 widely used libraries crucial for the Ethereum Name Service (ENS), including 'content-hash' and 'address-encoder'. The malware functions as a general-purpose credential stealer, exfiltrating secrets like wallet keys from infected developer environments. The scale is vast, with researchers at Wiz observing over 25,000 affected repositories, highlighting a critical threat to developer infrastructure worldwide.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Malware, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A major supply chain attack on the NPM repository involves the 'Shai-Hulud' worm, which has compromised hundreds of packages, including critical crypto libraries for ENS, to steal developer credentials.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> massive-npm-supply-chain-attack-spreads-shai-hulud-worm</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/massive-npm-supply-chain-attack-spreads-shai-hulud-worm/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Salesforce Data of 200+ Firms Exposed in Gainsight Supply Chain Breach</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/salesforce-data-exposed-in-gainsight-supply-chain-attack/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/salesforce-data-exposed-in-gainsight-supply-chain-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Salesforce Data of 200+ Firms Exposed in Gainsight Supply Chain Breach</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A sophisticated supply chain attack has compromised the sensitive data of over 200 corporate clients using Salesforce. The breach did not originate within Salesforce but through a third-party application from Gainsight. The threat actor group "Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters," reportedly linked to ShinyHunters, claimed responsibility, stating they used stolen authentication tokens to access Gainsight and pivot to connected Salesforce instances. High-profile companies like Atlassian, CrowdStrike, and Verizon were named as victims, though several have denied impact. As a precaution, Salesforce has revoked all active access tokens for Gainsight integrations.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Data Breach, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A supply chain attack on Gainsight, a Salesforce-integrated platform, has exposed data from over 200 corporate clients. The 'Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters' group claims responsibility.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> salesforce-data-exposed-in-gainsight-supply-chain-attack</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/salesforce-data-exposed-in-gainsight-supply-chain-attack/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Wall Street Banks Hit by Data Breach at Mortgage Technology Vendor SitusAMC</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/wall-street-banks-hit-by-breach-at-mortgage-tech-vendor-situsamc/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/wall-street-banks-hit-by-breach-at-mortgage-tech-vendor-situsamc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Wall Street Banks Hit by Data Breach at Mortgage Technology Vendor SitusAMC</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A significant cyberattack on SitusAMC, a key technology and service provider for the U.S. real estate finance industry, has exposed sensitive data belonging to major Wall Street banks, including JPMorgan Chase, Citi, and Morgan Stanley. The breach, first detected on November 12th, compromised both corporate data and customer information related to residential mortgages. SitusAMC, which serves most leading firms in the $13.5 trillion mortgage market, confirmed the incident but stated it did not involve ransomware. The attack highlights the systemic risk posed by third-party vendors in the critical financial supply chain.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Supply Chain Attack, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A cyberattack on mortgage technology vendor SitusAMC has exposed sensitive data from major Wall Street banks like JPMorgan Chase, Citi, and Morgan Stanley, highlighting significant supply chain risks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> wall-street-banks-hit-by-breach-at-mortgage-tech-vendor-situsamc</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/wall-street-banks-hit-by-breach-at-mortgage-tech-vendor-situsamc/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: FCC Rolls Back ISP Cybersecurity Rules Despite China-Linked Hacking Threats</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fcc-rescinds-isp-cybersecurity-rules-amidst-ongoing-threats/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fcc-rescinds-isp-cybersecurity-rules-amidst-ongoing-threats/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> FCC Rolls Back ISP Cybersecurity Rules Despite China-Linked Hacking Threats</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>In a controversial decision, the U.S. Federal Communications Commission (FCC) has rescinded cybersecurity regulations for internet service providers (ISPs). These rules were implemented by the Biden Administration following the discovery that the Chinese state-sponsored hacking group Salt Typhoon had breached major U.S. carriers. The revoked rules mandated minimum security standards and compliance certifications. The FCC claimed the original ruling was based on a "flawed legal analysis," but the move has drawn sharp criticism, with Commissioner Anna M. Gomez stating it leaves the country "less secure" against increasing nation-state threats.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The U.S. FCC has controversially rescinded cybersecurity regulations for ISPs that were enacted after breaches by the China-linked Salt Typhoon hacking group, raising national security concerns.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> fcc-rescinds-isp-cybersecurity-rules-amidst-ongoing-threats</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fcc-rescinds-isp-cybersecurity-rules-amidst-ongoing-threats/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Akira Ransomware Gang Hits LG Energy Solution, Claims 1.7TB Data Theft</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/akira-ransomware-hits-lg-energy-solution-claims-1-7tb-data-theft/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/akira-ransomware-hits-lg-energy-solution-claims-1-7tb-data-theft/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Akira Ransomware Gang Hits LG Energy Solution, Claims 1.7TB Data Theft</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>South Korean battery manufacturing giant LG Energy Solution has confirmed it was the victim of a ransomware attack at one of its overseas facilities. The notorious Akira ransomware gang has claimed responsibility for the breach, alleging on its dark web leak site that it stole 1.7 terabytes of data from the company's network. While LG Energy Solution reports that the affected systems have been restored and its headquarters was not impacted, the incident highlights the continued threat of double-extortion ransomware attacks against the manufacturing sector. The Akira gang has been highly active, often gaining initial access via compromised VPN credentials.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Akira ransomware gang has attacked LG Energy Solution, a major battery manufacturer, claiming to have stolen 1.7TB of data in a double-extortion attack on one of its overseas facilities.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> akira-ransomware-hits-lg-energy-solution-claims-1-7tb-data-theft</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/akira-ransomware-hits-lg-energy-solution-claims-1-7tb-data-theft/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New "Autumn Dragon" Espionage Campaign Targets Southeast Asia</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/autumn-dragon-espionage-campaign-targets-southeast-asian-nations/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/autumn-dragon-espionage-campaign-targets-southeast-asian-nations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New "Autumn Dragon" Espionage Campaign Targets Southeast Asia</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A newly identified cyber-espionage campaign named "Autumn Dragon" has been targeting government and media organizations across Southeast Asia since early 2025. The operation, attributed with medium confidence to a China-nexus Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) group, aims to gather intelligence related to the South China Sea. The attackers use spearphishing emails with malicious WinRAR archives that exploit the vulnerability CVE-2025-8088. Upon execution, a dropper script masquerading as a Windows Defender update retrieves and runs additional payloads to establish a foothold for intelligence gathering.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Cyberattack, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The 'Autumn Dragon' cyber-espionage campaign, linked to a China-nexus APT, is targeting government and media organizations in Southeast Asia using a WinRAR vulnerability (CVE-2025-8088).</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> autumn-dragon-espionage-campaign-targets-southeast-asian-nations</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/autumn-dragon-espionage-campaign-targets-southeast-asian-nations/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: ShadowPad Backdoor Deployed via Critical WSUS Server Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/shadowpad-backdoor-deployed-exploiting-windows-server-vulnerability/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/shadowpad-backdoor-deployed-exploiting-windows-server-vulnerability/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> ShadowPad Backdoor Deployed via Critical WSUS Server Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>An active intrusion campaign is exploiting a critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability, CVE-2025-59287, in Microsoft's Windows Server Update Services (WSUS). Attackers, believed to be Chinese state-sponsored APTs, are leveraging the flaw to gain system-level access and deploy the sophisticated ShadowPad backdoor. The attack chain involves using PowerShell and legitimate system utilities like 'certutil' and 'curl' to download the malware, which is then executed using a DLL sideloading technique for stealth and persistence. The campaign highlights the rapid weaponization of newly disclosed vulnerabilities for espionage purposes.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Threat Actor, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Chinese state-sponsored APTs are actively exploiting a critical RCE vulnerability (CVE-2025-59287) in Microsoft WSUS to deploy the ShadowPad backdoor for espionage. Patching is critical.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> shadowpad-backdoor-deployed-exploiting-windows-server-vulnerability</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/shadowpad-backdoor-deployed-exploiting-windows-server-vulnerability/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Supply Chain Breaches Escalate Despite Maturing Defenses, Report Finds</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/supply-chain-breaches-rise-despite-increased-defense-efforts-report-finds/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/supply-chain-breaches-rise-despite-increased-defense-efforts-report-finds/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Supply Chain Breaches Escalate Despite Maturing Defenses, Report Finds</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new 2025 report from cybersecurity firm BlueVoyant reveals a troubling trend: despite most organizations maturing their third-party risk management (TPRM) programs, the number of supply chain breaches is escalating. The study found that 97% of surveyed organizations experienced a supplier-related security incident in the past year, a significant jump from 81% in 2024. The report identifies ineffective tool integration and internal organizational silos as key barriers, with the manufacturing sector being particularly hard-hit, averaging 3.8 breaches per organization.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Security Operations, Policy and Compliance, Supply Chain Attack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A 2025 BlueVoyant report finds that 97% of organizations experienced a supply chain breach in the past year, up from 81% in 2024, indicating that current TPRM programs are proving ineffective.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> supply-chain-breaches-rise-despite-increased-defense-efforts-report-finds</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/supply-chain-breaches-rise-despite-increased-defense-efforts-report-finds/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Ransomware Attacks Peak on Holidays and Weekends, Exploiting Low Staffing</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-attacks-peak-on-holidays-and-weekends-study-shows/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-attacks-peak-on-holidays-and-weekends-study-shows/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Ransomware Attacks Peak on Holidays and Weekends, Exploiting Low Staffing</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new global study by Semperis, the "2025 Holiday Ransomware Risk Report," confirms that threat actors strategically launch attacks during holidays and weekends to exploit reduced security staffing. The report found that 52% of organizations were targeted during these off-hour periods. Alarmingly, 78% of companies cut their Security Operation Center (SOC) staffing by 50% or more during these times. The study also revealed that 60% of attacks follow major corporate events like mergers or layoffs, when organizations are most distracted.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Security Operations, Ransomware, Incident Response</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new Semperis report reveals that 52% of ransomware attacks occur during holidays and weekends, exploiting periods when security operations center (SOC) staffing is significantly reduced.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ransomware-attacks-peak-on-holidays-and-weekends-study-shows</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-attacks-peak-on-holidays-and-weekends-study-shows/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Incident Response</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Italian IT Firm Almaviva Hit by Cyberattack, 2.3TB of Data Leaked</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/italian-it-firm-almaviva-hit-by-cyberattack-2-3tb-of-data-leaked/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/italian-it-firm-almaviva-hit-by-cyberattack-2-3tb-of-data-leaked/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Italian IT Firm Almaviva Hit by Cyberattack, 2.3TB of Data Leaked</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The prominent Italian IT services provider Almaviva has confirmed it was hit by a major cyberattack, resulting in the theft and leaking of nearly 2.3 terabytes of sensitive data. The breach has exposed information from several of Almaviva's clients, most notably Italy's national railway operator, Ferrovie dello Stato Italiane. The leaked files reportedly include highly sensitive data such as passenger passport details, employee records, financial documents, and defense-related contracts. The identity of the attackers has not yet been disclosed.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Cyberattack, Supply Chain Attack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Italian IT firm Almaviva confirms a major cyberattack resulting in a 2.3TB data leak, exposing sensitive information from clients like Italy's national railway, including passport and defense data.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> italian-it-firm-almaviva-hit-by-cyberattack-2-3tb-of-data-leaked</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/italian-it-firm-almaviva-hit-by-cyberattack-2-3tb-of-data-leaked/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Harvard University Data Breach Exposes Donor Information After Phone Phishing Attack</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/harvard-university-discloses-data-breach-from-phone-phishing-attack/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/harvard-university-discloses-data-breach-from-phone-phishing-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Harvard University Data Breach Exposes Donor Information After Phone Phishing Attack</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Harvard University has disclosed a data breach affecting its Alumni Affairs and Development Office, discovered on November 18, 2025. The incident originated from a phone-based phishing (vishing) attack that gave an unauthorized party access to systems containing personal information and donation records of university affiliates and donors. While highly sensitive data like Social Security numbers were reportedly not compromised, the breach exposed names, contact details, and donation histories. This attack follows a similar pattern seen in recent incidents at Princeton University and the University of Pennsylvania, indicating a targeted campaign against the development departments of major educational institutions.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Phishing, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Harvard University's Alumni Affairs and Development Office was hit by a data breach originating from a phone-based phishing attack, potentially exposing donor records and personal information. Learn about the incident and mitigation steps.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> harvard-university-discloses-data-breach-from-phone-phishing-attack</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/harvard-university-discloses-data-breach-from-phone-phishing-attack/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Cl0p Ransomware Exploits Oracle Zero-Day to Breach Cox Enterprises, Hitting 9,500 Individuals</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cox-enterprises-discloses-data-breach-from-clop-exploit-of-oracle-zero-day/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cox-enterprises-discloses-data-breach-from-clop-exploit-of-oracle-zero-day/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Cl0p Ransomware Exploits Oracle Zero-Day to Breach Cox Enterprises, Hitting 9,500 Individuals</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Cox Enterprises, a $23 billion American conglomerate, has confirmed a data breach affecting nearly 9,500 individuals due to the exploitation of a zero-day vulnerability (CVE-2025-61882) in Oracle's E-Business Suite. The breach occurred in August 2025 but was not detected until late September. The notorious Cl0p ransomware gang has claimed responsibility, adding this attack to their long list of zero-day exploits against enterprise software, including MOVEit Transfer and GoAnywhere MFT. Cox is offering identity theft protection to affected individuals as the full scope of exposed data remains undisclosed.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Vulnerability, Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Cox Enterprises reports a data breach affecting 9,479 individuals after the Cl0p ransomware gang exploited a zero-day vulnerability (CVE-2025-61882) in Oracle E-Business Suite. Learn more about the attack.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cox-enterprises-discloses-data-breach-from-clop-exploit-of-oracle-zero-day</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cox-enterprises-discloses-data-breach-from-clop-exploit-of-oracle-zero-day/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: APT24's Three-Year "BadAudio" Cyberespionage Campaign Uncovered by Google</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apt24-badaudio-malware-campaign-exposed-after-three-years-of-espionage/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apt24-badaudio-malware-campaign-exposed-after-three-years-of-espionage/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> APT24's Three-Year "BadAudio" Cyberespionage Campaign Uncovered by Google</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Google's Threat Analysis Group (GTIG) has detailed a sophisticated, nearly three-year-long cyberespionage campaign attributed to the China-linked threat actor APT24. Active since at least November 2022, the operation used a custom C++ downloader called "BadAudio" to deploy payloads like Cobalt Strike. APT24's tactics evolved from broad strategic web compromises to a highly targeted supply chain attack in July 2024, where they compromised a Taiwanese digital marketing firm to distribute their malware. The campaign showcases the actor's persistence, adaptability, and use of advanced obfuscation and social engineering techniques.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Supply Chain Attack, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 7 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Google's Threat Analysis Group has exposed a nearly three-year cyberespionage campaign by APT24, which used 'BadAudio' malware and supply chain attacks to target organizations in Taiwan.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> apt24-badaudio-malware-campaign-exposed-after-three-years-of-espionage</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apt24-badaudio-malware-campaign-exposed-after-three-years-of-espionage/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Critical CVSS 10.0 Vulnerability in Grafana Enterprise Allows Account Takeover</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/grafana-enterprise-hit-by-critical-cvss-10-vulnerability-cve-2025-41115/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/grafana-enterprise-hit-by-critical-cvss-10-vulnerability-cve-2025-41115/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Critical CVSS 10.0 Vulnerability in Grafana Enterprise Allows Account Takeover</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Grafana has released urgent patches for CVE-2025-41115, a critical vulnerability in Grafana Enterprise with a maximum CVSS score of 10.0. The flaw resides in the System for Cross-domain Identity Management (SCIM) component and can allow a malicious SCIM client to provide a numeric external ID that overrides an internal user ID, leading to complete account takeover or privilege escalation. The vulnerability affects Grafana Enterprise versions 12.0.0 to 12.2.1 but is only exploitable if SCIM is explicitly enabled. Administrators are urged to update their instances immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A critical CVSS 10.0 vulnerability, CVE-2025-41115, has been discovered in Grafana Enterprise. The flaw allows for account takeover and requires immediate patching. Learn about the affected versions and mitigation steps.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> grafana-enterprise-hit-by-critical-cvss-10-vulnerability-cve-2025-41115</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/grafana-enterprise-hit-by-critical-cvss-10-vulnerability-cve-2025-41115/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Microsoft Mitigates Record-Breaking 15.72 Tbps DDoS Attack Targeting Azure</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-mitigates-record-breaking-15-72-tbps-ddos-attack-on-azure/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-mitigates-record-breaking-15-72-tbps-ddos-attack-on-azure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Microsoft Mitigates Record-Breaking 15.72 Tbps DDoS Attack Targeting Azure</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Microsoft has successfully mitigated the largest Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) attack ever recorded, peaking at an unprecedented 15.72 terabits per second (Tbps). The massive UDP flood attack, which also reached 3.64 billion packets per second, was attributed to the Aisuru Turbo botnet, a variant of the Mirai family. The attack originated from over 500,000 compromised IoT devices and targeted a public IP address on the Microsoft Azure cloud in Australia. Microsoft's advanced, real-time mitigation systems were able to absorb and filter the malicious traffic, preventing widespread service outages.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cyberattack, Threat Intelligence, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Microsoft successfully defended against a record-breaking 15.72 Tbps DDoS attack on its Azure cloud, launched by the Mirai-variant botnet 'Aisuru Turbo'. Learn about the attack and mitigation strategies.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> microsoft-mitigates-record-breaking-15-72-tbps-ddos-attack-on-azure</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-mitigates-record-breaking-15-72-tbps-ddos-attack-on-azure/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Chinese APT31 Group Infiltrates Russian IT Firms Using Yandex and OneDrive for C2</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-linked-apt31-targets-russian-it-sector-with-cloud-based-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-linked-apt31-targets-russian-it-sector-with-cloud-based-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Chinese APT31 Group Infiltrates Russian IT Firms Using Yandex and OneDrive for C2</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The China-linked threat group APT31 (also known as Zirconium or Violet Typhoon) has been conducting a prolonged cyber espionage campaign against the Russian IT sector, primarily targeting contractors for government agencies. According to Positive Technologies, the attacks, which took place between 2024 and 2025, were notable for their stealth. The group leveraged legitimate cloud services, including Yandex Cloud and Microsoft OneDrive, for command and control (C2) and data exfiltration. This tactic allowed their malicious traffic to blend in with normal network activity, enabling them to remain undetected in victim networks for years.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Cyberattack, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 7 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The China-linked group APT31 conducted a stealthy, multi-year cyber espionage campaign against the Russian IT sector, using legitimate cloud services like Yandex Cloud and OneDrive for C2.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> china-linked-apt31-targets-russian-it-sector-with-cloud-based-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-linked-apt31-targets-russian-it-sector-with-cloud-based-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CrowdStrike Fires Employee for Leaking Internal System Details to Hacking Group</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/crowdstrike-fires-employee-for-leaking-internal-data-to-hackers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/crowdstrike-fires-employee-for-leaking-internal-data-to-hackers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CrowdStrike Fires Employee for Leaking Internal System Details to Hacking Group</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Cybersecurity leader CrowdStrike has terminated an employee who was caught providing sensitive internal system information to an external hacking group. The company confirmed the insider threat incident on November 22, 2025, stating that its internal security protocols successfully detected and contained the threat. CrowdStrike reassured its customers that the incident was isolated and that no customer data or environments were accessed or compromised. The event serves as a powerful reminder that even the most security-focused organizations are susceptible to insider threats.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Threat Intelligence, Security Operations</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CrowdStrike terminated an employee in a malicious insider threat incident after the individual was caught sharing sensitive internal system information with a hacking group. No customer data was affected.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> crowdstrike-fires-employee-for-leaking-internal-data-to-hackers</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/crowdstrike-fires-employee-for-leaking-internal-data-to-hackers/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Fortinet Patches Actively Exploited Command Injection Flaw in FortiWeb WAF</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fortinet-patches-actively-exploited-fortiweb-command-injection-vulnerability-cve-2025-58034/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fortinet-patches-actively-exploited-fortiweb-command-injection-vulnerability-cve-2025-58034/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Fortinet Patches Actively Exploited Command Injection Flaw in FortiWeb WAF</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Fortinet has addressed an actively exploited command injection vulnerability, CVE-2025-58034, in its FortiWeb Web Application Firewall (WAF). The flaw allows an authenticated attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specially crafted requests. The vulnerability was reportedly 'stealth-patched' initially, with fixes included in software updates before a public advisory was released. With active exploitation confirmed and an exploit module now available in the Metasploit framework, Fortinet is urging all customers using affected 7.x and 8.x versions to apply the security updates immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Fortinet is urging customers to patch an actively exploited command injection vulnerability (CVE-2025-58034) in its FortiWeb WAF. The flaw allows for remote code execution and has a public Metasploit exploit.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> fortinet-patches-actively-exploited-fortiweb-command-injection-vulnerability-cve-2025-58034</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fortinet-patches-actively-exploited-fortiweb-command-injection-vulnerability-cve-2025-58034/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Google Patches Seventh Actively Exploited Chrome Zero-Day of 2025</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-zero-day-vulnerability-cve-2025-13223/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-zero-day-vulnerability-cve-2025-13223/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Google Patches Seventh Actively Exploited Chrome Zero-Day of 2025</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Google has released an emergency security update for its Chrome browser, patching a high-severity zero-day vulnerability tracked as CVE-2025-13223. The flaw, a type confusion weakness in the V8 JavaScript engine, is being actively exploited in the wild. A successful exploit could allow a remote attacker to achieve arbitrary code execution by tricking a user into visiting a malicious website. This is the seventh Chrome zero-day that Google has addressed in 2025. Users on Windows, macOS, and Linux are urged to update their browsers to version 142.0.7444.175 or later immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Google has patched CVE-2025-13223, a high-severity, actively exploited zero-day vulnerability in the Chrome V8 JavaScript engine. Users should update their browsers immediately to prevent remote code execution.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-zero-day-vulnerability-cve-2025-13223</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-zero-day-vulnerability-cve-2025-13223/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Gainsight Supply Chain Attack Exposes Data from Salesforce Customers; Verizon, GitLab Named as Victims</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/gainsight-supply-chain-attack-exposes-salesforce-customer-data/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/gainsight-supply-chain-attack-exposes-salesforce-customer-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Gainsight Supply Chain Attack Exposes Data from Salesforce Customers; Verizon, GitLab Named as Victims</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A supply chain attack targeting Gainsight, a customer success platform that integrates with Salesforce, has led to a significant data breach. A group calling itself 'Scattered LAPSUS$ Hunters' has claimed responsibility, alleging they have compromised data from 300 organizations, including high-profile Salesforce customers like Verizon, GitLab, and Atlassian. In response, Salesforce has revoked all active access tokens for the Gainsight integration to prevent further unauthorized access. The incident underscores the growing risk of supply chain attacks, where a breach at a third-party partner can have a cascading impact on its customers.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Data Breach, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 7 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A supply chain attack on the Gainsight platform has exposed data from hundreds of Salesforce customers, including Verizon and GitLab. A group called 'Scattered LAPSUS$ Hunters' has claimed responsibility.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> gainsight-supply-chain-attack-exposes-salesforce-customer-data</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/gainsight-supply-chain-attack-exposes-salesforce-customer-data/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Logitech Confirms Breach: Clop Ransomware Exploits Oracle Zero-Day</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/logitech-confirms-data-breach-by-clop-ransomware-via-oracle-zero-day/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/logitech-confirms-data-breach-by-clop-ransomware-via-oracle-zero-day/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Logitech Confirms Breach: Clop Ransomware Exploits Oracle Zero-Day</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Logitech has confirmed it suffered a data breach after the Clop ransomware gang exploited a zero-day vulnerability in Oracle's E-Business Suite (CVE-2025-61882). The consumer electronics giant stated that an unauthorized third party accessed and copied data related to employees, consumers, and suppliers. The incident is part of a wider campaign by Clop that has impacted numerous major organizations. Logitech asserts that sensitive personal data like credit card numbers was not exposed and business operations remain unaffected.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Ransomware, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Logitech confirms it was breached by the Clop ransomware gang, who exploited a zero-day vulnerability (CVE-2025-61882) in Oracle's E-Business Suite to steal company data.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> logitech-confirms-data-breach-by-clop-ransomware-via-oracle-zero-day</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 12:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/logitech-confirms-data-breach-by-clop-ransomware-via-oracle-zero-day/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: URGENT: CISA Orders 7-Day Patch for Actively Exploited FortiWeb Zero-Day</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> URGENT: CISA Orders 7-Day Patch for Actively Exploited FortiWeb Zero-Day</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Fortinet has disclosed a critical OS command injection zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2025-58034, in its FortiWeb Web Application Firewall (WAF) that is being actively exploited in the wild. The flaw allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying system. In response to observed attacks, the U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added the vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog and issued an emergency directive mandating federal agencies apply patches within an accelerated seven-day window, by November 25, 2025. Researchers have detected approximately 2,000 attacks leveraging the flaw and warn it could potentially be chained with a recently disclosed authentication bypass vulnerability (CVE-2025-64446) to achieve unauthenticated remote code execution.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Fortinet discloses and CISA mandates urgent patching for CVE-2025-58034, a critical OS command injection zero-day in FortiWeb WAFs that is under active exploitation. Learn about the risks and mitigation steps.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>