<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:59:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Sha1-Hulud: Destructive Supply Chain Attack Hits 25,000+ Repos via npm</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sha1-hulud-supply-chain-attack-compromises-25000-github-repos-via-npm/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sha1-hulud-supply-chain-attack-compromises-25000-github-repos-via-npm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Sha1-Hulud: Destructive Supply Chain Attack Hits 25,000+ Repos via npm</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A sophisticated and self-propagating software supply chain attack, dubbed 'Sha1-Hulud,' has compromised over 25,000 GitHub repositories since November 21, 2025. The attack leverages hundreds of malicious npm packages that execute code during the `preinstall` phase to steal developer credentials, GitHub tokens, and cloud secrets. The malware exfiltrates stolen data to public GitHub repositories and includes a destructive 'scorched earth' component that wipes the victim's home directory if data theft fails, turning it into a denial-of-service attack. The campaign has impacted packages from major organizations like Zapier, Postman, and ENS Domains, highlighting a severe threat to the open-source ecosystem.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Malware, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A massive software supply chain attack dubbed 'Sha1-Hulud' has compromised over 25,000 GitHub repositories by using malicious npm packages to steal developer credentials and secrets during the preinstall phase.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> sha1-hulud-supply-chain-attack-compromises-25000-github-repos-via-npm</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sha1-hulud-supply-chain-attack-compromises-25000-github-repos-via-npm/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA: Commercial Spyware Hijacking Signal &amp; WhatsApp via Zero-Clicks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-commercial-spyware-targets-signal-whatsapp-users/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-commercial-spyware-targets-signal-whatsapp-users/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA: Commercial Spyware Hijacking Signal &amp; WhatsApp via Zero-Clicks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has issued a critical alert regarding active campaigns using commercial spyware to compromise the Signal and WhatsApp accounts of high-value targets. Attackers are employing sophisticated methods including social engineering, malicious QR codes for device linking, and zero-click exploits that require no user interaction. The campaigns are reportedly targeting current and former government officials, military personnel, and civil society organizations across the U.S., Europe, and the Middle East. CISA warns that initial access to messaging apps is often used as a beachhead to deploy further malware and achieve full device compromise.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Mobile Security, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA warns that threat actors are using commercial spyware with sophisticated techniques like zero-click exploits to hijack Signal and WhatsApp accounts of high-value targets, including government officials.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-warns-commercial-spyware-targets-signal-whatsapp-users</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-commercial-spyware-targets-signal-whatsapp-users/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Patch Now: Critical 9.8 RCE Flaw in Oracle Identity Manager Under Active Attack</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-orders-patch-for-critical-oracle-identity-manager-rce-flaw-cve-2025-61757/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-orders-patch-for-critical-oracle-identity-manager-rce-flaw-cve-2025-61757/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Patch Now: Critical 9.8 RCE Flaw in Oracle Identity Manager Under Active Attack</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability, CVE-2025-61757, in Oracle Identity Manager is being actively exploited by threat actors. The flaw, which has a CVSS score of 9.8, allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain complete control over vulnerable systems via a specially crafted HTTP request. The vulnerability stems from a missing authentication check in the product's REST WebServices component. Due to evidence of in-the-wild exploitation, CISA has added the bug to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog and mandated that all U.S. federal agencies apply the patch by December 12, 2025.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA has added a critical, actively exploited RCE vulnerability (CVE-2025-61757) in Oracle Identity Manager to its KEV catalog, ordering federal agencies to patch the 9.8 CVSS flaw by December 12, 2025.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-orders-patch-for-critical-oracle-identity-manager-rce-flaw-cve-2025-61757</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-orders-patch-for-critical-oracle-identity-manager-rce-flaw-cve-2025-61757/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Akira Ransomware Targets M&amp;A Blind Spots, Breaching Firms via Inherited SonicWall Devices</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/akira-ransomware-exploits-unpatched-sonicwall-devices-during-ma/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/akira-ransomware-exploits-unpatched-sonicwall-devices-during-ma/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Akira Ransomware Targets M&amp;A Blind Spots, Breaching Firms via Inherited SonicWall Devices</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Akira ransomware group is exploiting security blind spots created during corporate mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;A). According to research by ReliaQuest, Akira affiliates are gaining initial access to acquiring companies by compromising vulnerable SonicWall SSL VPN appliances inherited from smaller, acquired firms. Attackers leverage the fact that the acquiring organizations are often unaware of these unpatched, legacy devices on their new network. Once inside, they use zombie credentials and move laterally, with the time from lateral movement to ransomware deployment averaging less than one hour, highlighting a rapid and effective attack chain.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Akira ransomware group is exploiting security gaps during corporate mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;A) by compromising vulnerable SonicWall VPNs inherited from acquired firms to breach the parent company.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> akira-ransomware-exploits-unpatched-sonicwall-devices-during-ma</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/akira-ransomware-exploits-unpatched-sonicwall-devices-during-ma/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Google Patches Actively Exploited Chrome Zero-Day in V8 Engine</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-v8-zero-day-cve-2025-13223/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-v8-zero-day-cve-2025-13223/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Google Patches Actively Exploited Chrome Zero-Day in V8 Engine</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Google has released an emergency security update for its Chrome web browser to fix a high-severity zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2025-13223, that is being actively exploited. The flaw is a type confusion vulnerability in the V8 JavaScript engine, which could allow a remote attacker to achieve arbitrary code execution by tricking a user into visiting a malicious website. The patch has been released for Chrome version 142.0.7444.175 on Windows, macOS, and Linux. Users of other Chromium-based browsers like Microsoft Edge and Brave are also urged to update immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Google has released an emergency patch for CVE-2025-13223, a high-severity, actively exploited zero-day type confusion vulnerability in the Chrome V8 JavaScript engine that allows for remote code execution.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-v8-zero-day-cve-2025-13223</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-v8-zero-day-cve-2025-13223/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Supply Chain Breach at Banking Vendor SitusAMC Exposes Client Financial Data</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/banking-vendor-situsamc-hit-by-supply-chain-attack-client-data-stolen/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/banking-vendor-situsamc-hit-by-supply-chain-attack-client-data-stolen/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Supply Chain Breach at Banking Vendor SitusAMC Exposes Client Financial Data</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>SitusAMC, a major third-party technology and services provider for the banking and real estate finance industry, has disclosed a cyberattack that occurred on November 12, 2025. The attackers breached SitusAMC's systems and exfiltrated sensitive data belonging to its banking clients, including accounting records and legal agreements. Personal data of the banks' customers was also compromised. The incident, which did not involve ransomware, is being investigated with the assistance of the FBI. It serves as a stark reminder of the significant supply chain risks within the heavily regulated financial services sector.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Data Breach, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> SitusAMC, a major vendor for the banking industry, has suffered a supply chain cyberattack, resulting in the theft of sensitive data from its clients and their customers, highlighting major third-party risks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> banking-vendor-situsamc-hit-by-supply-chain-attack-client-data-stolen</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/banking-vendor-situsamc-hit-by-supply-chain-attack-client-data-stolen/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Fortinet Warns of Actively Exploited Zero-Day in FortiWeb WAF Appliances</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fortinet-warns-of-actively-exploited-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fortinet-warns-of-actively-exploited-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Fortinet Warns of Actively Exploited Zero-Day in FortiWeb WAF Appliances</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Fortinet has revealed that a command injection vulnerability in its FortiWeb web application firewall (WAF), CVE-2025-58034, was exploited as a zero-day before a patch was available. The flaw, rated medium severity (CVSS 6.7), allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code. However, its risk is significantly elevated as it can be chained with another recently disclosed path-traversal zero-day (CVE-2025-64446). This combination allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to bypass authentication, create an admin account, and achieve full remote code execution. Patches are available and should be applied immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Cyberattack, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Fortinet warns of an actively exploited zero-day command injection flaw (CVE-2025-58034) in FortiWeb that can be chained with another vulnerability for unauthenticated RCE. Immediate patching is required.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> fortinet-warns-of-actively-exploited-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fortinet-warns-of-actively-exploited-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Black Friday Phishing Attacks Surge Over 600%; Amazon is Top Impersonated Brand</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/black-friday-phishing-attacks-skyrocket-620-percent-amazon-impersonated/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/black-friday-phishing-attacks-skyrocket-620-percent-amazon-impersonated/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Black Friday Phishing Attacks Surge Over 600%; Amazon is Top Impersonated Brand</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>As the Black Friday shopping season approaches, a new analysis from Darktrace reveals a massive 620% increase in phishing attacks since the beginning of November 2025. Attacks impersonating major retailers like Walmart and Macy's have jumped 54% in the last week alone. Amazon is the most abused brand, featuring in 80% of all major brand impersonation phishing attempts. Researchers warn that attack volumes are expected to climb another 20-30% during the peak shopping week, with cybercriminals using fake 'deal' websites and social engineering to lure victims into giving up personal data and payment information.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Phishing, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new report shows Black Friday phishing attacks have surged by 620% in November, with Amazon being impersonated in 80% of brand-related phishing scams designed to steal shopper data.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> black-friday-phishing-attacks-skyrocket-620-percent-amazon-impersonated</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/black-friday-phishing-attacks-skyrocket-620-percent-amazon-impersonated/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: UK Bill to Regulate Critical Infrastructure Supply Chain for First Time</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-introduces-cyber-security-and-resilience-bill-to-regulate-critical-suppliers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-introduces-cyber-security-and-resilience-bill-to-regulate-critical-suppliers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> UK Bill to Regulate Critical Infrastructure Supply Chain for First Time</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The United Kingdom has introduced the Cyber Security and Resilience Bill, a new law that will, for the first time, regulate the cybersecurity practices of suppliers to the nation's critical infrastructure. The bill aims to prevent supply chain attacks by legally requiring companies deemed 'critical suppliers'—such as IT management firms and data centers serving entities like the NHS and energy companies—to meet minimum security standards. These suppliers will also be mandated to report significant breaches to the government and the National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) and demonstrate robust incident response capabilities.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Supply Chain Attack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The UK government has introduced the Cyber Security and Resilience Bill, a new law that will regulate suppliers to critical infrastructure for the first time to prevent supply chain attacks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> uk-introduces-cyber-security-and-resilience-bill-to-regulate-critical-suppliers</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-introduces-cyber-security-and-resilience-bill-to-regulate-critical-suppliers/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Flaw in Chinese Electric Buses Allowing Remote Disabling Sparks European Security Probes</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/remote-disabling-flaw-in-chinese-electric-buses-sparks-european-security-probes/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/remote-disabling-flaw-in-chinese-electric-buses-sparks-european-security-probes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Flaw in Chinese Electric Buses Allowing Remote Disabling Sparks European Security Probes</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A software vulnerability discovered in Chinese-made electric buses operating in Oslo, Norway, has raised significant security alarms across Europe. The flaw could reportedly allow the vehicles to be remotely disabled, prompting authorities in the UK and Denmark to launch their own investigations into similar bus fleets. This incident has intensified concerns about potential backdoors and kill switches in Chinese technology embedded in critical public infrastructure. The finding comes amid heightened warnings from security agencies about pre-positioned threats in Western networks, such as the 'Volt Typhoon' campaign.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Industrial Control Systems, Vulnerability, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A software vulnerability in Chinese-made electric buses that could allow for remote disabling has been found in Norway, prompting security investigations in the UK and Denmark amid fears of backdoors in critical infrastructure.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> remote-disabling-flaw-in-chinese-electric-buses-sparks-european-security-probes</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/remote-disabling-flaw-in-chinese-electric-buses-sparks-european-security-probes/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: URGENT: CISA Orders 7-Day Patch for Actively Exploited FortiWeb Zero-Day</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> URGENT: CISA Orders 7-Day Patch for Actively Exploited FortiWeb Zero-Day</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Fortinet has disclosed a critical OS command injection zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2025-58034, in its FortiWeb Web Application Firewall (WAF) that is being actively exploited in the wild. The flaw allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying system. In response to observed attacks, the U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added the vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog and issued an emergency directive mandating federal agencies apply patches within an accelerated seven-day window, by November 25, 2025. Researchers have detected approximately 2,000 attacks leveraging the flaw and warn it could potentially be chained with a recently disclosed authentication bypass vulnerability (CVE-2025-64446) to achieve unauthenticated remote code execution.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Fortinet discloses and CISA mandates urgent patching for CVE-2025-58034, a critical OS command injection zero-day in FortiWeb WAFs that is under active exploitation. Learn about the risks and mitigation steps.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 2</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 2 updates recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>