<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 16:51:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Urgent Patch for Critical WSUS Flaw as Attacks Surge</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-microsoft-wsus-flaw-cve-2025-59287-actively-exploited/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-microsoft-wsus-flaw-cve-2025-59287-actively-exploited/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Urgent Patch for Critical WSUS Flaw as Attacks Surge</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in Microsoft's Windows Server Update Services (WSUS), tracked as CVE-2025-59287 with a CVSS score of 9.8, is being actively exploited by threat actors. The flaw allows unauthenticated attackers to achieve SYSTEM-level privileges, leading Microsoft to release an emergency out-of-band patch after its initial October fix proved insufficient. The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added the vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, mandating federal agencies to patch by November 14, 2025. Security researchers have observed in-the-wild attacks leveraging unsafe deserialization in the WSUS `GetCookie()` endpoint, underscoring the urgency for all organizations to apply the update immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Urgent analysis of CVE-2025-59287, a critical RCE vulnerability in Microsoft WSUS being actively exploited. Learn detection methods and apply the emergency patch immediately.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> critical-microsoft-wsus-flaw-cve-2025-59287-actively-exploited</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-microsoft-wsus-flaw-cve-2025-59287-actively-exploited/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Dublin Airport Breach Exposes 3.8 Million Passengers After Supplier Hack</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/dublin-airport-data-breach-august-2025-collins-aerospace/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/dublin-airport-data-breach-august-2025-collins-aerospace/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Dublin Airport Breach Exposes 3.8 Million Passengers After Supplier Hack</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Dublin Airport has confirmed a significant data breach impacting up to 3.8 million passengers who traveled in August 2025. The incident stemmed from a ransomware attack on a third-party IT supplier, Collins Aerospace, which provides check-in and boarding software. The Everest ransomware group has claimed responsibility, stating they stole 1.5 million passenger records and published them online. The exposed data includes full names, booking references, and contact information, putting millions of travelers at risk of sophisticated phishing and social engineering attacks. The breach is part of a wider attack on Collins Aerospace that disrupted several major European airports.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Supply Chain Attack, Ransomware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Details on the Dublin Airport data breach affecting 3.8 million passengers. The breach stemmed from a ransomware attack on third-party supplier Collins Aerospace.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> dublin-airport-data-breach-august-2025-collins-aerospace</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/dublin-airport-data-breach-august-2025-collins-aerospace/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: DDoS Attack on Russian Food Agency Cripples National Supply Chains</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ddos-attack-russian-food-safety-agency-disrupts-supply-chain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ddos-attack-russian-food-safety-agency-disrupts-supply-chain/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> DDoS Attack on Russian Food Agency Cripples National Supply Chains</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Russia's federal agency for veterinary and phytosanitary surveillance, Rosselkhoznadzor, has been targeted by a large-scale distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack starting October 22, 2025. The attack crippled the agency's critical electronic certification systems, including the 'Mercury' platform, which is essential for tracking animal products. The outage caused significant delays in food shipments from major producers of meat, milk, and baby food across the nation, highlighting the vulnerability of critical national infrastructure to cyberattacks. Russian telecom providers are working to mitigate the attack, for which no group has claimed responsibility.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cyberattack, Industrial Control Systems, Policy and Compliance</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A large-scale DDoS attack on Russia's food safety agency, Rosselkhoznadzor, has disrupted national food supply chains by taking critical certification systems offline.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ddos-attack-russian-food-safety-agency-disrupts-supply-chain</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ddos-attack-russian-food-safety-agency-disrupts-supply-chain/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Safepay Ransomware Hits German Surveillance Firm Xortec, Sparking Supply Chain Fears</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/safepay-ransomware-targets-german-video-surveillance-firm-xortec/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/safepay-ransomware-targets-german-video-surveillance-firm-xortec/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Safepay Ransomware Hits German Surveillance Firm Xortec, Sparking Supply Chain Fears</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Safepay ransomware group has claimed responsibility for a cyberattack against Xortec GmbH, a German provider of professional video surveillance solutions. The group has listed Xortec on its data leak site with a payment deadline of October 27, 2025. This attack raises significant supply chain concerns, as a compromise of a value-added distributor like Xortec could potentially lead to backdoored hardware or software being deployed in sensitive client environments. Safepay is a relatively new but aggressive ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) operation known for its rapid double-extortion attacks.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Supply Chain Attack, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Safepay ransomware group has targeted German video surveillance firm Xortec, raising concerns of a major supply chain attack with systemic risks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> safepay-ransomware-targets-german-video-surveillance-firm-xortec</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/safepay-ransomware-targets-german-video-surveillance-firm-xortec/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Nations Sign Landmark UN Cybercrime Treaty Amidst Privacy and Rights Concerns</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/un-cybercrime-treaty-signed-hanoi-amidst-privacy-concerns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/un-cybercrime-treaty-signed-hanoi-amidst-privacy-concerns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Nations Sign Landmark UN Cybercrime Treaty Amidst Privacy and Rights Concerns</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>In a landmark event in Hanoi, Vietnam, 72 nations have signed the first-ever United Nations Convention against Cybercrime. The treaty aims to establish a global legal framework for international cooperation in fighting digital crime, including provisions for rapid cross-border evidence sharing. While hailed by the UN as a major step in multilateralism, the convention has drawn sharp criticism from over 160 technology firms, including Meta and Dell, and various civil society groups. Critics warn its broad language could be used to criminalize legitimate security research and enable governments to repress dissent under the guise of fighting cybercrime.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Dozens of countries sign the first global UN Convention against Cybercrime in Hanoi. The treaty aims to foster international cooperation but faces criticism over privacy concerns.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> un-cybercrime-treaty-signed-hanoi-amidst-privacy-concerns</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/un-cybercrime-treaty-signed-hanoi-amidst-privacy-concerns/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>