<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:41:28 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Actively Exploited WSUS RCE Gets Emergency Patch After Initial Fix Fails</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-microsoft-wsus-rce-flaw-actively-exploited-after-botched-patch/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-microsoft-wsus-rce-flaw-actively-exploited-after-botched-patch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Actively Exploited WSUS RCE Gets Emergency Patch After Initial Fix Fails</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A critical remote code execution vulnerability in Microsoft's Windows Server Update Services (WSUS), tracked as CVE-2025-59287 with a 9.8 CVSS score, is being actively exploited in the wild. The situation was exacerbated by a failed initial patch, which prompted Microsoft to release an emergency out-of-band update. The flaw allows unauthenticated attackers to achieve SYSTEM-level privileges on vulnerable servers. Due to confirmed in-the-wild attacks, CISA has added the vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, mandating swift action from federal agencies.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A critical RCE vulnerability (CVE-2025-59287) in Microsoft Windows Server Update Services (WSUS) is under active attack. Learn about the failed patch, emergency update, and mitigation steps.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> critical-microsoft-wsus-rce-flaw-actively-exploited-after-botched-patch</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-microsoft-wsus-rce-flaw-actively-exploited-after-botched-patch/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Qilin Ransomware Claims 700 Victims in 2025, Becoming Top Global Threat</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-surges-to-become-most-prolific-threat-of-2025/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-surges-to-become-most-prolific-threat-of-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Qilin Ransomware Claims 700 Victims in 2025, Becoming Top Global Threat</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Qilin ransomware group has dramatically escalated its activities in 2025, claiming over 700 attacks to become the year's most prolific ransomware operation. Operating a Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) model, the Russia-based group has far surpassed the activity of 2024's leader, RansomHub. A significant surge in Qilin's attacks followed the shutdown of the RansomHub operation in April 2025, suggesting a migration of affiliates. Qilin aggressively targets critical infrastructure sectors worldwide, including healthcare, finance, and government, using double-extortion tactics.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Analysis of the Qilin ransomware group, which has become the most active RaaS operation in 2025 with over 700 victims, targeting critical infrastructure globally.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> qilin-ransomware-surges-to-become-most-prolific-threat-of-2025</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-surges-to-become-most-prolific-threat-of-2025/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Everest Ransomware Hits Swedish Power Grid Operator, Steals 280GB of Data</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/swedish-power-grid-operator-svenska-kraftnat-hit-by-everest-ransomware/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/swedish-power-grid-operator-svenska-kraftnat-hit-by-everest-ransomware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Everest Ransomware Hits Swedish Power Grid Operator, Steals 280GB of Data</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Sweden's national electricity operator, Svenska kraftnät, has confirmed a data breach following a claim by the Everest ransomware group. The attackers alleged on their dark web leak site that they had stolen 280 GB of internal data. Svenska kraftnät stated that the attack was confined to an external file transfer system and that the nation's core power grid operations and electricity supply were not affected. An investigation is underway to determine the scope of the compromised data.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cyberattack, Data Breach, Industrial Control Systems</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Everest ransomware group has claimed a data breach against Sweden's national power grid operator, Svenska kraftnät, allegedly stealing 280 GB of data from an external system.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> swedish-power-grid-operator-svenska-kraftnat-hit-by-everest-ransomware</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/swedish-power-grid-operator-svenska-kraftnat-hit-by-everest-ransomware/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Massive Breach at Kenyan Health Platform M-TIBA Exposes 4.8 Million Patients</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/massive-data-breach-at-kenyan-health-platform-m-tiba-hits-millions/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/massive-data-breach-at-kenyan-health-platform-m-tiba-hits-millions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Massive Breach at Kenyan Health Platform M-TIBA Exposes 4.8 Million Patients</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A threat actor named 'Kazu' has claimed responsibility for a catastrophic data breach against M-TIBA, a major mobile health platform in Kenya backed by Safaricom. The hacker alleges the theft of 2.15 terabytes of data, impacting up to 4.8 million users. The compromised information reportedly includes a vast trove of personally identifiable information (PII) and highly sensitive protected health information (PHI), such as patient diagnoses and treatment records from nearly 700 healthcare facilities. A 2GB data sample has already been leaked to substantiate the claim.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Threat Actor, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A massive data breach at M-TIBA, a Kenyan mobile health platform, has allegedly exposed the personal and medical data of 4.8 million users. A threat actor known as 'Kazu' is responsible.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> massive-data-breach-at-kenyan-health-platform-m-tiba-hits-millions</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/massive-data-breach-at-kenyan-health-platform-m-tiba-hits-millions/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA Warns of Critical Flaws in Global Fuel Gauge Systems, Risking Infrastructure Disruption</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-issues-alert-for-critical-flaws-in-veeder-root-fuel-gauge-systems/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-issues-alert-for-critical-flaws-in-veeder-root-fuel-gauge-systems/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Warns of Critical Flaws in Global Fuel Gauge Systems, Risking Infrastructure Disruption</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has issued a critical advisory for two vulnerabilities in Veeder-Root's TLS4B Automatic Tank Gauge (ATG) systems, which are used globally to monitor fuel levels. The most severe flaw, CVE-2025-58428, has a CVSS score of 9.9 and could allow a remote, authenticated attacker to execute system-level commands, potentially causing widespread disruption to fuel infrastructure. A second flaw, CVE-2025-55067, relates to the 'Year 2038' problem and could cause denial-of-service conditions.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Industrial Control Systems, Vulnerability, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA has issued a critical advisory for two vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-58428, CVE-2025-55067) in Veeder-Root TLS4B Automatic Tank Gauge systems, which could lead to remote code execution and disruption of fuel infrastructure.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-issues-alert-for-critical-flaws-in-veeder-root-fuel-gauge-systems</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-issues-alert-for-critical-flaws-in-veeder-root-fuel-gauge-systems/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Critical Apache Tomcat Flaws Expose Servers to RCE and Console Hijacking</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-apache-tomcat-flaws-expose-servers-to-rce-and-console-manipulation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-apache-tomcat-flaws-expose-servers-to-rce-and-console-manipulation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Critical Apache Tomcat Flaws Expose Servers to RCE and Console Hijacking</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Apache Software Foundation has released patches for two critical vulnerabilities, CVE-2025-55752 and CVE-2025-55754, affecting Apache Tomcat versions 9, 10, and 11. The most severe flaw, CVE-2025-55752, is a directory traversal bug that can be escalated to remote code execution (RCE) if non-default settings like PUT requests are enabled. The second flaw could allow for console manipulation on Windows systems. Administrators are urged to upgrade to the latest versions immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Apache has patched two critical vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-55752, CVE-2025-55754) in Tomcat versions 9, 10, and 11 that could lead to directory traversal, RCE, and console manipulation. Upgrade immediately.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> critical-apache-tomcat-flaws-expose-servers-to-rce-and-console-manipulation</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-apache-tomcat-flaws-expose-servers-to-rce-and-console-manipulation/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: North Korea's BlueNoroff APT Targets macOS Users with New 'GhostCall' Malware</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/north-koreas-bluenoroff-apt-deploys-new-macos-malware-in-sophisticated-campaigns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/north-koreas-bluenoroff-apt-deploys-new-macos-malware-in-sophisticated-campaigns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> North Korea's BlueNoroff APT Targets macOS Users with New 'GhostCall' Malware</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The North Korean advanced persistent threat (APT) group BlueNoroff has been linked to two new sophisticated campaigns, 'GhostCall' and 'GhostHire,' which specifically target macOS users. According to Kaspersky, the financially motivated group, a subset of the Lazarus Group, is targeting venture capitalists and Web3 developers with fake Zoom and Microsoft Teams clients, AI-enhanced social engineering, and a new suite of malware designed to steal cryptocurrency. Victims have been identified globally, including in Japan, Italy, France, and Singapore.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Malware, Phishing</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The North Korean APT group BlueNoroff (APT38) is targeting macOS users in the crypto sector with new malware campaigns 'GhostCall' and 'GhostHire,' using sophisticated social engineering to steal cryptocurrency.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> north-koreas-bluenoroff-apt-deploys-new-macos-malware-in-sophisticated-campaigns</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/north-koreas-bluenoroff-apt-deploys-new-macos-malware-in-sophisticated-campaigns/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Ransomware Victim Payments Plummet to Record Low of 23% in Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-payments-hit-historic-low-of-23-percent-in-q3-2025/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-payments-hit-historic-low-of-23-percent-in-q3-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Ransomware Victim Payments Plummet to Record Low of 23% in Q3 2025</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The rate of ransomware victims paying ransoms fell to a record low of 23% in the third quarter of 2025, according to a report from Coveware. This decline is driven by two key factors: large enterprises are increasingly refusing to pay, recognizing the low utility of doing so in data exfiltration cases, and major RaaS groups like Akira and Qilin are shifting their focus to high-volume attacks on mid-market firms with smaller ransom demands. Despite the lower payment rate, the overall volume of ransomware incidents remains at an all-time high.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Intelligence, Ransomware, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Ransomware payment rates dropped to a historic low of 23% in Q3 2025 as large enterprises increasingly refuse to pay and groups like Akira and Qilin target mid-market firms, according to Coveware.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ransomware-payments-hit-historic-low-of-23-percent-in-q3-2025</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-payments-hit-historic-low-of-23-percent-in-q3-2025/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: 183 Million Email Credentials Exposed in Massive Infostealer Malware Leak</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/183-million-email-credentials-exposed-through-infostealer-malware/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/183-million-email-credentials-exposed-through-infostealer-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> 183 Million Email Credentials Exposed in Massive Infostealer Malware Leak</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A massive dataset containing 183 million unique email addresses and their corresponding plaintext passwords has been discovered circulating on the dark web and added to the Have I Been Pwned database. The data, dubbed the "Synthient Stealer Log Threat Data," was not sourced from a breach of any single provider like Gmail, but was compiled from logs harvested by infostealer malware from millions of compromised user devices worldwide. The leak highlights the pervasive threat of infostealers and poses a severe risk of credential stuffing attacks across the internet.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Malware, Phishing</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A huge dataset from infostealer malware logs, containing 183 million unique email addresses and passwords, has been discovered. This was not a direct breach of any service but theft from users' devices, posing a massive credential stuffing risk.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> 183-million-email-credentials-exposed-through-infostealer-malware</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/183-million-email-credentials-exposed-through-infostealer-malware/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: U.S. Coast Guard Poised for 'Generational Change' in Maritime Cybersecurity with $25B Funding</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-coast-guard-receives-billions-in-funding-for-maritime-cybersecurity-overhaul/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-coast-guard-receives-billions-in-funding-for-maritime-cybersecurity-overhaul/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> U.S. Coast Guard Poised for 'Generational Change' in Maritime Cybersecurity with $25B Funding</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Coast Guard (USCG) is set for a 'generational change' in maritime cybersecurity, according to an analysis by the Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS). Nearly $25 billion in new funding, combined with expanded regulatory authorities, will allow the USCG to comprehensively modernize its systems, implement a zero-trust architecture, and enforce new cybersecurity standards across the entire U.S. Marine Transportation System. The move signals a major strategic shift, elevating cyberspace to an operational domain on par with air, land, and sea.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Industrial Control Systems</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> An analysis by CSIS highlights a 'generational change' for the U.S. Coast Guard's cybersecurity capabilities, backed by nearly $25 billion in funding to modernize systems and regulate the maritime industry.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> us-coast-guard-receives-billions-in-funding-for-maritime-cybersecurity-overhaul</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-coast-guard-receives-billions-in-funding-for-maritime-cybersecurity-overhaul/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA Adds Actively Exploited Motex LANSCOPE RCE Flaw to KEV Catalog</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-critical-motex-lanscope-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-critical-motex-lanscope-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Adds Actively Exploited Motex LANSCOPE RCE Flaw to KEV Catalog</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a critical vulnerability in Motex's LANSCOPE Endpoint Manager, CVE-2025-61932, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog following confirmation of active attacks. The flaw, rated 9.3 CVSS, allows for unauthenticated remote code execution on affected endpoints. Attackers have reportedly been weaponizing the vulnerability to install backdoors on victim systems, primarily observed in Japan. Federal agencies are now mandated to patch by November 12, 2025.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA has added CVE-2025-61932, a critical remote code execution vulnerability in Motex's LANSCOPE Endpoint Manager, to its KEV catalog due to active exploitation in the wild.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-adds-critical-motex-lanscope-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-critical-motex-lanscope-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Over-Privileged Active Directory Domain-Join Accounts Create Major Security Risk</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/active-directory-at-risk-from-over-privileged-domain-join-accounts/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/active-directory-at-risk-from-over-privileged-domain-join-accounts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Over-Privileged Active Directory Domain-Join Accounts Create Major Security Risk</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new security analysis reveals that Active Directory (AD) domain-join accounts, even when configured according to official guidance, often inherit excessive privileges that create a reliable pathway for attackers to achieve full domain compromise. These specialized accounts, used for automated machine provisioning, can have their credentials exposed during deployment. Attackers can then abuse the account's powerful default permissions, such as object ownership and rights related to Resource-Based Constrained Delegation (RBCD), to escalate privileges and take over computer objects.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Security Operations, Vulnerability, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A security analysis highlights how over-privileged Active Directory domain-join accounts, whose credentials are often exposed, create a significant risk for privilege escalation and domain compromise via RBCD attacks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> active-directory-at-risk-from-over-privileged-domain-join-accounts</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/active-directory-at-risk-from-over-privileged-domain-join-accounts/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Microsoft Report: AI-Generated Phishing Now 4.5x More Effective, Bypassing Traditional Defenses</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ai-powered-phishing-emails-prove-4-5-times-more-effective-microsoft-report-finds/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ai-powered-phishing-emails-prove-4-5-times-more-effective-microsoft-report-finds/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Microsoft Report: AI-Generated Phishing Now 4.5x More Effective, Bypassing Traditional Defenses</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>According to the Microsoft 2025 Digital Defense Report, the effectiveness of phishing attacks has surged with the adoption of artificial intelligence. AI-generated emails now achieve a 54% click-through rate, 4.5 times higher than traditional methods. The report, covering July 2024 to June 2025, also highlights a 32% increase in identity-based attacks and the growing use of AI by nation-state actors for disinformation. Microsoft stresses that phishing-resistant MFA remains the most effective defense, blocking over 99% of identity attacks.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Phishing, Threat Intelligence, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> AI phishing, Microsoft Digital Defense Report 2025, phishing effectiveness, identity based attacks, phishing resistant MFA, ClickFix attack, cybersecurity trends, generative AI threats</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Microsoft's 2025 Digital Defense Report finds AI-generated phishing emails are 4.5 times more effective, with a 54% click-through rate, fueling a surge in identity-based attacks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ai-powered-phishing-emails-prove-4-5-times-more-effective-microsoft-report-finds</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 2</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 2 updates recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ai-powered-phishing-emails-prove-4-5-times-more-effective-microsoft-report-finds/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 18 Minutes to Mayhem: Ransomware Attacks Now Fully Automated, Slashing Defender Response Time</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-automation-cuts-attack-timelines-to-18-minutes/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-automation-cuts-attack-timelines-to-18-minutes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> 18 Minutes to Mayhem: Ransomware Attacks Now Fully Automated, Slashing Defender Response Time</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new report from ReliaQuest reveals a dramatic acceleration in ransomware attacks, with the average time from initial access to lateral movement ('breakout time') plummeting to just 18 minutes. This is a significant decrease from 48 minutes in 2024, driven by the adoption of automation and AI by 80% of Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) groups. The report highlights the Qilin ransomware gang as a prime example, whose platform automates key attack phases like discovery, backup deletion, and encryption. Other groups like LockBit are also integrating AI to enhance their operations, creating a hyper-competitive landscape where speed and automation are paramount. This shrinking response window poses a monumental challenge for security teams, demanding automated detection and response capabilities to counter the threat.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 7 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Ransomware attacks have accelerated dramatically, with the average time from initial access to lateral movement now just 18 minutes, driven by automation and AI used by groups like Qilin and LockBit.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ransomware-automation-cuts-attack-timelines-to-18-minutes</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-automation-cuts-attack-timelines-to-18-minutes/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Microsoft Scrambles to Patch Actively Exploited Critical WSUS Flaw</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-critical-wsus-flaw-cve-2025-59287/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-critical-wsus-flaw-cve-2025-59287/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Microsoft Scrambles to Patch Actively Exploited Critical WSUS Flaw</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Microsoft has released an urgent, out-of-band security update for a critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in Windows Server Update Services (WSUS), tracked as CVE-2025-59287. The flaw, which has a CVSS score of 9.8, is being actively exploited in the wild, allowing unauthenticated attackers to achieve complete system control with SYSTEM privileges. The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added the vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, mandating immediate patching for federal agencies and strongly urging all organizations to apply the update without delay.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Microsoft releases an emergency out-of-band patch for a critical RCE vulnerability (CVE-2025-59287) in Windows Server Update Services (WSUS) that is under active attack.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-critical-wsus-flaw-cve-2025-59287</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-critical-wsus-flaw-cve-2025-59287/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Qilin Ransomware Attacks Skyrocket, Becoming 2025's Most Prolific Group</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-attacks-skyrocket-to-700-in-2025/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-attacks-skyrocket-to-700-in-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Qilin Ransomware Attacks Skyrocket, Becoming 2025's Most Prolific Group</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Russia-based Qilin ransomware group has become the most active ransomware operation of 2025, claiming 701 victims as of late October. This dramatic surge, representing a 280% increase since April, is largely attributed to the group absorbing affiliates from the defunct RansomHub operation. Qilin employs a double-extortion model, targeting critical infrastructure sectors such as manufacturing, healthcare, finance, and government, with the United States being the most heavily impacted nation. High-profile attacks have resulted in massive data theft and significant financial damages, cementing Qilin's status as a top-tier cyber threat.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Qilin ransomware group has claimed over 700 victims in 2025, making it the most active ransomware operation and targeting critical sectors worldwide.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> qilin-ransomware-attacks-skyrocket-to-700-in-2025</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-attacks-skyrocket-to-700-in-2025/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Massive 'Smishing Triad' Campaign Used 194,000+ Domains to Harvest Data</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-linked-smishing-campaign-used-194000-domains/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-linked-smishing-campaign-used-194000-domains/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Massive 'Smishing Triad' Campaign Used 194,000+ Domains to Harvest Data</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A massive smishing (SMS phishing) campaign attributed to the China-linked 'Smishing Triad' threat group has used over 194,000 malicious domains since the beginning of 2024. The operation, which escalated significantly in April, impersonates trusted entities like the US Postal Service, the IRS, banks, and toll services to trick victims into divulging sensitive personal information, including Social Security numbers. The campaign's infrastructure is designed for rapid turnover to evade detection, with many domains active for less than two days.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Phishing, Threat Actor, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A massive smishing campaign linked to the 'Smishing Triad' has used over 194,000 malicious domains to impersonate postal services, banks, and government agencies to steal sensitive personal information.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> china-linked-smishing-campaign-used-194000-domains</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-linked-smishing-campaign-used-194000-domains/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Critical Adobe Commerce Flaw Under Active Exploitation, CISA Warns</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-adobe-commerce-flaw-cve-2025-54236-under-active-exploitation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-adobe-commerce-flaw-cve-2025-54236-under-active-exploitation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Critical Adobe Commerce Flaw Under Active Exploitation, CISA Warns</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A critical improper input validation vulnerability in Adobe Commerce and Magento, tracked as CVE-2025-54236, is being actively exploited in the wild. Dubbed 'SessionReaper,' the flaw allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to hijack user sessions via the REST API, leading to potential web shell deployment and complete store takeover. CISA has added the vulnerability to its KEV catalog, and with reports suggesting over 60% of Magento stores remain unpatched, immediate action is urged for all administrators.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Cyberattack, Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A critical session hijacking vulnerability (CVE-2025-54236) in Adobe Commerce and Magento is under active exploitation, allowing attackers to deploy web shells. CISA has added it to the KEV catalog.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> critical-adobe-commerce-flaw-cve-2025-54236-under-active-exploitation</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-adobe-commerce-flaw-cve-2025-54236-under-active-exploitation/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Lazarus Group Targets European Defense Firms with New 'ScoringMathTea' RAT</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/north-korean-lazarus-group-targets-european-defense-firms-with-new-rat/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/north-korean-lazarus-group-targets-european-defense-firms-with-new-rat/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Lazarus Group Targets European Defense Firms with New 'ScoringMathTea' RAT</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The North Korean state-sponsored threat actor, Lazarus Group, is behind a sophisticated cyber-espionage campaign targeting European defense manufacturers, with a specific focus on companies producing Unmanned Aerial Vehicles (UAVs). The attackers used social engineering tactics, including fake job offers and trojanized GitHub projects, to gain initial access. Once inside, they deployed a previously unknown Remote Access Trojan (RAT) named 'ScoringMathTea' to exfiltrate sensitive intellectual property, including proprietary drone designs.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Cyberattack, Industrial Control Systems</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The North Korea-linked Lazarus group is targeting European defense manufacturers with a new remote access trojan (RAT) called ScoringMathTea to steal proprietary UAV designs.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> north-korean-lazarus-group-targets-european-defense-firms-with-new-rat</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/north-korean-lazarus-group-targets-european-defense-firms-with-new-rat/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: ChatGPT Flaw Allows 'Memory Poisoning' via CSRF Attack</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/chatgpt-atlas-browser-vulnerability-allows-memory-poisoning/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/chatgpt-atlas-browser-vulnerability-allows-memory-poisoning/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> ChatGPT Flaw Allows 'Memory Poisoning' via CSRF Attack</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A novel vulnerability discovered in OpenAI's ChatGPT Atlas web browser allows attackers to perform 'memory poisoning' through a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack. Researchers at LayerX Security found that this flaw can be used to invisibly inject malicious instructions into ChatGPT's persistent 'Memory' feature. These instructions survive across sessions and devices, and can be triggered by a user's normal prompts to execute malicious code, potentially leading to account takeover or malware deployment.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A CSRF vulnerability in OpenAI's ChatGPT Atlas web browser allows attackers to inject malicious instructions into the AI's persistent memory, leading to potential account takeover.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> chatgpt-atlas-browser-vulnerability-allows-memory-poisoning</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/chatgpt-atlas-browser-vulnerability-allows-memory-poisoning/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: APT-C-60 Escalates 'SpyGlace' Campaign Against Japan</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apt-c-60-intensifies-cyber-espionage-campaign-against-japan/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apt-c-60-intensifies-cyber-espionage-campaign-against-japan/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> APT-C-60 Escalates 'SpyGlace' Campaign Against Japan</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The South Korea-aligned cyber-espionage group APT-C-60 has significantly intensified its campaign against Japanese organizations in the third quarter of 2025. According to JPCERT/CC and Cyble, the group has deployed at least three new versions of its custom 'SpyGlace' backdoor. The attackers have evolved their tactics, now attaching malicious VHDX files directly to phishing emails and abusing legitimate services like GitHub and StatCounter for stealthy command-and-control communications and malware delivery, making detection more challenging.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Cyberattack, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The South Korea-aligned cyber-espionage group APT-C-60 has escalated its attacks against Japanese organizations, deploying updated versions of its 'SpyGlace' backdoor with enhanced evasion techniques.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> apt-c-60-intensifies-cyber-espionage-campaign-against-japan</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apt-c-60-intensifies-cyber-espionage-campaign-against-japan/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Google Rushes Patch for Critical Chrome V8 RCE Flaw</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-google-chrome-v8-vulnerability-cve-2025-12036-allows-rce/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-google-chrome-v8-vulnerability-cve-2025-12036-allows-rce/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Google Rushes Patch for Critical Chrome V8 RCE Flaw</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Google has released an emergency security update for Google Chrome to address a critical vulnerability, CVE-2025-12036, in its V8 JavaScript engine. The flaw, described as an 'inappropriate implementation,' could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on a victim's system by convincing them to visit a malicious website. The vulnerability was discovered by Google's own AI-driven research project, leading to a rapid patch release. All users of Chrome and other Chromium-based browsers are urged to update immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 3 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Google has issued an emergency security update for a critical remote code execution vulnerability (CVE-2025-12036) in the Chrome V8 JavaScript engine, affecting Chrome and other Chromium-based browsers.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> critical-google-chrome-v8-vulnerability-cve-2025-12036-allows-rce</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-google-chrome-v8-vulnerability-cve-2025-12036-allows-rce/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Data Breaches Hit Toys 'R' Us Canada, Askul, and Verisure</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/data-breaches-hit-toys-r-us-askul-verisure/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/data-breaches-hit-toys-r-us-askul-verisure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Data Breaches Hit Toys 'R' Us Canada, Askul, and Verisure</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A wave of data breaches has impacted several consumer-facing companies globally. Toys "R" Us Canada has had customer records leaked on the dark web. Japanese retailer Askul suffered a disruptive ransomware attack that halted operations and may have resulted in a data leak. Additionally, Swedish security firm Verisure disclosed a breach affecting 35,000 customers via a third-party vendor, and U.S.-based Jewett-Cameron Trading reported the theft of financial documents.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Ransomware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Several consumer-facing companies including Toys 'R' Us Canada, Japanese retailer Askul, and Swedish security firm Verisure have disclosed data breaches, resulting in the theft of customer personal information.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> data-breaches-hit-toys-r-us-askul-verisure</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/data-breaches-hit-toys-r-us-askul-verisure/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Healthcare Sector Rocked by Breaches at ModMed, LifeBridge, and Right at Home</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/healthcare-data-breaches-affect-modmed-lifebridge-right-at-home/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/healthcare-data-breaches-affect-modmed-lifebridge-right-at-home/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Healthcare Sector Rocked by Breaches at ModMed, LifeBridge, and Right at Home</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The healthcare sector continues to be a prime target for cyberattacks, with recent data breaches announced by Electronic Health Record (EHR) provider Modernizing Medicine (ModMed), home healthcare provider Right at Home, and Baltimore-based LifeBridge Health. The incidents, which include a ransomware attack claimed by the Sinobi group and a third-party breach via Oracle Health, have exposed a vast range of sensitive Protected Health Information (PHI), including Social Security numbers, medical diagnoses, and financial data.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Ransomware, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Data breaches have been announced by EHR provider Modernizing Medicine (ModMed), LifeBridge Health, and home healthcare provider Right at Home, exposing a wide range of patient and financial data.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> healthcare-data-breaches-affect-modmed-lifebridge-right-at-home</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/healthcare-data-breaches-affect-modmed-lifebridge-right-at-home/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Ransomware Attacks Surge 50% in 2025; Qilin Group Takes the Lead</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-attacks-skyrocket-50-percent-in-2025-qilin-emerges-as-leader/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-attacks-skyrocket-50-percent-in-2025-qilin-emerges-as-leader/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Ransomware Attacks Surge 50% in 2025; Qilin Group Takes the Lead</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Cybersecurity researchers report a staggering 50% increase in ransomware attacks in 2025, with over 5,000 incidents claimed on dark web leak sites by late October. This surge occurs amidst a significant realignment in the ransomware ecosystem, with formerly dominant groups fading while new and resurgent actors like Qilin take their place. The Qilin group has been particularly prolific, leading in victim counts for most of the past six months. The United States remains the most targeted nation, and the industrial sector is the most heavily impacted industry. PowerShell has become the primary tool for attackers, used in nearly 78% of observed campaigns.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A 50% surge in ransomware attacks is reported for 2025, with the Qilin group emerging as a dominant threat actor. The industrial sector is the most targeted, and PowerShell is the primary attack vector.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ransomware-attacks-skyrocket-50-percent-in-2025-qilin-emerges-as-leader</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-attacks-skyrocket-50-percent-in-2025-qilin-emerges-as-leader/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>