<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 21:09:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Washington Post Breached by Clop Ransomware via Oracle Flaws</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/washington-post-confirms-breach-in-massive-oracle-software-attack/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/washington-post-confirms-breach-in-massive-oracle-software-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Washington Post Breached by Clop Ransomware via Oracle Flaws</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Washington Post has officially confirmed it was a victim of a large-scale cyberattack orchestrated by the Clop ransomware group. The threat actors exploited vulnerabilities in Oracle's E-Business Suite, compromising over 100 organizations globally. The campaign involves data exfiltration followed by aggressive extortion tactics, with Clop publicly naming victims on its dark web leak site to pressure them into paying ransoms reportedly as high as $50 million. This incident underscores the significant risk posed by vulnerabilities in widely used enterprise software and the sophisticated, multi-faceted extortion methods employed by modern ransomware gangs.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Clop ransomware, Washington Post breach, Oracle E-Business Suite vulnerability, data extortion, cyberattack, TA505, ransomware campaign</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Clop ransomware group has breached The Washington Post and over 100 other organizations by exploiting vulnerabilities in Oracle's E-Business Suite, leading to massive data theft and extortion.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> washington-post-confirms-breach-in-massive-oracle-software-attack</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/washington-post-confirms-breach-in-massive-oracle-software-attack/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Microsoft 'Whisper Leak' Attack Can Spy on Encrypted AI Chats</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-reveals-whisper-leak-attack-infers-ai-chat-topics-from-encrypted-traffic/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-reveals-whisper-leak-attack-infers-ai-chat-topics-from-encrypted-traffic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Microsoft 'Whisper Leak' Attack Can Spy on Encrypted AI Chats</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Microsoft researchers have discovered a novel side-channel attack method named 'Whisper Leak' that undermines the privacy of encrypted AI chatbot conversations. By analyzing the size and timing of encrypted data packets from streaming Large Language Models (LLMs), a passive network observer can accurately infer the topic of a conversation. The proof-of-concept attack achieved over 98% accuracy against models from OpenAI, Mistral, xAI, and DeepSeek. While major AI providers have already implemented mitigations following a responsible disclosure, the finding exposes a fundamental privacy risk in the architecture of streaming LLMs, particularly for users in sensitive sectors like law and healthcare.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Threat Intelligence, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> TechArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Whisper Leak, AI privacy, side-channel attack, LLM security, encrypted traffic analysis, Microsoft, OpenAI</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Microsoft researchers detail 'Whisper Leak,' a new side-channel attack that can infer the topic of encrypted AI chat sessions by analyzing network traffic patterns, posing a major privacy risk.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> microsoft-reveals-whisper-leak-attack-infers-ai-chat-topics-from-encrypted-traffic</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-reveals-whisper-leak-attack-infers-ai-chat-topics-from-encrypted-traffic/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: GlassWorm Malware Hits VSCode Marketplace, Stealing Dev Credentials</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/glassworm-malware-returns-in-vscode-marketplace-supply-chain-attack/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/glassworm-malware-returns-in-vscode-marketplace-supply-chain-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> GlassWorm Malware Hits VSCode Marketplace, Stealing Dev Credentials</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The financially motivated GlassWorm malware campaign has returned, targeting developers through the OpenVSX marketplace for Visual Studio Code. Security researchers discovered three malicious VSCode extensions published on November 8, 2025, which have already been downloaded over 10,000 times. The malware is designed to steal developer credentials, including GitHub and NPM tokens, and exfiltrate data from 49 different cryptocurrency wallet extensions. In a novel twist, the malware uses Solana blockchain transactions to fetch its malicious payload, complicating detection and takedown efforts. The extensions remain active, posing an ongoing threat to the software development community.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Supply Chain Attack, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> GlassWorm malware, VSCode extension attack, OpenVSX security, software supply chain, developer credential theft, Solana C2</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The GlassWorm malware has returned in a supply chain attack, using malicious Visual Studio Code extensions on the OpenVSX marketplace to steal developer credentials and cryptocurrency.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> glassworm-malware-returns-in-vscode-marketplace-supply-chain-attack</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/glassworm-malware-returns-in-vscode-marketplace-supply-chain-attack/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: QNAP Patches 7 Zero-Days Allowing Full NAS Takeover</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qnap-patches-seven-zero-day-vulnerabilities-from-pwn2own-2025/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qnap-patches-seven-zero-day-vulnerabilities-from-pwn2own-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> QNAP Patches 7 Zero-Days Allowing Full NAS Takeover</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>QNAP has issued urgent security updates to address seven zero-day vulnerabilities affecting its QTS, QuTS hero, and related software. These critical flaws were successfully exploited by security researchers at the Pwn2Own Ireland 2025 hacking contest in October, demonstrating paths to unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE) and full system takeover. The vulnerabilities, including buffer overflows and path traversal issues, impact the NAS operating systems as well as integrated applications like HBS 3 Hybrid Backup Sync and Malware Remover. QNAP users are strongly urged to apply the patches immediately to protect their data from potential attack.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> QNAP zero-day, Pwn2Own 2025, QNAP vulnerability, CVE-2025-62847, NAS security, remote code execution</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> QNAP has patched seven critical zero-day vulnerabilities in its NAS operating systems (QTS, QuTS hero) that allow for remote code execution, following their exploitation at Pwn2Own 2025.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> qnap-patches-seven-zero-day-vulnerabilities-from-pwn2own-2025</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qnap-patches-seven-zero-day-vulnerabilities-from-pwn2own-2025/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Chinese-Made Electric Buses in Europe &amp; Australia Pose Remote Shutdown Risk</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/security-risk-found-in-chinese-made-electric-buses-across-europe-australia/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/security-risk-found-in-chinese-made-electric-buses-across-europe-australia/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Chinese-Made Electric Buses in Europe &amp; Australia Pose Remote Shutdown Risk</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Cybersecurity tests conducted in Norway on November 7, 2025, have uncovered a significant security risk in Chinese-manufactured Yutong electric buses, which are widely used across Europe and Australia. The 'Lion Cage' experiment demonstrated that the buses' connected systems could theoretically be accessed and disabled remotely by the manufacturer. The findings have triggered urgent security reviews by public transit authorities in multiple countries, highlighting the growing national security concerns surrounding internet-connected critical infrastructure and potential vulnerabilities in international supply chains.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Industrial Control Systems, Cyberattack, Supply Chain Attack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Yutong electric bus, cybersecurity, critical infrastructure, remote shutdown, Norway, supply chain risk, connected vehicle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Cybersecurity tests in Norway show that Chinese-made Yutong electric buses, used widely in Europe and Australia, could be remotely disabled, raising major national security concerns.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> security-risk-found-in-chinese-made-electric-buses-across-europe-australia</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/security-risk-found-in-chinese-made-electric-buses-across-europe-australia/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Accenture Report: 90% of Firms Unprepared for AI-Powered Cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/only-10-percent-of-firms-ready-for-ai-powered-cyberattacks-accenture-report/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/only-10-percent-of-firms-ready-for-ai-powered-cyberattacks-accenture-report/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Accenture Report: 90% of Firms Unprepared for AI-Powered Cyberattacks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new report from Accenture, 'State of Cybersecurity Resilience 2025,' reveals a critical gap in corporate defenses against AI-augmented cyberattacks. The study, surveying over 2,200 executives, found that only 10% of organizations are 'Reinvention Ready' with adaptive and resilient security postures. A concerning 63% are in the 'Exposed Zone,' relying on reactive and insufficient defenses. The report highlights that AI adoption is rapidly outpacing security implementation, with 77% of firms lacking the necessary security practices to protect their AI models and data pipelines, creating a significant and growing business risk.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Threat Intelligence, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Accenture report, AI cyberattacks, cybersecurity resilience, AI security, generative AI risk, security governance</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Accenture's 'State of Cybersecurity Resilience 2025' report finds 90% of organizations are unprepared for AI-driven cyberattacks, with most operating with reactive and fragmented defenses.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> only-10-percent-of-firms-ready-for-ai-powered-cyberattacks-accenture-report</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/only-10-percent-of-firms-ready-for-ai-powered-cyberattacks-accenture-report/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Indian MP Proposes National Council to Standardize Cybersecurity Certifications</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/indian-mp-urges-government-to-create-national-cybersecurity-certification-council/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/indian-mp-urges-government-to-create-national-cybersecurity-certification-council/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Indian MP Proposes National Council to Standardize Cybersecurity Certifications</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>On November 9, 2025, Indian MP Praveen Khandelwal formally requested that the central government establish a National Cybersecurity Certification Council. The proposal aims to standardize cybersecurity education and professional certifications across India to address the growing talent gap and combat a recent surge in cyber fraud and data breaches. By promoting globally recognized certifications like CEH and CCISO, the council would seek to build a skilled workforce, enhance national cyber defense capabilities, and support the 'Digital India' initiative.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Other</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> National Cybersecurity Certification Council, India cybersecurity, Praveen Khandelwal, cybersecurity education, Digital India</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> An Indian MP has formally proposed the creation of a National Cybersecurity Certification Council to standardize cybersecurity education and certifications to combat rising cybercrime.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> indian-mp-urges-government-to-create-national-cybersecurity-certification-council</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/indian-mp-urges-government-to-create-national-cybersecurity-certification-council/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Other</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Philippines Lawmakers Push for National Cybersecurity Fund</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/philippines-lawmakers-propose-dedicated-national-cybersecurity-fund/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/philippines-lawmakers-propose-dedicated-national-cybersecurity-fund/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Philippines Lawmakers Push for National Cybersecurity Fund</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>In the Philippines, Representatives Migz and Luigi Villafuerte have introduced a proposal to create a 'Cybersecurity Risk Management and Mitigation Fund' (CRMMF). This dedicated national fund would provide the government with the necessary resources to prevent and respond to cyberattacks against both public and private sector entities. The proposal comes after recent DDoS attack attempts on local banks and designates 30% of the fund for rapid restoration of critical information infrastructure, signaling a strong political push to enhance the nation's cyber resilience.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Incident Response</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Philippines cybersecurity, Cybersecurity Risk Management and Mitigation Fund, CRMMF, Villafuerte, DICT Philippines</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Lawmakers in the Philippines have proposed a dedicated national Cybersecurity Risk Management and Mitigation Fund to finance prevention and response to cyberattacks on government and businesses.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> philippines-lawmakers-propose-dedicated-national-cybersecurity-fund</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/philippines-lawmakers-propose-dedicated-national-cybersecurity-fund/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Incident Response</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Microsoft Warns of 'Payroll Pirates' Phishing Gang Targeting M365 Credentials</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-warns-of-payroll-pirates-phishing-campaign/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-warns-of-payroll-pirates-phishing-campaign/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Microsoft Warns of 'Payroll Pirates' Phishing Gang Targeting M365 Credentials</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Microsoft has issued a warning about a sophisticated phishing campaign dubbed 'Payroll Pirates.' The attackers impersonate HR departments in targeted emails to lure employees into giving up their Microsoft 365 credentials. The campaign uses spoofed domains and legitimate Microsoft Forms to appear authentic. The ultimate goal of the operation is to gain access to employee accounts, alter their direct deposit information, and divert their payroll to attacker-controlled bank accounts. This form of Business Email Compromise (BEC) attack poses a direct financial threat to employees, and Microsoft urges organizations to enable multi-factor authentication as a key defense.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Phishing, Threat Actor, Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Payroll Pirates, phishing campaign, Microsoft 365 security, BEC attack, payroll diversion, MFA</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Microsoft is warning about a new 'Payroll Pirates' phishing campaign where attackers impersonate HR departments to steal Microsoft 365 credentials and reroute employee payroll.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> microsoft-warns-of-payroll-pirates-phishing-campaign</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-warns-of-payroll-pirates-phishing-campaign/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Critical Container Escape Flaws in runC Threaten Docker &amp; Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-flaws-in-runc-container-runtime-threaten-docker-kubernetes/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-flaws-in-runc-container-runtime-threaten-docker-kubernetes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Critical Container Escape Flaws in runC Threaten Docker &amp; Kubernetes</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A security alert issued on November 9, 2025, warns of three new critical vulnerabilities in runC, the low-level container runtime used by Docker, Kubernetes, and other major container platforms. The flaws could allow a malicious actor to execute a 'container escape,' breaking out of the isolated container environment to gain unauthorized access to the underlying host operating system. A successful container escape is a worst-case scenario in cloud-native security, as it would allow an attacker to compromise all other containers on the host. Administrators of all containerized environments are urged to monitor for and apply patches immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Cloud Security, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> TechArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> runC vulnerability, container escape, Docker security, Kubernetes security, cloud native security, CVE</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Three critical new vulnerabilities have been found in runC, the core container runtime for Docker and Kubernetes, which could allow attackers to escape container isolation and access the host OS.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> critical-flaws-in-runc-container-runtime-threaten-docker-kubernetes</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-flaws-in-runc-container-runtime-threaten-docker-kubernetes/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Over 75% of Orgs Can't Keep Pace with AI-Powered Attacks, Survey Finds</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/76-percent-of-orgs-cant-match-speed-of-ai-powered-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/76-percent-of-orgs-cant-match-speed-of-ai-powered-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Over 75% of Orgs Can't Keep Pace with AI-Powered Attacks, Survey Finds</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new survey from CrowdStrike reveals a stark reality: 76% of global organizations admit they cannot match the speed and sophistication of AI-powered cyberattacks. The 2025 State of Ransomware Survey highlights a dangerous 'confidence illusion,' where leaders believe they are prepared, yet 78% of their organizations were attacked in the past year. With adversaries using AI to accelerate attacks, 89% of security leaders now agree that AI-powered protection is essential to close the widening security gap and defend against modern threats.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Intelligence, Ransomware, Policy and Compliance</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A CrowdStrike survey reveals 76% of organizations struggle to match the speed of AI-powered attacks, highlighting a 'confidence illusion' among leaders and the urgent need for AI-driven cyber defenses.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> 76-percent-of-orgs-cant-match-speed-of-ai-powered-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/76-percent-of-orgs-cant-match-speed-of-ai-powered-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Pwn2Own Day 1: Hackers Net $522K for 34 Zero-Days in SOHO Devices</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pwn2own-ireland-day-1-hackers-earn-522k-for-34-zero-days/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pwn2own-ireland-day-1-hackers-earn-522k-for-34-zero-days/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Pwn2Own Day 1: Hackers Net $522K for 34 Zero-Days in SOHO Devices</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The first day of Trend Micro's Pwn2Own Ireland 2025 competition was a resounding success for security researchers, who earned a total of $522,500 for demonstrating 34 unique zero-day vulnerabilities. In a stunning display, every single one of the 17 scheduled attempts against popular SOHO devices—including printers, NAS devices, and smart home products from brands like QNAP, Synology, Canon, and HP—was successful. The highlight was a complex 'SOHO Smashup' that chained eight bugs to compromise a router and a NAS device.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, IoT Security, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> On Day 1 of Pwn2Own Ireland 2025, security researchers earned $522,500 by demonstrating 34 zero-day vulnerabilities against popular SOHO devices from QNAP, Synology, Canon, and HP with a 100% success rate.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> pwn2own-ireland-day-1-hackers-earn-522k-for-34-zero-days</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pwn2own-ireland-day-1-hackers-earn-522k-for-34-zero-days/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>IoT Security</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: LANDFALL Spyware Uses Samsung Zero-Day for Zero-Click Attacks in Middle East</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/landfall-spyware-exploits-samsung-zero-day-in-middle-east-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/landfall-spyware-exploits-samsung-zero-day-in-middle-east-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> LANDFALL Spyware Uses Samsung Zero-Day for Zero-Click Attacks in Middle East</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A sophisticated commercial-grade Android spyware known as LANDFALL has been identified in targeted cyber-espionage campaigns across the Middle East. The attackers exploited a critical zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2025-21042, in Samsung Galaxy devices to achieve remote code execution without user interaction. The flaw, an out-of-bounds write in an image processing library, was triggered by sending a malicious DNG image file. The campaign was active for months before Samsung issued a patch in April 2025, affecting users in Iraq, Iran, Turkey, and Morocco. Once installed, LANDFALL acts as a comprehensive surveillance tool, capable of exfiltrating a wide array of data, including microphone recordings, location data, photos, and communications.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Malware, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> LANDFALL spyware, CVE-2025-21042, Samsung zero-day, Android security, zero-click exploit, Middle East cyber attack, mobile spyware, Unit 42, libimagecodec.quram.so</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Learn about the LANDFALL spyware campaign that used a critical Samsung zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2025-21042, to conduct zero-click attacks against targets in the Middle East. Discover the technical details, impact, and mitigation steps.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> landfall-spyware-exploits-samsung-zero-day-in-middle-east-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/landfall-spyware-exploits-samsung-zero-day-in-middle-east-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Sandworm Escalates Wiper Attacks, Targeting Ukraine's Grain Sector for First Time</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/russian-apt-sandworm-intensifies-destructive-attacks-on-ukraine/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/russian-apt-sandworm-intensifies-destructive-attacks-on-ukraine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Sandworm Escalates Wiper Attacks, Targeting Ukraine's Grain Sector for First Time</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new report from ESET covering APT activity from April to September 2025 reveals that the Russia-linked threat group Sandworm has escalated its destructive cyberattacks against Ukraine. The group deployed new data-wiping malware, including Zerolot and Sting, targeting government bodies, energy companies, and logistics. In a significant strategic shift, Sandworm's attacks have expanded to include Ukraine's grain export sector, a vital part of its economy. The report also notes that another group, UAC-0099, has been observed supporting Sandworm by providing initial access to victim networks. This campaign is part of a broader increase in global state-sponsored cyber activity, with groups from China, Iran, and North Korea also expanding their espionage and disruptive operations.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Cyberattack, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Sandworm, ESET report, Ukraine cyber attack, wiper malware, Zerolot, Sting, Russian hackers, APT activity, grain sector</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> ESET's latest report reveals Russia's Sandworm group is intensifying cyberattacks on Ukraine, using new wiper malware like Zerolot and Sting to target the energy, government, and, for the first time, grain sectors.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> russian-apt-sandworm-intensifies-destructive-attacks-on-ukraine</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/russian-apt-sandworm-intensifies-destructive-attacks-on-ukraine/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Software Supply Chain Attacks Surge Over 30% to Record High, Driven by Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/software-supply-chain-attacks-hit-record-high-in-october-2025/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/software-supply-chain-attacks-hit-record-high-in-october-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Software Supply Chain Attacks Surge Over 30% to Record High, Driven by Ransomware</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>According to a new report from threat intelligence firm Cyble, software supply chain attacks surged to a record high in October 2025, with 41 documented incidents. This represents a 30% increase from the previous peak and more than double the monthly average from early 2024. Ransomware groups, notably Qilin and Akira, are increasingly adopting this tactic, shifting focus from direct network breaches to compromising organizations through their third-party technology partners. The attacks have heavily targeted the energy, healthcare, and manufacturing sectors. Incidents include Qilin compromising a cloud services provider for the healthcare sector by finding clear-text credentials, demonstrating the critical need for improved vendor risk management.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Ransomware, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> software supply chain attack, Cyble, Qilin ransomware, Akira ransomware, third-party risk management, cybersecurity report, October 2025, vendor risk</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A Cyble report reveals a record-breaking surge in software supply chain attacks in October 2025, with ransomware groups like Qilin and Akira leading the charge. Learn about the targeted sectors and mitigation strategies.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> software-supply-chain-attacks-hit-record-high-in-october-2025</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/software-supply-chain-attacks-hit-record-high-in-october-2025/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Qilin Ransomware Gang Claims 7 of 11 New Victims in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/daily-ransomware-report-qilin-gang-dominates-november-8-2025/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/daily-ransomware-report-qilin-gang-dominates-november-8-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Qilin Ransomware Gang Claims 7 of 11 New Victims in 24 Hours</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The daily ransomware report for November 8, 2025, highlights a significant burst of activity from the Qilin ransomware group, which claimed responsibility for 7 of the 11 new victims announced in the past 24 hours. The DragonForce group was the second most active with three victims. The attacks primarily targeted the professional services and manufacturing sectors, with victims located in the United States, Canada, and the United Kingdom. This latest surge brings the total number of publicly claimed ransomware victims in 2025 to 6,364, underscoring the relentless and persistent threat that ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) operations pose to organizations globally.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Qilin ransomware, daily ransomware report, DragonForce, ransomware victims, professional services, manufacturing, cyber attacks</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Daily ransomware report for November 8, 2025, shows the Qilin ransomware group is highly active, responsible for 7 of 11 new victims. The professional services and manufacturing sectors are the primary targets.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> daily-ransomware-report-qilin-gang-dominates-november-8-2025</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/daily-ransomware-report-qilin-gang-dominates-november-8-2025/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: SonicWall: State-Sponsored Actor Breached Cloud Backups via API Exploit</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sonicwall-confirms-state-sponsored-actor-behind-cloud-backup-breach/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sonicwall-confirms-state-sponsored-actor-behind-cloud-backup-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> SonicWall: State-Sponsored Actor Breached Cloud Backups via API Exploit</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Cybersecurity vendor SonicWall has confirmed that a sophisticated state-sponsored threat actor was behind the security breach in September 2025. The investigation, assisted by Mandiant, found that the attackers gained unauthorized access to a cloud environment by exploiting a compromised API call. This allowed them to steal firewall configuration backup files belonging to customers of the MySonicWall cloud backup service. SonicWall asserts that the incident was isolated to that specific environment and did not affect its core products or internal networks. The company has since implemented remedial actions and released tools to help customers reset credentials and secure their services.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Cloud Security, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> SonicWall breach, state-sponsored hackers, MySonicWall, API security, cloud backup breach, Mandiant, cybersecurity incident</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> SonicWall confirms a state-sponsored actor was behind a September 2025 breach, exploiting an API to steal customer firewall configuration backups from the MySonicWall cloud service. Learn about the impact and response.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> sonicwall-confirms-state-sponsored-actor-behind-cloud-backup-breach</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sonicwall-confirms-state-sponsored-actor-behind-cloud-backup-breach/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Malicious VS Code Extension with Ransomware Capabilities Discovered on Official Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/malicious-vs-code-extension-with-ransomware-found-on-marketplace/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/malicious-vs-code-extension-with-ransomware-found-on-marketplace/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Malicious VS Code Extension with Ransomware Capabilities Discovered on Official Marketplace</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A malicious Visual Studio (VS) Code extension named "susvsex" was discovered on the official VS Code Extension Marketplace. The extension, which appears to have been created with AI assistance, contained overt ransomware capabilities. Upon activation, it was designed to archive a target directory, exfiltrate the ZIP file to a remote server, and then encrypt the original files. The extension also used a private GitHub repository as a command-and-control channel. Although its default target was a test folder, it could easily be modified to target sensitive user data. Microsoft has since removed the extension, which was published on November 5, 2025.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Supply Chain Attack, Ransomware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> VS Code extension, malicious extension, susvsex, ransomware, developer security, Visual Studio Code marketplace, AI generated malware</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A malicious Visual Studio Code extension, 'susvsex', was found on the official marketplace with ransomware capabilities. Learn how it worked, the risks to developers, and how to mitigate this threat vector.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> malicious-vs-code-extension-with-ransomware-found-on-marketplace</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/malicious-vs-code-extension-with-ransomware-found-on-marketplace/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: UAE Issues Public Warning on Misinformation Risks from AI Deepfakes</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uae-cybersecurity-council-warns-public-on-deepfake-dangers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uae-cybersecurity-council-warns-public-on-deepfake-dangers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> UAE Issues Public Warning on Misinformation Risks from AI Deepfakes</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The UAE Cybersecurity Council issued a formal public warning on November 7, 2025, about the escalating threat posed by AI-generated "deepfake" content. The advisory highlights the potential for highly realistic but fraudulent videos and audio clips to be used for spreading misinformation, committing fraud, and damaging the reputations of individuals and institutions. The council emphasized that public awareness is the primary defense and urged citizens to verify information from official sources before sharing. The warning also referenced Federal Decree-Law No. (34) of 2021, which criminalizes the creation and distribution of such content.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> UAE deepfake, AI warning, Cybersecurity Council, misinformation, digital fraud, cybercrime law UAE, deepfake video</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The UAE Cybersecurity Council issues a formal warning to the public about the increasing threat of AI-generated deepfake videos and audio, highlighting risks of misinformation and fraud.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> uae-cybersecurity-council-warns-public-on-deepfake-dangers</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uae-cybersecurity-council-warns-public-on-deepfake-dangers/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Data of Nearly 200,000 Supporters of Hungarian Party TISZA Leaked Online</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/hungarian-political-party-tisza-suffers-major-data-breach/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/hungarian-political-party-tisza-suffers-major-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Data of Nearly 200,000 Supporters of Hungarian Party TISZA Leaked Online</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The personal data of nearly 200,000 supporters of the Hungarian political party TISZA has been leaked and is being widely distributed online. The breach, which occurred in October 2025, originated from the party's "TISZA Világ" service. The compromised dataset, containing 198,500 records, has been added to the Have I Been Pwned service. Exposed information includes supporters' full names, email addresses, phone numbers, physical addresses, and usernames. This incident places affected individuals at significant risk of phishing, fraud, and other malicious targeting.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> TISZA data breach, Hungarian political party, Have I Been Pwned, PII leak, cybersecurity Hungary, TISZA Világ</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A major data breach at the Hungarian political party TISZA has exposed the personal data of 198,500 supporters, including names, emails, and addresses. The incident has been added to Have I Been Pwned.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> hungarian-political-party-tisza-suffers-major-data-breach</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/hungarian-political-party-tisza-suffers-major-data-breach/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: EU Strengthens Digital Rulebook with New GDPR Enforcement and DSA Measures</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/eu-advances-digital-regulation-with-new-gdpr-and-dsa-enforcement/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/eu-advances-digital-regulation-with-new-gdpr-and-dsa-enforcement/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> EU Strengthens Digital Rulebook with New GDPR Enforcement and DSA Measures</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The European Union has taken several steps to strengthen its digital regulatory environment. New rules have been passed to harmonize the enforcement of GDPR in cross-border cases. A new regulation on political advertising has also entered into force, imposing transparency requirements on online platforms and banning certain types of ad targeting. Additionally, the European Commission has issued a Cloud Sovereignty Framework and is advancing enforcement actions under the Digital Services Act (DSA), including issuing preliminary findings that Meta and TikTok may have breached DSA obligations regarding researcher access to data.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Regulatory, Policy and Compliance</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> EU digital regulation, GDPR enforcement, Digital Services Act, DSA, political advertising, cloud sovereignty, Meta, TikTok</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The EU strengthens its digital regulations with new rules for cross-border GDPR enforcement, a law for transparent political advertising, and enforcement actions under the Digital Services Act (DSA).</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> eu-advances-digital-regulation-with-new-gdpr-and-dsa-enforcement</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/eu-advances-digital-regulation-with-new-gdpr-and-dsa-enforcement/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Bahrain Fosters Digital Talent with AI and Cybersecurity Partnership</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/bahrain-polytechnic-and-beyon-cyber-partner-on-ai-and-cybersecurity/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/bahrain-polytechnic-and-beyon-cyber-partner-on-ai-and-cybersecurity/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Bahrain Fosters Digital Talent with AI and Cybersecurity Partnership</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Bahrain is strengthening its national digital capabilities through a new partnership between Beyon Cyber, a cybersecurity firm, and Bahrain Polytechnic. The two organizations signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to foster innovation in Artificial Intelligence and cybersecurity. The collaboration aims to develop advanced, AI-driven security solutions and cultivate a skilled local workforce. This strategic initiative is aligned with Bahrain's goal of becoming a regional leader in technology and equipping its next generation of professionals with the skills to tackle modern cybersecurity challenges.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Security Operations, Other</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Beyon Cyber, Bahrain Polytechnic, cybersecurity Bahrain, AI innovation, digital talent, MoU</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 3 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Beyon Cyber and Bahrain Polytechnic have signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to collaborate on AI and cybersecurity innovation, aiming to develop advanced security solutions and a skilled digital workforce in Bahrain.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> bahrain-polytechnic-and-beyon-cyber-partner-on-ai-and-cybersecurity</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/bahrain-polytechnic-and-beyon-cyber-partner-on-ai-and-cybersecurity/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
      <category>Other</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Qilin Ransomware Strikes Again, Claiming Victims Across US, France, and Africa</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-gang-claims-new-attacks-across-us-france-africa/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-gang-claims-new-attacks-across-us-france-africa/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Qilin Ransomware Strikes Again, Claiming Victims Across US, France, and Africa</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Qilin ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) group has had a highly active month, listing numerous new victims on its data leak site. The group has claimed responsibility for attacks against a wide range of organizations in the U.S., France, and Africa. Victims include insurance providers, healthcare authorities, real estate firms, and French municipalities. This follows recent high-profile claims against two Texas electric cooperatives and Volkswagen Group Finance, demonstrating the group's broad targeting and operational capability, supported by resilient bulletproof hosting infrastructure.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Qilin ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) group has claimed responsibility for a flurry of new attacks, listing victims in the US, France, and Africa from sectors including insurance, healthcare, and utilities.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> qilin-ransomware-gang-claims-new-attacks-across-us-france-africa</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 12:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-gang-claims-new-attacks-across-us-france-africa/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Cl0p Gang Exploits Oracle EBS Zero-Day in Massive Data Theft Spree</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/clop-ransomware-exploits-oracle-e-business-suite-zero-day-cve-2025-61882/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/clop-ransomware-exploits-oracle-e-business-suite-zero-day-cve-2025-61882/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Cl0p Gang Exploits Oracle EBS Zero-Day in Massive Data Theft Spree</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Cl0p ransomware syndicate, also known as Graceful Spider, is actively exploiting a critical zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2025-61882, in Oracle's E-Business Suite (EBS). The flaw, which has a CVSS score of 9.8, allows for unauthenticated remote code execution and has been used to steal data from numerous organizations since at least August 2025. The attackers exfiltrated data for weeks before sending extortion demands in late September. In response, Oracle released an emergency patch on October 4, 2025, and CISA has added the vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, mandating a patch deadline for federal agencies.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Ransomware, Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Detailed analysis of the Cl0p ransomware campaign exploiting the critical Oracle E-Business Suite zero-day vulnerability CVE-2025-61882. Learn about the threat, impact, and mitigation steps.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> clop-ransomware-exploits-oracle-e-business-suite-zero-day-cve-2025-61882</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 2</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 2 updates recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/clop-ransomware-exploits-oracle-e-business-suite-zero-day-cve-2025-61882/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: SonicWall Breach Far Worse Than Feared: All Cloud Backup Users' Firewall Configs Stolen</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sonicwall-breach-expands-compromising-all-cloud-backup-users/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sonicwall-breach-expands-compromising-all-cloud-backup-users/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> SonicWall Breach Far Worse Than Feared: All Cloud Backup Users' Firewall Configs Stolen</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>**[SonicWall](https://www.sonicwall.com)** has issued a major update on a September data breach, revealing its impact is far more severe than initially disclosed. The company confirmed that an unauthorized party accessed and exfiltrated firewall configuration backups for **all** customers of its MySonicWall cloud backup service, a stark revision from the initial estimate of less than 5%. The stolen `.EXP` files contain complete firewall configurations, including security rules and encrypted credentials. While the credentials remain encrypted, security experts warn that possession of these files significantly lowers the bar for future targeted attacks. SonicWall, assisted by **[Mandiant](https://www.mandiant.com/)**, is urging all affected customers to reset passwords and follow detailed mitigation guidance.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Supply Chain Attack, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> SonicWall data breach, MySonicWall, firewall configuration, cloud backup breach, Mandiant, cybersecurity incident, network security</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> SonicWall confirms a massive data breach impacting all users of its MySonicWall cloud backup service. Attackers stole firewall configuration files, increasing the risk of future targeted attacks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> sonicwall-breach-expands-compromising-all-cloud-backup-users</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sonicwall-breach-expands-compromising-all-cloud-backup-users/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: AI-Powered Social Engineering to Become Top Cyber Threat, ISACA Warns</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ai-driven-social-engineering-top-cyber-threat-for-2026/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ai-driven-social-engineering-top-cyber-threat-for-2026/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> AI-Powered Social Engineering to Become Top Cyber Threat, ISACA Warns</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new report from the global IT association ISACA reveals a major shift in the threat landscape, with IT professionals now believing AI-driven social engineering will be the most significant cyber threat by 2026. The survey of 3,000 professionals found that 63% ranked this emerging threat highest, surpassing ransomware. Critically, the report also highlights a widespread lack of preparedness, with only 13% of organizations feeling 'very prepared' to manage the risks of generative AI, signaling an urgent need for new defense strategies and training.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Intelligence, Phishing, Policy and Compliance</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new ISACA survey of 3,000 IT professionals reveals that AI-driven social engineering is expected to be the top cyber threat by 2026, with most organizations unprepared.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ai-driven-social-engineering-top-cyber-threat-for-2026</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ai-driven-social-engineering-top-cyber-threat-for-2026/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>