<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:43:50 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/rss/last.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA Mandates Patching for Four Actively Exploited Flaws in Zimbra, Vite, and More</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-four-actively-exploited-vulnerabilities-to-kev-catalog-january-2026/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-four-actively-exploited-vulnerabilities-to-kev-catalog-january-2026/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Mandates Patching for Four Actively Exploited Flaws in Zimbra, Vite, and More</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added four vulnerabilities to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, confirming they are under active attack. The flaws affect a diverse range of products, including Synacor Zimbra Collaboration Suite (CVE-2025-68645), the Vite frontend framework (CVE-2025-31125), Versa Concerto SD-WAN (CVE-2025-34026), and the 'eslint-config-prettier' NPM package (CVE-2025-54313). Due to evidence of ongoing exploitation, Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies are required to apply patches or mitigations by February 12, 2026. CISA strongly urges all organizations to prioritize remediation to defend against these immediate threats.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Supply Chain Attack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA has added four actively exploited vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-68645, CVE-2025-31125, CVE-2025-34026, CVE-2025-54313) to its KEV catalog, affecting Zimbra, Vite, and more. Learn about the threats and the required remediation steps.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-adds-four-actively-exploited-vulnerabilities-to-kev-catalog-january-2026</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-four-actively-exploited-vulnerabilities-to-kev-catalog-january-2026/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/cisa-adds-four-actively-exploited-vulnerabilities-to-kev-catalog-january-2026.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: North Korean Hackers Lure Developers with Fake Job Interviews, Backdoor macOS via VS Code</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/north-korean-contagious-interview-campaign-weaponizes-vs-code-projects/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/north-korean-contagious-interview-campaign-weaponizes-vs-code-projects/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> North Korean Hackers Lure Developers with Fake Job Interviews, Backdoor macOS via VS Code</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>State-sponsored threat actors from North Korea, including the Lazarus Group, are targeting software developers in a sophisticated campaign dubbed 'Contagious Interview.' According to Jamf Threat Labs, the attackers use fake job offers to entice developers, particularly in the crypto and fintech sectors, into cloning malicious repositories from GitHub and GitLab. The attack abuses a feature in Microsoft's Visual Studio Code (VS Code), where trusting a repository can automatically execute a hidden `tasks.json` file. This triggers a backdoor on macOS systems, establishing persistence, collecting system data, and opening a C2 channel for remote code execution.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Supply Chain Attack, Phishing</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> North Korean threat actors (Lazarus Group) are targeting developers with a 'Contagious Interview' campaign, using malicious VS Code projects on GitHub to install backdoors on macOS systems.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> north-korean-contagious-interview-campaign-weaponizes-vs-code-projects</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/north-korean-contagious-interview-campaign-weaponizes-vs-code-projects/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/north-korean-contagious-interview-campaign-weaponizes-vs-code-projects.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: PcComponentes Denies Data Breach, Blames Credential Stuffing for Account Takeovers</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/spanish-retailer-pccomponentes-denies-breach-cites-credential-stuffing-attack/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/spanish-retailer-pccomponentes-denies-breach-cites-credential-stuffing-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> PcComponentes Denies Data Breach, Blames Credential Stuffing for Account Takeovers</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Spanish electronics retailer PcComponentes has denied claims of a massive data breach affecting 16 million customers, stating its internal systems were not compromised. The announcement came after a threat actor, 'daghetiaw,' attempted to sell a large customer database on a hacking forum. The company's investigation concluded the incident was a large-scale credential stuffing attack, where attackers used credentials stolen from other breaches to access user accounts. While denying the breach, PcComponentes confirmed that customer data such as names, addresses, and phone numbers were exposed for accounts with reused passwords. In response, the company has mandated two-factor authentication (2FA) for all users and invalidated all active sessions.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Phishing, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> PcComponentes, a major Spanish online retailer, refutes claims of a 16 million user data breach, attributing the incident to a credential stuffing attack and has since mandated 2FA for all accounts.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> spanish-retailer-pccomponentes-denies-breach-cites-credential-stuffing-attack</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/spanish-retailer-pccomponentes-denies-breach-cites-credential-stuffing-attack/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/spanish-retailer-pccomponentes-denies-breach-cites-credential-stuffing-attack.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: VoidLink Malware Believed to Be First Major Threat Almost Entirely Coded by AI</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/voidlink-malware-marks-new-era-of-ai-generated-threats/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/voidlink-malware-marks-new-era-of-ai-generated-threats/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> VoidLink Malware Believed to Be First Major Threat Almost Entirely Coded by AI</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Security researchers at Check Point Research now believe the sophisticated VoidLink malware framework was almost entirely developed using AI. This marks a significant shift in the threat landscape, dramatically lowering the barrier to entry for creating complex, modular malware. VoidLink, which targets Linux-based cloud and containerized environments (AWS, GCP, Azure), was reportedly developed in a fraction of the time it would take a human team. The malware is inspired by Cobalt Strike and is designed for long-term stealth, surveillance, and data collection, featuring 37 default plug-ins. This development suggests that AI can now be used not just to assist, but to lead the creation of advanced cyber weapons.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Threat Intelligence, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new Linux malware framework, VoidLink, is believed to have been almost entirely created by AI, targeting cloud and containerized environments for stealthy surveillance. This marks a new era of AI-generated threats.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> voidlink-malware-marks-new-era-of-ai-generated-threats</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/voidlink-malware-marks-new-era-of-ai-generated-threats/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/voidlink-malware-marks-new-era-of-ai-generated-threats.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New 'Osiris' Ransomware Borrows TTPs from Medusa and Inc Gangs, Uses Signed Driver to Kill AV</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-osiris-ransomware-linked-to-medusa-and-inc-gang-ttps/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-osiris-ransomware-linked-to-medusa-and-inc-gang-ttps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New 'Osiris' Ransomware Borrows TTPs from Medusa and Inc Gangs, Uses Signed Driver to Kill AV</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new ransomware strain named Osiris is demonstrating a high level of sophistication by combining tactics from established ransomware groups like Medusa and Inc. The attackers use Rclone for data exfiltration to Wasabi cloud storage and deploy a version of Mimikatz named `kaz.exe`, both TTPs linked to the Inc group. More significantly, Osiris uses a custom-developed and signed malicious driver, 'Abyssworker' (aka Poortry), in a Bring-Your-Own-Vulnerable-Driver (BYOVD) attack to terminate security software. This driver and its loader, 'Stonestop,' have been previously associated with the Medusa ransomware gang. The use of these advanced, borrowed TTPs suggests Osiris is operated by experienced actors, possibly former affiliates of other groups.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Malware, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The new Osiris ransomware strain shows links to Medusa and Inc groups, using a custom-signed malicious driver (Poortry/Abyssworker) to disable security software in a sophisticated BYOVD attack.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> new-osiris-ransomware-linked-to-medusa-and-inc-gang-ttps</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-osiris-ransomware-linked-to-medusa-and-inc-gang-ttps/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/new-osiris-ransomware-linked-to-medusa-and-inc-gang-ttps.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: INC Ransomware OPSEC Fail: Reused Infrastructure Leads to Data Recovery for 12 U.S. Victims</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/inc-ransomware-opsec-fail-allows-data-recovery-for-12-us-firms/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/inc-ransomware-opsec-fail-allows-data-recovery-for-12-us-firms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> INC Ransomware OPSEC Fail: Reused Infrastructure Leads to Data Recovery for 12 U.S. Victims</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A significant operational security (OPSEC) failure by the INC ransomware group has allowed cybersecurity firm Cyber Centaurs to recover stolen data for twelve U.S. organizations. The discovery was made after analyzing an attack involving the RainINC ransomware variant. Researchers found artifacts from the open-source backup tool, Restic, including hardcoded S3 access keys and passwords. By pivoting to this attacker-controlled infrastructure, Cyber Centaurs found that the gang had been reusing the same cloud storage repositories across multiple attacks, leaving the encrypted data of a dozen unrelated victims accessible. This rare win for defenders highlights how even sophisticated groups can make critical mistakes.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Incident Response, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> An operational security (OPSEC) failure by the INC ransomware group, involving reused cloud infrastructure and hardcoded credentials, allowed Cyber Centaurs to recover stolen data for 12 U.S. companies.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> inc-ransomware-opsec-fail-allows-data-recovery-for-12-us-firms</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/inc-ransomware-opsec-fail-allows-data-recovery-for-12-us-firms/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/inc-ransomware-opsec-fail-allows-data-recovery-for-12-us-firms.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Incident Response</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Apple Supplier Luxshare Breached by RansomHub, Leaking Unreleased Product Designs</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apple-supplier-luxshare-hit-by-ransomhub-confidential-data-leaked/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apple-supplier-luxshare-hit-by-ransomhub-confidential-data-leaked/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Apple Supplier Luxshare Breached by RansomHub, Leaking Unreleased Product Designs</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The RansomHub ransomware group has claimed a major supply chain attack against Luxshare Precision Industry, a key Chinese manufacturing partner for Apple, nVidia, and LG. The attackers allege they stole over a terabyte of data in December 2025 and, after a failed ransom negotiation, began leaking it on their dark web site. The leaked data reportedly includes highly sensitive intellectual property, such as 3D CAD models (.prt files), PCB designs, and engineering drawings for unreleased Apple products. This breach poses a significant risk to Apple's product roadmap and highlights the critical vulnerability of even the most secure companies to attacks on their supply chain partners.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Ransomware, Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Apple supplier Luxshare has been breached by the RansomHub ransomware group, resulting in the theft and leak of over a terabyte of sensitive data, including confidential designs for future Apple products.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> apple-supplier-luxshare-hit-by-ransomhub-confidential-data-leaked</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apple-supplier-luxshare-hit-by-ransomhub-confidential-data-leaked/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/apple-supplier-luxshare-hit-by-ransomhub-confidential-data-leaked.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Victims of Manage My Health Breach in New Zealand Warned of Follow-On Phishing Attacks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/manage-my-health-breach-victims-warned-of-secondary-phishing-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/manage-my-health-breach-victims-warned-of-secondary-phishing-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Victims of Manage My Health Breach in New Zealand Warned of Follow-On Phishing Attacks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>New Zealand's Manage My Health patient portal is warning customers affected by its late 2025 data breach to be vigilant for secondary attacks. The company stated that malicious actors are now sending spam and phishing emails impersonating the organization to exploit the more than 120,000 individuals whose data was stolen. The original breach involved an organized hacking group, with one actor using the alias 'Kazu,' exfiltrating over 400,000 medical documents and demanding a ransom. The incident has triggered an official inquiry by New Zealand's Office of the Privacy Commissioner and an urgent government review.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Phishing, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Following a major data breach, New Zealand's Manage My Health portal is warning over 120,000 victims to be aware of secondary spam and phishing campaigns that are impersonating the organization.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> manage-my-health-breach-victims-warned-of-secondary-phishing-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/manage-my-health-breach-victims-warned-of-secondary-phishing-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/manage-my-health-breach-victims-warned-of-secondary-phishing-attacks.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Anubis RaaS Ups the Ante with Destructive 'Wipe Mode' to Maximize Extortion</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/anubis-raas-offers-destructive-wipe-mode-for-extortion/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/anubis-raas-offers-destructive-wipe-mode-for-extortion/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Anubis RaaS Ups the Ante with Destructive 'Wipe Mode' to Maximize Extortion</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) operation named Anubis is gaining attention for its destructive capabilities. Evolving from a prototype called 'Sphinx,' Anubis offers its affiliates a dual-execution model. In addition to standard encryption, the malware can be run with a `/WIPEMODE` parameter that irreversibly overwrites and destroys victim files, rendering them unrecoverable. This tactic fundamentally changes the extortion negotiation, as paying a ransom cannot restore the data. It indicates a strategy where attackers rely solely on the threat of leaking exfiltrated data for payment, using permanent data destruction as additional leverage. The group is targeting organizations opportunistically across the globe.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Malware, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Anubis Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) operation features a dual-execution model with an optional '/WIPEMODE' that permanently destroys victim data, escalating extortion tactics.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> anubis-raas-offers-destructive-wipe-mode-for-extortion</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/anubis-raas-offers-destructive-wipe-mode-for-extortion/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/anubis-raas-offers-destructive-wipe-mode-for-extortion.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: China-Linked APT UAT-8837 Hits Critical Infrastructure with Sitecore Zero-Day</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-linked-apt-uat-8837-exploits-sitecore-zero-day-in-critical-infrastructure/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-linked-apt-uat-8837-exploits-sitecore-zero-day-in-critical-infrastructure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> China-Linked APT UAT-8837 Hits Critical Infrastructure with Sitecore Zero-Day</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A China-linked APT group, tracked by Cisco Talos as UAT-8837, is actively exploiting a critical zero-day vulnerability (CVE-2025-53690) in Sitecore products to compromise critical infrastructure organizations in North America. The flaw, a ViewState deserialization vulnerability with a 9.0 CVSS score, allows for remote code execution. After gaining initial access, UAT-8837 deploys a range of open-source tools like Sharphound, Earthworm, and Certipy for reconnaissance, persistence, and data harvesting. The group's main payload is the WeepSteel backdoor. In one case, the attackers were seen exfiltrating DLLs related to the victim's own products, raising fears of future supply chain attacks.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Vulnerability, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 7 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> China-nexus APT group UAT-8837 is exploiting a critical zero-day (CVE-2025-53690) in Sitecore to target critical infrastructure, using open-source tools and the WeepSteel backdoor for espionage.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> china-linked-apt-uat-8837-exploits-sitecore-zero-day-in-critical-infrastructure</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-linked-apt-uat-8837-exploits-sitecore-zero-day-in-critical-infrastructure/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/china-linked-apt-uat-8837-exploits-sitecore-zero-day-in-critical-infrastructure.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: North Korean 'Konni' APT Abuses Google Ad Trackers to Deliver Malware in 'Operation Poseidon'</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/konni-apt-operation-poseidon-abuses-ad-trackers-for-malware-delivery/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/konni-apt-operation-poseidon-abuses-ad-trackers-for-malware-delivery/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> North Korean 'Konni' APT Abuses Google Ad Trackers to Deliver Malware in 'Operation Poseidon'</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The North Korean-linked Konni APT group is conducting a spear-phishing campaign, 'Operation Poseidon,' that abuses legitimate ad tracking infrastructure from Google and Naver to evade detection. Attackers embed malicious URLs within trusted ad-tracking links (e.g., ad.doubleclick.net). When a victim clicks the link, they are redirected through the ad network to a compromised WordPress site that serves malware like the EndRAT or FalseCub trojans. This technique effectively bypasses email security filters and lowers user suspicion. The campaign has been observed targeting government employees in Afghanistan with emails disguised as official correspondence.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Phishing, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The North Korean Konni APT is abusing legitimate ad trackers from Google and Naver in 'Operation Poseidon,' a spear-phishing campaign to deliver EndRAT and FalseCub malware by bypassing security filters.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> konni-apt-operation-poseidon-abuses-ad-trackers-for-malware-delivery</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/konni-apt-operation-poseidon-abuses-ad-trackers-for-malware-delivery/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/konni-apt-operation-poseidon-abuses-ad-trackers-for-malware-delivery.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Oracle Drops Massive January 2026 Patch: 337 Flaws Fixed, Including a 10.0 CVSS Bug</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/oracle-january-2026-critical-patch-update-addresses-337-vulnerabilities/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/oracle-january-2026-critical-patch-update-addresses-337-vulnerabilities/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Oracle Drops Massive January 2026 Patch: 337 Flaws Fixed, Including a 10.0 CVSS Bug</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Oracle has released its first Critical Patch Update (CPU) for 2026, a massive release containing 337 new security patches for a wide array of its products. The update includes a fix for a critical vulnerability, CVE-2026-21962, which affects the Oracle HTTP Server and WebLogic Server Proxy Plug-in and carries a CVSS score of 10.0. This flaw is remotely exploitable without authentication and could allow an attacker to completely take over the affected system and access all its data. Another high-severity flaw, CVE-2026-21969, affects Oracle's Supply Chain Supplier Portal. Oracle strongly urges customers to apply these patches immediately to defend against potential attacks.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Patch Management, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Oracle's January 2026 Critical Patch Update addresses 337 security vulnerabilities, including a critical CVSS 10.0 flaw (CVE-2026-21962) in Oracle HTTP Server and WebLogic. Apply patches now.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> oracle-january-2026-critical-patch-update-addresses-337-vulnerabilities</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/oracle-january-2026-critical-patch-update-addresses-337-vulnerabilities/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/oracle-january-2026-critical-patch-update-addresses-337-vulnerabilities.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: New Zealand's 'Manage My Health' Portal Breached; Data of 120,000 Patients Held for Ransom</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-zealand-patient-portal-manage-my-health-hit-by-ransomware/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-zealand-patient-portal-manage-my-health-hit-by-ransomware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New Zealand's 'Manage My Health' Portal Breached; Data of 120,000 Patients Held for Ransom</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>New Zealand's largest patient portal, Manage My Health, is responding to a significant data breach that occurred in late December 2025. An attacker using the alias 'Kazu' claims to have stolen over 400,000 files, including sensitive medical records like lab results and clinical notes, affecting up to 126,000 individuals. The attacker has demanded a $60,000 ransom. The breach originated from a vulnerability in the 'Health Documents' module of the application. Manage My Health has since closed the security gap and is working with New Zealand authorities, while the government has launched an urgent review of the incident.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Ransomware, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> New Zealand's Manage My Health patient portal has suffered a major data breach, with an attacker named 'Kazu' stealing sensitive health data of up to 126,000 users and demanding a ransom.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> new-zealand-patient-portal-manage-my-health-hit-by-ransomware</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-zealand-patient-portal-manage-my-health-hit-by-ransomware/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/new-zealand-patient-portal-manage-my-health-hit-by-ransomware.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: China-Linked APT 'UAT-8837' Targets North American Critical Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-linked-apt-targets-north-american-critical-infrastructure/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-linked-apt-targets-north-american-critical-infrastructure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> China-Linked APT 'UAT-8837' Targets North American Critical Infrastructure</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new report from Cisco Talos has identified a China-nexus Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) group, tracked as UAT-8837, actively targeting critical infrastructure organizations in North America since at least 2025. The group gains initial access by exploiting public-facing vulnerabilities, including a zero-day in SiteCore products (CVE-2025-53690), and using compromised credentials. Once inside, UAT-8837 employs a variety of open-source tools, such as the Earthworm utility for creating reverse tunnels, to conduct reconnaissance, exfiltrate data, and maintain persistence. Cisco Talos assesses with medium confidence that the group is linked to China, highlighting the ongoing threat of state-sponsored espionage against vital sectors.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Cyberattack, Industrial Control Systems</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Cisco Talos reports a China-nexus APT group, UAT-8837, is targeting North American critical infrastructure by exploiting vulnerabilities like CVE-2025-53690 and using the Earthworm tunneling tool.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> china-linked-apt-targets-north-american-critical-infrastructure</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-linked-apt-targets-north-american-critical-infrastructure/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/china-linked-apt-targets-north-american-critical-infrastructure.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Oracle's January 2026 Patch Update Fixes 337 Flaws, Including Critical Remote Exploits</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/oracle-january-2026-cpu-fixes-337-flaws-including-critical-remote-exploits/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/oracle-january-2026-cpu-fixes-337-flaws-including-critical-remote-exploits/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Oracle's January 2026 Patch Update Fixes 337 Flaws, Including Critical Remote Exploits</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Oracle has released its January 2026 Critical Patch Update (CPU), a massive security update containing 337 new patches for vulnerabilities across more than 30 product families. The update resolves approximately 230 unique CVEs, with the discrepancy due to shared components like third-party libraries affecting multiple products. Alarmingly, over 235 of the patched vulnerabilities can be exploited remotely without authentication, significantly increasing their risk. The update includes fixes for over two dozen critical-rated flaws, such as CVE-2025-66516, a 10.0 CVSS vulnerability in the Apache Tika library embedded in Oracle products. Oracle strongly urges customers to apply these patches without delay.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Patch Management, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Oracle's January 2026 Critical Patch Update (CPU) addresses 337 security vulnerabilities across its product portfolio, with over 235 remotely exploitable without authentication. Key flaws include CVE-2025-66516.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> oracle-january-2026-cpu-fixes-337-flaws-including-critical-remote-exploits</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/oracle-january-2026-cpu-fixes-337-flaws-including-critical-remote-exploits/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/oracle-january-2026-cpu-fixes-337-flaws-including-critical-remote-exploits.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Cisco Scrambles to Patch Actively Exploited RCE Zero-Day in Comms Products</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisco-warns-of-actively-exploited-zero-day-rce-flaw-cve-2026-20045/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisco-warns-of-actively-exploited-zero-day-rce-flaw-cve-2026-20045/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Cisco Scrambles to Patch Actively Exploited RCE Zero-Day in Comms Products</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Cisco has issued an urgent warning and emergency patches for a critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability, CVE-2026-20045, affecting a wide range of its Unified Communications and Webex Calling products. This zero-day flaw is being actively exploited in the wild, allowing unauthenticated attackers to send crafted HTTP requests to the web management interface and execute arbitrary code, potentially leading to full root access on the underlying server. In response to the active threat, the U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added the vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, mandating federal agencies to patch by February 11, 2026. Cisco has confirmed there are no workarounds and is urging all customers to apply the updates immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Cisco releases emergency patches for CVE-2026-20045, a critical RCE zero-day vulnerability under active exploitation affecting Unified Communications and Webex products. CISA has added it to the KEV catalog.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisco-warns-of-actively-exploited-zero-day-rce-flaw-cve-2026-20045</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisco-warns-of-actively-exploited-zero-day-rce-flaw-cve-2026-20045/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/cisco-warns-of-actively-exploited-zero-day-rce-flaw-cve-2026-20045.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Everest Ransomware Leaks Data of 72 Million Under Armour Customers After Failed Talks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/everest-ransomware-claims-under-armour-breach-leaks-data-of-72m-customers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/everest-ransomware-claims-under-armour-breach-leaks-data-of-72m-customers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Everest Ransomware Leaks Data of 72 Million Under Armour Customers After Failed Talks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Everest ransomware group has claimed a massive data breach against athletic apparel giant Under Armour. After negotiations allegedly failed, the group announced on its dark web leak site that it has published the full dataset, which it claims contains 191 million records, including 72.7 million unique email addresses. The compromised data reportedly includes sensitive customer information such as full names, phone numbers, physical locations, and purchase histories. This breach places a huge number of individuals at significant risk for targeted phishing campaigns, identity theft, and other fraudulent activities.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Everest ransomware group claims to have breached Under Armour, leaking a massive dataset allegedly containing the personal information of over 72 million customers on the dark web.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> everest-ransomware-claims-under-armour-breach-leaks-data-of-72m-customers</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/everest-ransomware-claims-under-armour-breach-leaks-data-of-72m-customers/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/everest-ransomware-claims-under-armour-breach-leaks-data-of-72m-customers.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Exposed Security Training Apps Like OWASP Juice Shop Create Backdoors into Corporate Clouds</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/insecure-security-training-apps-expose-cloud-infrastructure-at-major-firms/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/insecure-security-training-apps-expose-cloud-infrastructure-at-major-firms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Exposed Security Training Apps Like OWASP Juice Shop Create Backdoors into Corporate Clouds</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new report reveals a dangerous trend where intentionally vulnerable security training applications, such as OWASP Juice Shop and DVWA, are being deployed on live, production cloud infrastructure and left exposed to the internet. Threat actors are actively scanning for and exploiting these misconfigured applications to compromise the cloud environments of numerous organizations, including Fortune 500 companies and security vendors. The exploits have been used to achieve remote code execution, deploy webshells, install cryptominers, and steal sensitive cloud credentials, turning these training tools into unmonitored backdoors.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cloud Security, Cyberattack, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A report reveals threat actors are exploiting misconfigured, internet-exposed security training applications like OWASP Juice Shop and DVWA to compromise corporate cloud infrastructure, leading to credential theft and RCE.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> insecure-security-training-apps-expose-cloud-infrastructure-at-major-firms</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/insecure-security-training-apps-expose-cloud-infrastructure-at-major-firms/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/insecure-security-training-apps-expose-cloud-infrastructure-at-major-firms.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: 'Skeleton Key' Attacks Bypass Defenses by Weaponizing Legitimate RMM Tools</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/skeleton-key-campaign-bypasses-malware-defenses-by-abusing-rmm-tools/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/skeleton-key-campaign-bypasses-malware-defenses-by-abusing-rmm-tools/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> 'Skeleton Key' Attacks Bypass Defenses by Weaponizing Legitimate RMM Tools</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A sophisticated attack campaign dubbed "Skeleton Key" is bypassing traditional, malware-focused security defenses by weaponizing legitimate remote monitoring and management (RMM) software. A report from KnowBe4 Threat Labs details how attackers first compromise user credentials and then abuse trusted IT tools to create persistent, stealthy backdoors inside enterprise networks. This 'living-off-the-land' (LotL) technique allows attackers to blend in with normal administrative activity, making their presence extremely difficult to detect and highlighting the need for security teams to shift focus from signature-based detection to behavioral analysis and identity security.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Intelligence, Security Operations, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A report on the 'Skeleton Key' campaign details how threat actors are abusing legitimate remote monitoring and management (RMM) software to create persistent, stealthy backdoors, bypassing traditional malware defenses.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> skeleton-key-campaign-bypasses-malware-defenses-by-abusing-rmm-tools</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/skeleton-key-campaign-bypasses-malware-defenses-by-abusing-rmm-tools/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/skeleton-key-campaign-bypasses-malware-defenses-by-abusing-rmm-tools.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Zoom &amp; GitLab Race to Patch Critical Flaws, Including a 9.9 CVSS RCE Bug</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/zoom-and-gitlab-patch-critical-flaws-including-9-9-cvss-vulnerability/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/zoom-and-gitlab-patch-critical-flaws-including-9-9-cvss-vulnerability/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Zoom &amp; GitLab Race to Patch Critical Flaws, Including a 9.9 CVSS RCE Bug</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Both Zoom and GitLab have released critical security updates to address several high-severity vulnerabilities. The most severe flaw, CVE-2026-22844, is a remote code execution vulnerability in Zoom Node Multimedia Routers (MMRs) with a near-perfect CVSS score of 9.9. This flaw could allow an unauthenticated attacker with network access to compromise the devices. GitLab's updates address multiple vulnerabilities, including two high-severity flaws (CVE-2025-13927 and CVE-2025-13928) that could allow an unauthenticated user to cause denial-of-service conditions. Users of all affected products are urged to apply the patches immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Patch Management, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Zoom and GitLab release critical security patches. Zoom addresses CVE-2026-22844, a 9.9 CVSS RCE flaw in Node Multimedia Routers, while GitLab fixes several high-severity DoS and 2FA bypass vulnerabilities.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> zoom-and-gitlab-patch-critical-flaws-including-9-9-cvss-vulnerability</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/zoom-and-gitlab-patch-critical-flaws-including-9-9-cvss-vulnerability/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/zoom-and-gitlab-patch-critical-flaws-including-9-9-cvss-vulnerability.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Spotlight on Supply Chain Risk: Reports Warn of Escalating SaaS-to-SaaS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/reports-highlight-growing-threat-of-saas-and-digital-supply-chain-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/reports-highlight-growing-threat-of-saas-and-digital-supply-chain-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Spotlight on Supply Chain Risk: Reports Warn of Escalating SaaS-to-SaaS Attacks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The digital supply chain has become a primary focus of cyber risk, as highlighted by multiple events on January 22, 2026. A new report from security firm Black Kite warns that the retail and wholesale sectors are highly exposed to attacks that exploit interconnected IT systems and shared vendors. Concurrently, SaaS security leader Obsidian Security launched the industry's first end-to-end SaaS supply chain security solution to combat the growing threat of SaaS-to-SaaS attacks, where a compromise in one application (like Salesloft) can cascade to affect hundreds of integrated partner applications (like Drift). These developments underscore the urgent need for organizations to gain visibility and control over their sprawling, interconnected digital ecosystems.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Cloud Security, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> New reports from Black Kite and a new platform launch from Obsidian Security highlight the escalating threat of digital supply chain attacks, particularly in retail and interconnected SaaS environments.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> reports-highlight-growing-threat-of-saas-and-digital-supply-chain-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/reports-highlight-growing-threat-of-saas-and-digital-supply-chain-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/reports-highlight-growing-threat-of-saas-and-digital-supply-chain-attacks.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: osTicket Flaw Lets Attackers Read Server Files via Malicious PDF Export</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/osticket-vulnerability-allows-arbitrary-file-reading-via-pdf-export-cve-2026-22200/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/osticket-vulnerability-allows-arbitrary-file-reading-via-pdf-export-cve-2026-22200/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> osTicket Flaw Lets Attackers Read Server Files via Malicious PDF Export</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A high-severity vulnerability, CVE-2026-22200, has been disclosed in osTicket, a popular open-source helpdesk system. The flaw allows an unauthenticated, anonymous attacker to read arbitrary files from the server by injecting a malicious PHP filter chain into a support ticket. When a privileged user exports the ticket to PDF, the vulnerability is triggered, embedding the contents of sensitive server files (like configuration files) into the generated PDF as a bitmap image. Researchers warn this flaw can be chained with other vulnerabilities for full remote code execution (RCE). Patches are available in versions 1.18.3 and 1.17.4.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A vulnerability (CVE-2026-22200) in the osTicket helpdesk system allows unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary server files by exploiting the PDF export function with a malicious PHP filter chain.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> osticket-vulnerability-allows-arbitrary-file-reading-via-pdf-export-cve-2026-22200</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/osticket-vulnerability-allows-arbitrary-file-reading-via-pdf-export-cve-2026-22200/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/osticket-vulnerability-allows-arbitrary-file-reading-via-pdf-export-cve-2026-22200.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Everest Ransomware Claims Breach of McDonald's India, Threatens to Leak 861GB of Data</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/everest-ransomware-group-claims-breach-of-mcdonalds-india/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/everest-ransomware-group-claims-breach-of-mcdonalds-india/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Everest Ransomware Claims Breach of McDonald's India, Threatens to Leak 861GB of Data</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Everest ransomware group continues its spree of high-profile attacks, now claiming to have breached McDonald's India. In a post on its dark web leak site dated January 20, 2026, the group alleged the exfiltration of 861 GB of data and gave the company a two-day deadline to respond. To back its claim, Everest leaked screenshots purportedly showing financial reports, internal audits, and a 'Contact Database' with investor and partner information from the US, UK, Singapore, and India. The data structure suggests the attackers may have compromised core accounting or ERP systems.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Everest ransomware group has claimed a cyberattack on McDonald's India, alleging the exfiltration of 861 GB of sensitive corporate and customer data and threatening a public leak.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> everest-ransomware-group-claims-breach-of-mcdonalds-india</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/everest-ransomware-group-claims-breach-of-mcdonalds-india/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/everest-ransomware-group-claims-breach-of-mcdonalds-india.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Critical Flaw in Popular Node.js Library 'binary-parser' Allows Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-nodejs-flaw-in-binary-parser-library-allows-code-execution-cve-2026-1245/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-nodejs-flaw-in-binary-parser-library-allows-code-execution-cve-2026-1245/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Critical Flaw in Popular Node.js Library 'binary-parser' Allows Code Execution</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The CERT Coordination Center (CERT/CC) has issued a warning about a critical vulnerability, CVE-2026-1245, in the popular 'binary-parser' npm library for Node.js. The flaw, which has a CVSS score of 6.5, allows for arbitrary JavaScript execution. The vulnerability exists because the library dynamically generates parser code from user-supplied input without proper sanitization, creating a code injection sink. This poses a significant software supply chain risk, as any application using the library to parse untrusted data could be compromised. Developers are urged to update to the patched version 2.3.0 immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Supply Chain Attack, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A critical vulnerability (CVE-2026-1245) in the 'binary-parser' npm library for Node.js allows for arbitrary code execution due to improper sanitization, posing a significant software supply chain risk.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> critical-nodejs-flaw-in-binary-parser-library-allows-code-execution-cve-2026-1245</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-nodejs-flaw-in-binary-parser-library-allows-code-execution-cve-2026-1245/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/critical-nodejs-flaw-in-binary-parser-library-allows-code-execution-cve-2026-1245.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New Android Malware Uses AI to Mimic Human Behavior and Evade Detection</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-ai-powered-android-malware-evades-detection-with-human-like-behavior/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-ai-powered-android-malware-evades-detection-with-human-like-behavior/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New Android Malware Uses AI to Mimic Human Behavior and Evade Detection</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new and sophisticated family of Android malware is leveraging artificial intelligence to commit ad fraud while evading detection. The malware uses TensorFlow, Google's open-source machine learning framework, to mimic human-like behavior, such as realistic clicks and swipes on hidden advertisements. This advanced technique allows it to bypass traditional ad fraud detection systems that rely on identifying the predictable, scripted patterns of bots. The malware can also stream video of its operations back to attackers, likely for model refinement, representing a significant evolution in mobile threat capabilities.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Mobile Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new family of Android malware is using artificial intelligence and the TensorFlow framework to mimic human behavior, allowing it to commit sophisticated ad fraud and evade traditional detection methods.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> new-ai-powered-android-malware-evades-detection-with-human-like-behavior</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-ai-powered-android-malware-evades-detection-with-human-like-behavior/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/new-ai-powered-android-malware-evades-detection-with-human-like-behavior.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Critical GNU Inetutils Flaw Allows Root Access via Telnet Authentication Bypass</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/gnu-inetutils-flaw-allows-remote-authentication-bypass-in-telnet-cve-2026-24061/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/gnu-inetutils-flaw-allows-remote-authentication-bypass-in-telnet-cve-2026-24061/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Critical GNU Inetutils Flaw Allows Root Access via Telnet Authentication Bypass</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A critical authentication bypass vulnerability, CVE-2026-24061, has been disclosed in the telnet daemon (telnetd) of GNU Inetutils, a common package of networking utilities for many Unix-like operating systems. The flaw allows a remote attacker to bypass authentication and gain root access to the system simply by providing a specially crafted username. Successful exploitation, achieved by passing '-f root' as the USER environment variable, leads to a complete compromise of the machine. All versions of GNU Inetutils up to and including 2.7 are affected. Administrators are urged to disable the telnetd service immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A critical authentication bypass vulnerability (CVE-2026-24061) in the telnet daemon of GNU Inetutils allows a remote attacker to gain root access to a vulnerable system.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> gnu-inetutils-flaw-allows-remote-authentication-bypass-in-telnet-cve-2026-24061</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/gnu-inetutils-flaw-allows-remote-authentication-bypass-in-telnet-cve-2026-24061/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/gnu-inetutils-flaw-allows-remote-authentication-bypass-in-telnet-cve-2026-24061.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Everest Ransomware Claims 861GB Data Breach at McDonald's India</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/everest-ransomware-claims-major-data-breach-at-mcdonalds-india/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/everest-ransomware-claims-major-data-breach-at-mcdonalds-india/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Everest Ransomware Claims 861GB Data Breach at McDonald's India</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Everest ransomware group has claimed a major cyberattack against McDonald's India, alleging the theft of 861 gigabytes of sensitive data. In a post on its dark web leak site on January 20, 2026, the group threatened to publicly release the information if a ransom is not paid. The compromised data reportedly includes a vast amount of personal information on customers and employees, as well as internal corporate documents. This incident, if confirmed, would be the latest in a series of data security issues for the fast-food giant's Indian operations, which suffered previous breaches. The Everest group, a Russian-speaking operation active since 2020, is known for its double-extortion tactics, and the potential leak of customer data poses a significant risk of identity theft and phishing campaigns.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Everest ransomware group claims to have breached McDonald's India, exfiltrating 861 GB of sensitive customer and corporate data and threatening to leak it on the dark web.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> everest-ransomware-claims-major-data-breach-at-mcdonalds-india</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/everest-ransomware-claims-major-data-breach-at-mcdonalds-india/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/everest-ransomware-claims-major-data-breach-at-mcdonalds-india.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Oracle Issues Critical Patch for CVSS 10.0 Auth Bypass in WebLogic Server</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/oracle-january-2026-critical-patch-update-fixes-337-flaws-including-cvss-10-bug/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/oracle-january-2026-critical-patch-update-fixes-337-flaws-including-cvss-10-bug/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Oracle Issues Critical Patch for CVSS 10.0 Auth Bypass in WebLogic Server</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Oracle has released its January 2026 Critical Patch Update (CPU), a massive security release containing 337 fixes for vulnerabilities across its product portfolio. The most severe flaw addressed is CVE-2026-21962, a critical authentication bypass vulnerability in the Oracle WebLogic Server Proxy Plug-in with a CVSS score of 10.0. This vulnerability can be exploited remotely by a low-privileged attacker without user interaction, potentially allowing complete takeover of the affected component. The flaw impacts WebLogic Server Proxy Plug-in versions 12.2.1.4.0, 14.1.1.0.0, and 14.1.2.0.0. Oracle strongly urges customers to apply these cumulative patches immediately, highlighting the continued risk of exploitation of previously patched vulnerabilities due to slow enterprise adoption rates.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Patch Management, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Oracle's January 2026 Critical Patch Update fixes 337 vulnerabilities, including the critical CVE-2026-21962 (CVSS 10.0) in Oracle WebLogic Server which allows for remote authentication bypass.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> oracle-january-2026-critical-patch-update-fixes-337-flaws-including-cvss-10-bug</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/oracle-january-2026-critical-patch-update-fixes-337-flaws-including-cvss-10-bug/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/oracle-january-2026-critical-patch-update-fixes-337-flaws-including-cvss-10-bug.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>