<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 23:05:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: React2Shell Zero-Day Exploited by Chinese Hackers Hours After Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/chinese-state-backed-groups-exploit-critical-react2shell-vulnerability/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/chinese-state-backed-groups-exploit-critical-react2shell-vulnerability/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> React2Shell Zero-Day Exploited by Chinese Hackers Hours After Disclosure</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability with a 10.0 CVSS score, dubbed "React2Shell" (CVE-2025-55182), is under active exploitation by multiple Chinese state-sponsored threat groups. The flaw affects modern web applications using React Server Components and the Next.js framework, allowing for unauthenticated code execution. The attacks began just hours after the vulnerability's public disclosure, prompting the U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) to add it to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, mandating urgent patching for federal agencies.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Cyberattack, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Critical RCE vulnerability CVE-2025-55182 (React2Shell) in React and Next.js is under active exploitation by Chinese state-sponsored groups. Learn about the impact, affected versions, and mitigation steps.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> chinese-state-backed-groups-exploit-critical-react2shell-vulnerability</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/chinese-state-backed-groups-exploit-critical-react2shell-vulnerability/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Google Patches Two Android Zero-Days Exploited in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-patches-two-actively-exploited-android-zero-days/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-patches-two-actively-exploited-android-zero-days/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Google Patches Two Android Zero-Days Exploited in the Wild</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Google has released its December 2025 Android Security Bulletin, addressing over 100 vulnerabilities. Among them are two high-severity zero-days, CVE-2025-48633 and CVE-2025-48572, which are being actively exploited in limited, targeted attacks. Both vulnerabilities reside in the Android Framework, affecting versions 13 through 16, and can be chained for information disclosure and privilege escalation. CISA has added both flaws to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, mandating a patch deadline of December 23, 2025, for U.S. federal agencies.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Mobile Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Google's December 2025 Android update patches two actively exploited zero-day vulnerabilities, CVE-2025-48633 and CVE-2025-48572. Learn about the flaws and the importance of updating your device.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> google-patches-two-actively-exploited-android-zero-days</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-patches-two-actively-exploited-android-zero-days/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: US &amp; Canada Warn of Chinese "BRICKSTORM" Malware Targeting VMware</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-canada-issue-alert-on-chinese-brickstorm-malware/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-canada-issue-alert-on-chinese-brickstorm-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> US &amp; Canada Warn of Chinese "BRICKSTORM" Malware Targeting VMware</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>U.S. and Canadian cybersecurity agencies have released a joint advisory on "BRICKSTORM," a sophisticated malware backdoor attributed to a Chinese state-sponsored threat actor dubbed "Warp Panda." The malware has been used in long-term campaigns since at least 2022 to compromise VMware environments in government and IT sectors. Attackers exploit edge devices for initial access, then pivot to VMware vCenter servers to deploy BRICKSTORM, enabling persistent access, data exfiltration, and further malware execution.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Threat Actor, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Joint alert from CISA, NSA, and CCCS warns of BRICKSTORM, a sophisticated malware backdoor used by Chinese actor Warp Panda to compromise VMware environments for espionage and data theft.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> us-canada-issue-alert-on-chinese-brickstorm-malware</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-canada-issue-alert-on-chinese-brickstorm-malware/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Ransomware Tactics Evolve: Data Theft and Extortion Replace Encryption in Manufacturing Sector</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-tactics-shift-data-theft-spikes-in-manufacturing-sector/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-tactics-shift-data-theft-spikes-in-manufacturing-sector/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Ransomware Tactics Evolve: Data Theft and Extortion Replace Encryption in Manufacturing Sector</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new report on ransomware trends reveals a major tactical shift in attacks against the manufacturing sector. Over the past year, attacks involving data encryption have fallen from 74% to 40%, while extortion-only attacks have tripled to 10%. This change suggests that while organizations are getting better at preventing operational disruption, attackers are adapting by focusing on data theft for financial leverage. Double extortion, combining both theft and encryption, was used in over half of all incidents, with groups like Akira, Qilin, and PLAY being the most active.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Intelligence, Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new report reveals a major shift in ransomware tactics targeting the manufacturing sector, with attackers favoring data theft and extortion over encryption. Akira, Qilin, and PLAY are among the top threats.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ransomware-tactics-shift-data-theft-spikes-in-manufacturing-sector</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-tactics-shift-data-theft-spikes-in-manufacturing-sector/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Spyware Vendor Intellexa Wields Zero-Days and Malicious Ads to Deploy Predator Spyware</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/spyware-vendor-intellexa-arsenal-of-zero-days-and-ad-based-attacks-revealed/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/spyware-vendor-intellexa-arsenal-of-zero-days-and-ad-based-attacks-revealed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Spyware Vendor Intellexa Wields Zero-Days and Malicious Ads to Deploy Predator Spyware</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new report from Google's Threat Analysis Group (TAG) identifies sanctioned spyware vendor Intellexa as one of the most prolific exploiters of zero-day vulnerabilities, responsible for 15 unique flaws discovered by Google since 2021. In a major tactical shift, Intellexa is now leveraging the mobile advertising ecosystem to deliver its Predator spyware. A system called "Aladdin" uses malicious ads to fingerprint and redirect targets to exploit servers in zero-click attacks, moving beyond the group's previous reliance on one-time links.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Malware, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Google's Threat Analysis Group reports that spyware vendor Intellexa is a prolific user of zero-day exploits and is now using malicious online ads to deliver its Predator spyware in zero-click attacks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> spyware-vendor-intellexa-arsenal-of-zero-days-and-ad-based-attacks-revealed</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/spyware-vendor-intellexa-arsenal-of-zero-days-and-ad-based-attacks-revealed/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New "Benzona" Ransomware Strain Discovered in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-benzona-ransomware-strain-emerges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-benzona-ransomware-strain-emerges/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New "Benzona" Ransomware Strain Discovered in the Wild</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Security researchers at CYFIRMA have discovered a new ransomware strain named "Benzona." The malware encrypts files on Windows, macOS, and Linux systems, appending a ".benzona" extension and dropping a ransom note titled "RECOVERY_INFO.txt". Victims are instructed to use the TOR browser to access a chat portal for recovery negotiations. The threat actors behind Benzona are believed to use a variety of initial access vectors, including social engineering, botnets, and exploitation of software vulnerabilities.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Security researchers have identified a new ransomware strain called Benzona that encrypts files, appends a .benzona extension, and uses a TOR-based chat for ransom negotiations.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> new-benzona-ransomware-strain-emerges</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-benzona-ransomware-strain-emerges/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Clop Ransomware Breaches UK's Largest NHS Trust via Oracle Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/clop-ransomware-breaches-barts-health-nhs-trust-via-oracle-vulnerability/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/clop-ransomware-breaches-barts-health-nhs-trust-via-oracle-vulnerability/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Clop Ransomware Breaches UK's Largest NHS Trust via Oracle Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Clop ransomware group has successfully breached Barts Health NHS Trust, the largest NHS trust in the United Kingdom. The attack, confirmed by the trust on December 5, 2025, involved the exploitation of an unspecified vulnerability in its Oracle E-business Suite software. The Russian-speaking cybercrime group stole files from a database and is known for leveraging software vulnerabilities for large-scale data theft and extortion campaigns. This incident highlights the significant and ongoing threat ransomware poses to the critical healthcare sector.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Ransomware, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Clop ransomware group breached Barts Health NHS Trust, the UK's largest, by exploiting a vulnerability in its Oracle E-business Suite software to steal data, highlighting risks to the healthcare sector.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> clop-ransomware-breaches-barts-health-nhs-trust-via-oracle-vulnerability</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/clop-ransomware-breaches-barts-health-nhs-trust-via-oracle-vulnerability/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: FTC Settles with Ed-Tech Firm Illuminate Education After Breach Exposed 10 Million Students' Data</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ftc-reaches-settlement-with-illuminate-education-over-massive-student-data-breach/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ftc-reaches-settlement-with-illuminate-education-over-massive-student-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> FTC Settles with Ed-Tech Firm Illuminate Education After Breach Exposed 10 Million Students' Data</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has reached a proposed settlement with education technology provider Illuminate Education, Inc. following a major data breach in 2021. The incident, which exposed the personal information of over 10 million students, was allegedly caused by inadequate security practices, including the failure to deactivate the credentials of a former employee. The settlement will require the company to significantly improve its data security program and undergo regular audits.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Regulatory, Policy and Compliance</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The FTC settles with Illuminate Education over a massive 2021 student data breach affecting 10 million students, citing inadequate security and failure to deactivate a former employee's credentials.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ftc-reaches-settlement-with-illuminate-education-over-massive-student-data-breach</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ftc-reaches-settlement-with-illuminate-education-over-massive-student-data-breach/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: G7 Unveils Framework for Coordinated Cyber Response in Financial Sector</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/g7-announces-framework-for-coordinated-cyber-incident-response-in-financial-sector/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/g7-announces-framework-for-coordinated-cyber-incident-response-in-financial-sector/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> G7 Unveils Framework for Coordinated Cyber Response in Financial Sector</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The G7 Cyber Expert Group, co-chaired by the U.S. Treasury and the Bank of England, has published a new policy paper outlining a framework for Collective Cyber Incident Response and Recovery (CCIRR). Released on December 4, 2025, the paper provides non-binding principles to enhance cooperation and compatibility among financial institutions and authorities during major cyber incidents. The framework aims to build a trusted community to respond to attacks that could threaten global financial stability.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The G7 Cyber Expert Group, led by the U.S. Treasury and Bank of England, has released a framework for Collective Cyber Incident Response and Recovery (CCIRR) to improve cooperation in the financial sector.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> g7-announces-framework-for-coordinated-cyber-incident-response-in-financial-sector</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/g7-announces-framework-for-coordinated-cyber-incident-response-in-financial-sector/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Critical 7-Zip RCE Vulnerability Now Under Active Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/active-exploitation-of-critical-7-zip-rce-vulnerability-confirmed/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/active-exploitation-of-critical-7-zip-rce-vulnerability-confirmed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Critical 7-Zip RCE Vulnerability Now Under Active Exploitation</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the popular 7-Zip file archiver, tracked as CVE-2025-11001, is now being actively exploited in the wild. The path traversal flaw, which affects versions prior to 25.0.0, can be triggered when a user extracts a specially crafted malicious archive. This allows an attacker to write files to arbitrary locations and execute code. NHS England has issued an advisory confirming active exploitation, urging all organizations to update their installations immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in 7-Zip (CVE-2025-11001) is under active exploitation. Learn how the path traversal flaw works and why you must update to version 25.0.0 immediately.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> active-exploitation-of-critical-7-zip-rce-vulnerability-confirmed</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/active-exploitation-of-critical-7-zip-rce-vulnerability-confirmed/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Washington Post Breached by Clop Ransomware via Oracle Flaws</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/washington-post-confirms-breach-in-massive-oracle-software-attack/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/washington-post-confirms-breach-in-massive-oracle-software-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Washington Post Breached by Clop Ransomware via Oracle Flaws</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Washington Post has officially confirmed it was a victim of a large-scale cyberattack orchestrated by the Clop ransomware group. The threat actors exploited vulnerabilities in Oracle's E-Business Suite, compromising over 100 organizations globally. The campaign involves data exfiltration followed by aggressive extortion tactics, with Clop publicly naming victims on its dark web leak site to pressure them into paying ransoms reportedly as high as $50 million. This incident underscores the significant risk posed by vulnerabilities in widely used enterprise software and the sophisticated, multi-faceted extortion methods employed by modern ransomware gangs.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Clop ransomware, Washington Post breach, Oracle E-Business Suite vulnerability, data extortion, cyberattack, TA505, ransomware campaign</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Clop ransomware group has breached The Washington Post and over 100 other organizations by exploiting vulnerabilities in Oracle's E-Business Suite, leading to massive data theft and extortion.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> washington-post-confirms-breach-in-massive-oracle-software-attack</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 4</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 4 updates recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/washington-post-confirms-breach-in-massive-oracle-software-attack/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: CISA Exposes 'BRICKSTORM' Backdoor Used by Chinese State Actors to Infiltrate US Government</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-brickstorm-malware-used-by-chinese-hackers-against-us-government/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-brickstorm-malware-used-by-chinese-hackers-against-us-government/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Exposes 'BRICKSTORM' Backdoor Used by Chinese State Actors to Infiltrate US Government</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The US Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), NSA, and Canadian Centre for Cyber Security have jointly exposed a sophisticated backdoor named 'BRICKSTORM'. According to the December 4, 2025 advisory, People's Republic of China (PRC) state-sponsored actors are using this malware to target government and IT sector organizations. BRICKSTORM is designed for stealth and long-term persistence in both VMware vSphere and Windows environments. It employs multi-layered encrypted communications, including DNS-over-HTTPS (DoH), to hide its C2 traffic. The advisory details an attack chain where actors used a web shell for initial access, moved laterally via RDP, and ultimately deployed BRICKSTORM on a VMware vCenter server to compromise domain controllers. Agencies are urged to hunt for this threat immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Malware, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA, NSA, and the Canadian Cyber Centre have issued a joint alert on BRICKSTORM, a stealthy backdoor used by Chinese state-sponsored actors to target government and IT sectors. Learn the TTPs and mitigations.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-warns-of-brickstorm-malware-used-by-chinese-hackers-against-us-government</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-brickstorm-malware-used-by-chinese-hackers-against-us-government/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Android Zero-Days Under Active Attack, CISA Adds to KEV Catalog</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/actively-exploited-android-zero-days-added-to-cisa-kev-catalog/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/actively-exploited-android-zero-days-added-to-cisa-kev-catalog/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Android Zero-Days Under Active Attack, CISA Adds to KEV Catalog</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added two high-severity Android zero-day vulnerabilities to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, indicating they are under active attack. The vulnerabilities, CVE-2025-48633 (Information Disclosure) and CVE-2025-48572 (Elevation of Privilege), affect the core Android Framework on versions 13, 14, 15, and 16. Google's December 2025 security bulletin confirmed the flaws may be subject to 'limited, targeted exploitation,' a pattern often associated with sophisticated spyware campaigns. Federal agencies are now mandated to patch these vulnerabilities, and all Android users are urged to apply the latest security updates as soon as possible to protect against potential device compromise.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Mobile Security, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA adds two actively exploited Android zero-day vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-48633, CVE-2025-48572) to its KEV catalog. Learn about the high-severity flaws and the urgent need to patch Android devices.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> actively-exploited-android-zero-days-added-to-cisa-kev-catalog</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/actively-exploited-android-zero-days-added-to-cisa-kev-catalog/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: React2Shell: Critical 10.0 CVSS RCE Flaw in React and Next.js Under Active Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-react2shell-rce-vulnerability-in-react-and-nextjs-sparks-emergency-patching/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-react2shell-rce-vulnerability-in-react-and-nextjs-sparks-emergency-patching/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> React2Shell: Critical 10.0 CVSS RCE Flaw in React and Next.js Under Active Exploitation</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A critical, unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability, dubbed 'React2Shell' (CVE-2025-55182), has been disclosed in React Server Components, affecting popular frameworks like Next.js. With a maximum CVSS score of 10.0, the flaw allows attackers to compromise servers with a single crafted HTTP request, requiring no user interaction. The vulnerability stems from an unsafe deserialization process in the 'Flight' protocol. Following the public disclosure on December 3, 2025, multiple weaponized proofs-of-concept became available, and active exploitation attempts by threat actors, including China-nexus groups, were observed. CISA has added CVE-2025-55182 to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, mandating immediate patching for federal agencies and urging all organizations to update affected components.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Cyberattack, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A critical 10.0 CVSS RCE vulnerability, CVE-2025-55182 (React2Shell), affects React Server Components and Next.js. Learn about the active exploitation, affected versions, and immediate patching instructions.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> critical-react2shell-rce-vulnerability-in-react-and-nextjs-sparks-emergency-patching</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-react2shell-rce-vulnerability-in-react-and-nextjs-sparks-emergency-patching/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Ransomware Payments Exceed $2.1 Billion Since 2022, FinCEN Reports</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fincen-report-reveals-2-1-billion-in-ransomware-payments-since-2022/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fincen-report-reveals-2-1-billion-in-ransomware-payments-since-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Ransomware Payments Exceed $2.1 Billion Since 2022, FinCEN Reports</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new Financial Trend Analysis from the U.S. Treasury's Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN), released December 4, 2025, reveals that financial institutions reported over $2.1 billion in ransomware-related payments between January 2022 and December 2024. The data, derived from Bank Secrecy Act (BSA) filings, shows a peak in 2023 with $1.1 billion in payments. The report identifies ALPHV/BlackCat, LockBit, and Akira as some of the most prevalent variants, with the manufacturing and financial services sectors being the most frequent victims. The analysis underscores the critical role of BSA reporting in tracking cybercrime trends and informing law enforcement actions.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Regulatory, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new FinCEN report reveals over $2.1 billion in ransomware payments were made between 2022 and 2024, with 2023 hitting a record $1.1 billion. Learn about the top variants and targeted industries.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> fincen-report-reveals-2-1-billion-in-ransomware-payments-since-2022</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fincen-report-reveals-2-1-billion-in-ransomware-payments-since-2022/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Freedom Mobile Data Breach Exposes Customer PII via Compromised Subcontractor</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/freedom-mobile-discloses-data-breach-via-compromised-subcontractor-account/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/freedom-mobile-discloses-data-breach-via-compromised-subcontractor-account/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Freedom Mobile Data Breach Exposes Customer PII via Compromised Subcontractor</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Canadian telecommunications provider Freedom Mobile announced on December 3, 2025, that it suffered a data breach after an unauthorized party gained access to its systems on October 23, 2025. The attacker leveraged the compromised account of a third-party subcontractor to access a customer account management platform. Exposed data includes customer names, addresses, birth dates, phone numbers, and account numbers. Freedom Mobile stated that more sensitive data like payment card information and passwords were not affected. The company is notifying a 'limited number' of affected individuals and advising them to be vigilant against phishing attacks.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Supply Chain Attack, Phishing</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Canadian carrier Freedom Mobile reports a data breach exposing customer personal information after an attacker gained access using a compromised subcontractor account. Find out what data was exposed and how to stay safe.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> freedom-mobile-discloses-data-breach-via-compromised-subcontractor-account</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/freedom-mobile-discloses-data-breach-via-compromised-subcontractor-account/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: G7 Unveils New Framework for Coordinated Cyber Response in Global Financial Sector</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/g7-publishes-new-framework-for-coordinated-cyber-response-in-financial-sector/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/g7-publishes-new-framework-for-coordinated-cyber-response-in-financial-sector/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> G7 Unveils New Framework for Coordinated Cyber Response in Global Financial Sector</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The G7 Cyber Expert Group, co-chaired by the U.S. Treasury and the Bank of England, has released a new policy paper outlining a framework for coordinated cyber incident response and recovery (CCIRR) in the global financial sector. Published on December 3, 2025, the non-binding guidelines aim to improve cross-border cooperation, information sharing, and communication among financial authorities and private entities during a major cyber crisis. The framework is built on three pillars: establishing response arrangements, utilizing them during an incident, and maintaining them through testing and exercises. The goal is to enhance the resilience of the interconnected international financial system against systemic cyber threats.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Incident Response</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The G7 Cyber Expert Group has published a new non-binding framework to improve collective cyber incident response and recovery within the global financial sector, focusing on cross-border cooperation.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> g7-publishes-new-framework-for-coordinated-cyber-response-in-financial-sector</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/g7-publishes-new-framework-for-coordinated-cyber-response-in-financial-sector/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Incident Response</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA KEV Alert: Actively Exploited ScadaBR Flaw Puts Industrial Control Systems at Risk</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-exploited-scadabr-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-exploited-scadabr-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA KEV Alert: Actively Exploited ScadaBR Flaw Puts Industrial Control Systems at Risk</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>CISA has added CVE-2021-26828, a high-severity vulnerability in the OpenPLC ScadaBR industrial control system (ICS) software, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog as of December 3, 2025. The flaw, with a CVSS score of 8.7, is an unrestricted file upload vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution (RCE) by uploading a malicious JSP file. This poses a significant risk to operational technology (OT) environments where this open-source SCADA solution is deployed. Federal agencies are mandated to patch by December 24, 2025, and CISA urges all organizations in critical infrastructure sectors to prioritize remediation.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Industrial Control Systems, Vulnerability, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA adds CVE-2021-26828, a high-severity RCE vulnerability in OpenPLC ScadaBR, to its KEV catalog due to active exploitation. Learn how this flaw impacts ICS/OT environments and how to mitigate it.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-adds-exploited-scadabr-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-exploited-scadabr-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Under Armour Sued Over Data Breach Attributed to 'Everest' Cybercrime Group</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/under-armour-faces-class-action-lawsuit-over-november-2025-data-breach/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/under-armour-faces-class-action-lawsuit-over-november-2025-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Under Armour Sued Over Data Breach Attributed to 'Everest' Cybercrime Group</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Athletic apparel giant Under Armour is the target of a new class action lawsuit following a November 2025 data breach. The suit, reported on December 4, 2025, claims the company was negligent in protecting the personal information of consumers and employees. The breach was allegedly carried out by the 'Everest' cybercriminal group, which claims to have stolen and leaked hundreds of gigabytes of data. The lawsuit asserts that Under Armour failed to implement basic cybersecurity measures like encryption and did not provide timely notification to victims, who now face a heightened risk of identity theft and fraud.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Threat Actor, Policy and Compliance</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Under Armour has been hit with a class action lawsuit alleging negligence after the Everest cybercrime group stole and leaked sensitive consumer and employee data in a November 2025 data breach.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> under-armour-faces-class-action-lawsuit-over-november-2025-data-breach</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/under-armour-faces-class-action-lawsuit-over-november-2025-data-breach/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Critical Zero-Days in PyTorch Scanner 'PickleScan' Create AI Supply Chain Risk</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/jfrog-uncovers-critical-zero-days-in-pytorch-scanning-tool-picklescan/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/jfrog-uncovers-critical-zero-days-in-pytorch-scanning-tool-picklescan/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Critical Zero-Days in PyTorch Scanner 'PickleScan' Create AI Supply Chain Risk</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Security firm JFrog has disclosed three critical zero-day vulnerabilities in PickleScan, a popular open-source tool used to scan Python pickle files for malware, particularly within the PyTorch AI framework. The flaws, collectively rated with a CVSS score of 9.3, allow an attacker to craft a malicious AI model that bypasses PickleScan's security checks. When this seemingly safe model is loaded by a user, it can lead to arbitrary code execution. This discovery, announced on December 3, 2025, highlights a significant software supply chain risk for the AI/ML community, as attackers could distribute weaponized models that evade standard security scanning.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Supply Chain Attack, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> JFrog has discovered three critical zero-day vulnerabilities (CVSS 9.3) in PickleScan, a tool for scanning PyTorch AI models, allowing malicious models to bypass security and execute code.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> jfrog-uncovers-critical-zero-days-in-pytorch-scanning-tool-picklescan</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/jfrog-uncovers-critical-zero-days-in-pytorch-scanning-tool-picklescan/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: AWS Boosts Cloud Defense with New AI-Powered Security Tools at re:Invent 2025</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/aws-unveils-new-ai-powered-security-tools-at-reinvent-2025/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/aws-unveils-new-ai-powered-security-tools-at-reinvent-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> AWS Boosts Cloud Defense with New AI-Powered Security Tools at re:Invent 2025</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>At its re:Invent 2025 conference, Amazon Web Services (AWS) unveiled several major additions to its security portfolio, heavily infused with artificial intelligence. Key announcements on December 3, 2025, included the preview of AWS Security Agent, a context-aware tool for proactive application security testing throughout the development lifecycle. AWS also announced the general availability of its revamped AWS Security Hub for centralized cloud security posture management (CSPM) and new attack sequence findings in Amazon GuardDuty for better threat detection in EC2 and ECS environments. These updates aim to automate and enhance security operations for organizations in the cloud.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cloud Security, Security Operations, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Amazon Web Services (AWS) announced new AI-powered security tools at re:Invent 2025, including AWS Security Agent, an upgraded AWS Security Hub, and enhanced Amazon GuardDuty threat detection.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> aws-unveils-new-ai-powered-security-tools-at-reinvent-2025</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/aws-unveils-new-ai-powered-security-tools-at-reinvent-2025/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>