<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:43:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: PhantomRaven Hits npm: Stealthy Attack Steals Dev Credentials &amp; CI/CD Secrets</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/phantomraven-supply-chain-attack-hits-npm-with-novel-stealth-technique/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/phantomraven-supply-chain-attack-hits-npm-with-novel-stealth-technique/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> PhantomRaven Hits npm: Stealthy Attack Steals Dev Credentials &amp; CI/CD Secrets</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A highly evasive software supply chain attack dubbed 'PhantomRaven' has compromised at least 126 npm packages, resulting in over 86,000 downloads. The campaign, discovered by Koi Security, utilizes a novel technique called 'Remote Dynamic Dependencies' (RDD) to bypass security scanners. The malicious packages appear benign with no dependencies but fetch a malicious payload from an external server during installation. This payload then steals developer credentials, including `.gitconfig` and `.npmrc` files, and CI/CD secrets for platforms like GitHub Actions, GitLab, and Jenkins. The attackers also employ 'slopsquatting,' creating plausible but non-existent package names that AI coding assistants might mistakenly suggest, tricking developers into installation.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Malware, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Learn about the PhantomRaven supply chain attack targeting the npm registry, which uses a 'Remote Dynamic Dependencies' (RDD) technique to steal developer credentials and CI/CD secrets.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> phantomraven-supply-chain-attack-hits-npm-with-novel-stealth-technique</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/phantomraven-supply-chain-attack-hits-npm-with-novel-stealth-technique/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Conduent Breach Exposes 10.5M; SafePay Ransomware Claims 8.5TB Data Theft</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/conduent-data-breach-exposes-10-million-individuals-data-from-safepay-ransomware-attack/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/conduent-data-breach-exposes-10-million-individuals-data-from-safepay-ransomware-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Conduent Breach Exposes 10.5M; SafePay Ransomware Claims 8.5TB Data Theft</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Business services giant Conduent has begun notifying over 10.5 million people that their sensitive data was stolen in a major cyberattack attributed to the SafePay ransomware group. The breach, which ranks as one of the largest healthcare data breaches ever, occurred between October 21, 2024, and January 13, 2025. The attackers had a dwell time of nearly three months, allowing them to exfiltrate an estimated 8.5 terabytes of data. The compromised information includes names, Social Security numbers, health insurance details, and medical records. Numerous government and corporate clients were affected, including various Blue Cross Blue Shield entities and state human services departments. The significant delay in notifying victims, a year after the intrusion began, has led to legal investigations.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Ransomware, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Business services provider Conduent is notifying 10.5 million individuals of a massive data breach by the SafePay ransomware group, which stole sensitive personal and medical information.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> conduent-data-breach-exposes-10-million-individuals-data-from-safepay-ransomware-attack</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/conduent-data-breach-exposes-10-million-individuals-data-from-safepay-ransomware-attack/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA KEV Alert: XWiki RCE Flaw Actively Exploited for Cryptomining</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/xwiki-rce-flaw-cve-2025-24893-added-to-cisa-kev-catalog-amid-active-exploitation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/xwiki-rce-flaw-cve-2025-24893-added-to-cisa-kev-catalog-amid-active-exploitation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA KEV Alert: XWiki RCE Flaw Actively Exploited for Cryptomining</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The US Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the XWiki enterprise wiki platform, CVE-2025-24893, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog. The flaw, rated 9.8 on the CVSS scale, allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code by injecting malicious Groovy expressions into a search query. Security researchers at VulnCheck have confirmed active exploitation in the wild, with attackers using the vulnerability to deploy cryptocurrency mining malware. CISA has mandated that federal agencies patch the flaw promptly due to the immediate risk.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA adds critical XWiki RCE vulnerability CVE-2025-24893 (CVSS 9.8) to its KEV catalog due to active exploitation for cryptomining. Patch immediately.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> xwiki-rce-flaw-cve-2025-24893-added-to-cisa-kev-catalog-amid-active-exploitation</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/xwiki-rce-flaw-cve-2025-24893-added-to-cisa-kev-catalog-amid-active-exploitation/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: VMware Zero-Day LPE Flaw Exploited by China-Linked Actor Added to CISA KEV</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/vmware-privilege-escalation-zero-day-cve-2025-41244-added-to-cisa-kev-catalog/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/vmware-privilege-escalation-zero-day-cve-2025-41244-added-to-cisa-kev-catalog/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> VMware Zero-Day LPE Flaw Exploited by China-Linked Actor Added to CISA KEV</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>CISA has added CVE-2025-41244, a high-severity local privilege escalation (LPE) vulnerability in VMware products, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog. The flaw affects VMware Aria Operations and VMware Tools and allows a non-administrative user on a virtual machine to gain root privileges. The vulnerability has been exploited as a zero-day since mid-October 2024, with attribution pointing to UNC5174, a suspected China-linked threat actor. The flaw is an untrusted search path vulnerability, and a public proof-of-concept is available, increasing the risk to unpatched systems.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Threat Actor, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA adds VMware zero-day CVE-2025-41244 to its KEV catalog. The LPE flaw, exploited by a China-linked actor, allows root access on virtual machines. Patch now.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> vmware-privilege-escalation-zero-day-cve-2025-41244-added-to-cisa-kev-catalog</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/vmware-privilege-escalation-zero-day-cve-2025-41244-added-to-cisa-kev-catalog/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Global Azure Outage Blamed on Faulty 'Front Door' Configuration Change</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-azure-global-outage-caused-by-faulty-front-door-configuration-change/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-azure-global-outage-caused-by-faulty-front-door-configuration-change/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Global Azure Outage Blamed on Faulty 'Front Door' Configuration Change</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A major global outage struck Microsoft Azure for approximately 8.5 hours on October 29-30, 2025, affecting a vast range of services including Microsoft 365, Xbox Live, and customer applications like those of Alaska Airlines. Microsoft attributed the root cause to a faulty tenant configuration change within its Azure Front Door (AFD) service. A defect in the deployment system's validation logic allowed the erroneous configuration to be pushed live, causing AFD nodes to fail and leading to a cascading DNS failure. Microsoft engineers resolved the issue by rolling back the change and rerouting traffic.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cloud Security, Security Operations, Incident Response</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A detailed analysis of the October 2025 global Microsoft Azure outage, caused by a faulty configuration change in the Azure Front Door service, impacting millions of users.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> microsoft-azure-global-outage-caused-by-faulty-front-door-configuration-change</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-azure-global-outage-caused-by-faulty-front-door-configuration-change/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
      <category>Incident Response</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Finance Execs Targeted in Sophisticated LinkedIn Phishing Scheme with Fake Board Invites</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/linkedin-phishing-campaign-targets-finance-execs-with-fake-board-invites/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/linkedin-phishing-campaign-targets-finance-execs-with-fake-board-invites/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Finance Execs Targeted in Sophisticated LinkedIn Phishing Scheme with Fake Board Invites</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A sophisticated phishing campaign is targeting finance executives through LinkedIn direct messages, using fake invitations to an executive board as a lure. The multi-stage attack, detailed by Push Security, aims to harvest Microsoft credentials and session cookies to bypass MFA. The attack chain leverages trusted services to appear legitimate, starting with a Google open redirect, leading to a fraudulent portal hosted on Google Firebase, and using a Cloudflare CAPTCHA to evade security bots. This non-email-based phishing vector is reportedly becoming significantly more common, accounting for over a third of recent attempts tracked by researchers.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Phishing, Threat Actor, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A sophisticated phishing campaign on LinkedIn is targeting finance executives with fake board invitations to steal Microsoft credentials and bypass MFA using trusted services.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> linkedin-phishing-campaign-targets-finance-execs-with-fake-board-invites</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/linkedin-phishing-campaign-targets-finance-execs-with-fake-board-invites/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Telecom Giant Ribbon Communications Breached by Nation-State Actor for 10 Months</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/telecom-provider-ribbon-communications-discloses-year-long-nation-state-breach/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/telecom-provider-ribbon-communications-discloses-year-long-nation-state-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Telecom Giant Ribbon Communications Breached by Nation-State Actor for 10 Months</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Telecommunications provider Ribbon Communications has disclosed a significant security breach by a suspected nation-state actor. According to an SEC filing, the attackers first gained access in December 2024 and remained undetected for nearly a year until September 2025. The company, which serves critical clients including the U.S. Department of Defense and major carriers like Verizon, stated the actor accessed several customer files stored on two laptops outside the main network. The long dwell time and the nature of the target suggest a sophisticated espionage campaign, raising serious concerns about supply chain security in the telecommunications sector.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cyberattack, Threat Actor, Supply Chain Attack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Telecom provider Ribbon Communications reveals a 10-month breach by a suspected nation-state actor, raising supply chain security concerns for its government and carrier clients.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> telecom-provider-ribbon-communications-discloses-year-long-nation-state-breach</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/telecom-provider-ribbon-communications-discloses-year-long-nation-state-breach/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: EY Exposes 4TB Database Backup on Public Azure Server</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ey-exposes-4tb-database-backup-on-public-azure-server/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ey-exposes-4tb-database-backup-on-public-azure-server/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> EY Exposes 4TB Database Backup on Public Azure Server</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Global accounting firm Ernst &amp; Young (EY) inadvertently exposed a massive 4-terabyte SQL Server backup file on a public Microsoft Azure server. The unprotected `.BAK` file was discovered by a security researcher from Neo Security and was not password-protected, leaving it accessible to anyone on the internet. Such a file could contain extremely sensitive corporate and client data, including database schemas, user information, API keys, and passwords. EY was notified through its CSIRT and promptly secured the file, stating that no client data was affected. The incident highlights the significant risks of cloud misconfigurations.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Cloud Security, Security Operations</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Global accounting firm EY exposed a 4TB SQL Server backup on a public Azure server due to a cloud misconfiguration, highlighting significant data security risks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ey-exposes-4tb-database-backup-on-public-azure-server</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ey-exposes-4tb-database-backup-on-public-azure-server/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Canada Issues National Alert as Hacktivists Target Critical Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/canada-issues-national-alert-as-hacktivists-target-critical-infrastructure/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/canada-issues-national-alert-as-hacktivists-target-critical-infrastructure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Canada Issues National Alert as Hacktivists Target Critical Infrastructure</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Canadian Centre for Cyber Security, along with the RCMP, has issued a national alert warning of increasing cyberattacks by hacktivists against the nation's critical infrastructure. The advisory follows multiple successful breaches of internet-accessible Industrial Control Systems (ICS) in sectors like water treatment, food, and manufacturing. The alert notes a tactical shift by hacktivists from simple DDoS attacks to more disruptive intrusions into Operational Technology (OT). Authorities are urging organizations, especially in under-regulated sectors, to immediately inventory and secure exposed ICS/OT devices, recommending VPNs with 2FA and enhanced monitoring to mitigate the risk to public safety.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Industrial Control Systems, Policy and Compliance, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Canadian Centre for Cyber Security issues a national alert over rising hacktivist attacks targeting internet-exposed Industrial Control Systems (ICS) in critical sectors.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> canada-issues-national-alert-as-hacktivists-target-critical-infrastructure</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/canada-issues-national-alert-as-hacktivists-target-critical-infrastructure/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Qilin Ransomware Rampage: Manufacturing Sector Bears the Brunt of 2025 Attacks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-surges-in-2025-with-manufacturing-sector-hit-hardest/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-surges-in-2025-with-manufacturing-sector-hit-hardest/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Qilin Ransomware Rampage: Manufacturing Sector Bears the Brunt of 2025 Attacks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Qilin ransomware group (also known as Agenda) has become one of the most prolific ransomware operations in 2025, according to a new report from Cisco Talos. The group is publishing data from over 40 victims per month on its leak site. The manufacturing sector is the most heavily targeted industry, accounting for 23% of all incidents, followed by professional services and wholesale trade. Talos researchers observed Qilin operators using the legitimate tool Cyberduck for data exfiltration and PsExec for lateral movement. The group also used standard Windows tools like notepad.exe to view sensitive data on compromised systems, likely as an evasion tactic.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A Cisco Talos report details a surge in attacks by the Qilin ransomware group in 2025, with the manufacturing sector being the hardest hit at 23% of all incidents.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> qilin-ransomware-surges-in-2025-with-manufacturing-sector-hit-hardest</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-surges-in-2025-with-manufacturing-sector-hit-hardest/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Conduent Data Breach: 10 Million+ Individuals' Personal &amp; Medical Data Exposed</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/government-contractor-conduent-breach-exposes-data-of-10-million/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/government-contractor-conduent-breach-exposes-data-of-10-million/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Conduent Data Breach: 10 Million+ Individuals' Personal &amp; Medical Data Exposed</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Conduent Business Services, a major contractor for U.S. government agencies, has disclosed a massive data breach impacting over 10 million individuals. The incident, which occurred between October 2024 and January 2025, involved an unauthorized third party gaining access to Conduent's network and exfiltrating files. The compromised data is highly sensitive, including names, Social Security numbers, medical information, and health insurance details. The breach has affected residents across numerous states, including Texas, Washington, and California, and has triggered a legal investigation by the law firm Edelson Lechtzin LLP into the company's data privacy practices.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Threat Intelligence, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Conduent data breach, government contractor breach, PII leak, PHI breach, Edelson Lechtzin LLP, identity theft, cybersecurity incident, data privacy</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Government contractor Conduent confirms a data breach exposed the personal and medical information, including Social Security numbers, of over 10 million individuals.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> government-contractor-conduent-breach-exposes-data-of-10-million</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/government-contractor-conduent-breach-exposes-data-of-10-million/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Qilin Ransomware Claims 700 Victims in 2025, Becoming Top Global Threat</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-surges-to-become-most-prolific-threat-of-2025/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-surges-to-become-most-prolific-threat-of-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Qilin Ransomware Claims 700 Victims in 2025, Becoming Top Global Threat</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Qilin ransomware group has dramatically escalated its activities in 2025, claiming over 700 attacks to become the year's most prolific ransomware operation. Operating a Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) model, the Russia-based group has far surpassed the activity of 2024's leader, RansomHub. A significant surge in Qilin's attacks followed the shutdown of the RansomHub operation in April 2025, suggesting a migration of affiliates. Qilin aggressively targets critical infrastructure sectors worldwide, including healthcare, finance, and government, using double-extortion tactics.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Analysis of the Qilin ransomware group, which has become the most active RaaS operation in 2025 with over 700 victims, targeting critical infrastructure globally.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> qilin-ransomware-surges-to-become-most-prolific-threat-of-2025</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/qilin-ransomware-surges-to-become-most-prolific-threat-of-2025/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Azure Down: Misconfiguration Triggers Global Microsoft Service Outage</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-azure-outage-disrupts-global-services-after-configuration-error/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-azure-outage-disrupts-global-services-after-configuration-error/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Azure Down: Misconfiguration Triggers Global Microsoft Service Outage</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A faulty configuration change in Microsoft's Azure Front Door (AFD) service on October 29-30, 2025, led to a multi-hour global outage. The incident caused widespread latency, timeouts, and connection failures for numerous Microsoft services, including Microsoft 365, Xbox Live, and Entra ID, as well as customer applications like Alaska Airlines' website. Microsoft engineers identified the inadvertent tenant configuration change as the root cause and initiated a rollback to restore services. The event highlights the systemic risk and fragility within globally interconnected cloud ecosystems, where a single non-malicious error can have a cascading, worldwide impact.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cloud Security, Cyberattack, Incident Response</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Microsoft Azure outage, Azure Front Door, cloud outage, Microsoft 365 down, global outage, configuration error, Alaska Airlines, cloud security, incident response</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A major Microsoft Azure outage on Oct 29-30, 2025, caused by a configuration error in Azure Front Door, disrupted global services like Microsoft 365 and Xbox Live.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> microsoft-azure-outage-disrupts-global-services-after-configuration-error</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-azure-outage-disrupts-global-services-after-configuration-error/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Incident Response</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Scattered Spider's Phishing Blitz Caused Millions in Damages to UK Retailers</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/scattered-spider-linked-to-major-uk-retail-breaches-in-phishing-report/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/scattered-spider-linked-to-major-uk-retail-breaches-in-phishing-report/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Scattered Spider's Phishing Blitz Caused Millions in Damages to UK Retailers</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new phishing report from KnowBe4 has attributed hundreds of millions in damages at major UK retailers like M&amp;S, Co-Op, and Harrods to the cybercrime group 'Scattered Spider'. The group utilizes a potent mix of social engineering, vishing (voice phishing), and MFA bombing to circumvent security controls. After breaching the companies, Scattered Spider launched secondary phishing campaigns impersonating the brands to steal customer credentials. The report also highlights a massive 449% increase in vishing attacks in 2025 and the growing use of AI-generated voices in callback scams, signaling a shift towards human-layer attacks.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Phishing, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Scattered Spider, phishing report, vishing, MFA bombing, MFA fatigue, KnowBe4, UK retail breach, social engineering, cybercrime</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A KnowBe4 report reveals the 'Scattered Spider' cybercrime group caused millions in damages to UK retailers using advanced vishing, social engineering, and MFA bombing tactics.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> scattered-spider-linked-to-major-uk-retail-breaches-in-phishing-report</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/scattered-spider-linked-to-major-uk-retail-breaches-in-phishing-report/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New 'Herodotus' Android Trojan Mimics Human Typing to Defeat Biometric Security</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/herodotus-android-malware-mimics-human-typing-to-bypass-security/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/herodotus-android-malware-mimics-human-typing-to-bypass-security/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New 'Herodotus' Android Trojan Mimics Human Typing to Defeat Biometric Security</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new Android banking trojan, named 'Herodotus,' is being sold as a Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) and is designed to evade modern behavioral biometric security. According to researchers at Threat Fabric, the malware gains full control of a device via Accessibility Service abuse. Its key innovation is the ability to 'humanize' fraudulent actions by simulating realistic typing, introducing random delays between keystrokes. This allows it to perform automated on-device fraud, such as transferring funds, while appearing as a legitimate user. The malware, spread via smishing, has been observed targeting banking users in Italy and Brazil.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Mobile Security, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Herodotus malware, Android banking trojan, Threat Fabric, MaaS, smishing, on-device fraud, behavioral biometrics, Accessibility Service abuse</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Researchers have discovered 'Herodotus,' a new Android banking trojan that mimics human typing with random delays to bypass behavioral biometric fraud detection systems.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> herodotus-android-malware-mimics-human-typing-to-bypass-security</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/herodotus-android-malware-mimics-human-typing-to-bypass-security/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Ad Giant Dentsu's Subsidiary Merkle Hit by Cyberattack, Staff and Client Data Exposed</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/dentsu-subsidiary-merkle-hit-by-cyberattack-exposing-data/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/dentsu-subsidiary-merkle-hit-by-cyberattack-exposing-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Ad Giant Dentsu's Subsidiary Merkle Hit by Cyberattack, Staff and Client Data Exposed</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Global advertising firm Dentsu has confirmed that its US-based customer experience management (CXM) subsidiary, Merkle, was the target of a cyberattack. The company detected 'abnormal activity' on Merkle's network and proactively shut down certain systems to contain the threat. An investigation has confirmed that the incident led to the exposure of both staff and sensitive client data. Merkle, a major player in the CXM industry, handles large volumes of customer data, making it a high-value target for threat actors. The full scope of the breach is still under investigation.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cyberattack, Data Breach, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Dentsu cyberattack, Merkle data breach, customer experience management, CXM security, advertising agency breach, supply chain attack, client data exposed</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Global advertising firm Dentsu confirmed its US subsidiary, Merkle, was hit by a cyberattack that exposed both staff and sensitive client data, prompting system shutdowns.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> dentsu-subsidiary-merkle-hit-by-cyberattack-exposing-data</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/dentsu-subsidiary-merkle-hit-by-cyberattack-exposing-data/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: EY Leaks 4TB+ SQL Database Packed with Corporate Secrets via Cloud Misconfiguration</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/consulting-giant-ey-exposes-4tb-sql-database-to-internet/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/consulting-giant-ey-exposes-4tb-sql-database-to-internet/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> EY Leaks 4TB+ SQL Database Packed with Corporate Secrets via Cloud Misconfiguration</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Consulting giant EY (Ernst &amp; Young) inadvertently exposed a massive, 4TB+ SQL Server backup file to the public internet due to a cloud storage misconfiguration. The unencrypted `.BAK` file, discovered by researchers at Neo Security, contained a treasure trove of highly sensitive internal data, including API keys, service account passwords, session tokens, and user credentials. The incident highlights the severe risks associated with cloud service misconfigurations, where tools designed for convenience can lead to catastrophic data exposure if not secured properly. Neo Security described the leak as equivalent to finding the 'master blueprint and physical keys to a vault.'</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Cloud Security, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> EY data leak, Ernst &amp; Young breach, cloud misconfiguration, SQL database exposed, Neo Security, cloud security posture management, CSPM, data exposure</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Consulting firm EY exposed a 4TB+ unencrypted SQL Server backup file containing API keys, passwords, and other sensitive data on the public internet due to a cloud misconfiguration.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> consulting-giant-ey-exposes-4tb-sql-database-to-internet</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/consulting-giant-ey-exposes-4tb-sql-database-to-internet/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: IncRansom Claims 20TB Data Heist from Evolve Mortgage Services</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/incransom-gang-claims-20tb-data-theft-from-evolve-mortgage-services/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/incransom-gang-claims-20tb-data-theft-from-evolve-mortgage-services/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> IncRansom Claims 20TB Data Heist from Evolve Mortgage Services</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The 'incransom' ransomware group has claimed responsibility for a significant data breach at Evolve Mortgage Services, listing the company on its dark web leak site on October 30, 2025. The attackers allege they have stolen over 20 terabytes of data, including 2 terabytes of databases containing sensitive PII such as Social Security numbers, client IDs, and full credit histories dating back to 2016. The group is using a pure data-theft extortion model, threatening to leak the data after claiming the company refused to negotiate. This incident highlights the ongoing threat of data extortion attacks against the U.S. financial services sector.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> incransom, Evolve Mortgage Services, ransomware, data theft, dark web leak, financial services breach, data extortion</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The incransom ransomware group has claimed a major data breach at Evolve Mortgage Services, alleging the theft of over 20TB of data including SSNs and credit histories.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> incransom-gang-claims-20tb-data-theft-from-evolve-mortgage-services</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/incransom-gang-claims-20tb-data-theft-from-evolve-mortgage-services/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: UK Proposes Ransomware Payment Ban as 'Nationally Significant' Cyberattacks Double</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-sees-alarming-rise-in-cyber-threats-proposes-ransomware-payment-ban/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-sees-alarming-rise-in-cyber-threats-proposes-ransomware-payment-ban/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> UK Proposes Ransomware Payment Ban as 'Nationally Significant' Cyberattacks Double</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The UK is facing an 'alarming' increase in cyber threats, with a GCHQ report revealing that 'nationally significant' cyberattacks more than doubled to 204 in the past year, costing the economy billions. High-profile ransomware attacks on companies like Marks &amp; Spencer and Jaguar Land Rover have inflicted massive financial damage. In response, the UK government is consulting on new legislation that includes a targeted ban on ransomware payments for public sector bodies and critical national infrastructure operators. The proposals aim to disrupt the ransomware business model and improve national threat intelligence through mandated incident reporting.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Ransomware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> UK ransomware ban, NCSC annual review, GCHQ report, cybersecurity legislation UK, ransomware payment, critical national infrastructure, Cybersecurity and Resilience Bill</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> In response to a GCHQ report showing UK cyberattacks have doubled, the government is consulting on new laws, including a targeted ban on ransomware payments for critical infrastructure.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> uk-sees-alarming-rise-in-cyber-threats-proposes-ransomware-payment-ban</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-sees-alarming-rise-in-cyber-threats-proposes-ransomware-payment-ban/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA: Patch Now! Critical, Actively Exploited RCE Flaw in Windows Server (WSUS)</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-active-exploitation-of-critical-wsus-vulnerability-cve-2025-59287/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-active-exploitation-of-critical-wsus-vulnerability-cve-2025-59287/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA: Patch Now! Critical, Actively Exploited RCE Flaw in Windows Server (WSUS)</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has issued an urgent alert for a critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability, CVE-2025-59287, in Microsoft's Windows Server Update Services (WSUS). The flaw is being actively exploited in the wild, allowing unauthenticated attackers to gain system-level privileges on vulnerable servers. A previous patch was incomplete, necessitating an out-of-band security update from Microsoft. CISA has added the vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog and is instructing organizations to apply the new patch immediately or take mitigation steps.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> CVE-2025-59287, CISA KEV, WSUS vulnerability, Windows Server exploit, remote code execution, Huntress, patch management, CISA alert</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA issues an urgent alert for CVE-2025-59287, a critical, actively exploited RCE vulnerability in Windows Server Update Services (WSUS), and urges immediate patching.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-warns-of-active-exploitation-of-critical-wsus-vulnerability-cve-2025-59287</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-active-exploitation-of-critical-wsus-vulnerability-cve-2025-59287/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New 'logins[.]zip' Infostealer Claims 99% Credential Theft in 12 Seconds Using Zero-Days</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-logins-zip-infostealer-service-uses-browser-exploits-for-rapid-theft/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-logins-zip-infostealer-service-uses-browser-exploits-for-rapid-theft/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New 'logins[.]zip' Infostealer Claims 99% Credential Theft in 12 Seconds Using Zero-Days</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) infostealer named 'logins[.]zip' is being sold on the clear web, boasting incredible speed and efficiency. According to a report from Hudson Rock, its authors claim it can exfiltrate 99% of passwords and cookies from a victim's machine in under 12 seconds. The stealer's key selling point is its alleged use of two Chromium zero-day exploits, which allow it to steal credentials without needing admin rights. The service, sold for $150/month, provides a browser-based builder for creating polymorphic stubs and targets logins, cookies, payment cards, and crypto wallets.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Threat Intelligence, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> logins.zip malware, infostealer MaaS, Chromium zero day, Hudson Rock, credential theft, Lumma stealer, RedLine stealer, malware as a service</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new Malware-as-a-Service infostealer called 'logins[.]zip' is being sold on the clear web, claiming to use Chromium zero-days to steal 99% of credentials in under 12 seconds.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> new-logins-zip-infostealer-service-uses-browser-exploits-for-rapid-theft</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-logins-zip-infostealer-service-uses-browser-exploits-for-rapid-theft/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: UK's NCSC Warns 'Nationally Significant' Cyber Attacks Have More Than Doubled</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-ncsc-reports-nationally-significant-cyber-attacks-doubled/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-ncsc-reports-nationally-significant-cyber-attacks-doubled/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> UK's NCSC Warns 'Nationally Significant' Cyber Attacks Have More Than Doubled</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The UK's National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) has released its 2025 Annual Review, revealing a stark increase in major cyber threats. The agency handled 204 'nationally significant' incidents in the past year, more than double the 89 from the previous year. Ransomware remains the most acute threat, particularly to the UK's Critical National Infrastructure (CNI). The report highlights a growing gap between the escalating threats from APTs and cybercriminals and the nation's collective defenses, prompting the NCSC to urge all UK businesses to make cyber resilience a board-level priority and adopt foundational security controls.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Regulatory, Policy and Compliance, Ransomware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The UK National Cyber Security Centre's (NCSC) 2025 annual review shows that nationally significant cyber attacks more than doubled to 204 in the past year, with ransomware being the top threat.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> uk-ncsc-reports-nationally-significant-cyber-attacks-doubled</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-ncsc-reports-nationally-significant-cyber-attacks-doubled/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>