<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:47:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/rss/last.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA Issues Directive Forcing Federal Agencies to Purge End-of-Life Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-removal-of-unsupported-edge-devices-from-federal-networks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-removal-of-unsupported-edge-devices-from-federal-networks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Issues Directive Forcing Federal Agencies to Purge End-of-Life Edge Devices</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has issued Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 26-02, a sweeping mandate requiring Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies to address the significant security risks posed by unsupported network edge devices. Announced on February 5, 2026, the directive establishes a multi-phase, 18-month timeline for agencies to inventory, update, and ultimately remove all hardware and software that have reached end-of-life (EOL) or end-of-support (EOS). CISA highlighted that these devices, including firewalls, VPNs, and routers, are being actively and consistently exploited by advanced persistent threat actors as initial access vectors into federal networks. The directive is a proactive measure to shrink the government's attack surface rather than a response to a single incident, reflecting a strategic shift to harden network infrastructure against widespread exploitation campaigns.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA issues Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 26-02, mandating federal agencies to remove all end-of-life (EOL) and end-of-support (EOS) network edge devices to combat exploitation by nation-state actors.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-mandates-removal-of-unsupported-edge-devices-from-federal-networks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-removal-of-unsupported-edge-devices-from-federal-networks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/cisa-mandates-removal-of-unsupported-edge-devices-from-federal-networks.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New '0APT' Extortion Group Fakes Data Breach in Bluff Attack on Australian Hospital</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fake-ransomware-group-0apt-bluffs-australian-hospital-in-extortion-attempt/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fake-ransomware-group-0apt-bluffs-australian-hospital-in-extortion-attempt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New '0APT' Extortion Group Fakes Data Breach in Bluff Attack on Australian Hospital</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new extortion group calling itself '0APT' has targeted Australia's Epworth HealthCare, claiming to have stolen 920GB of sensitive patient and financial data. The group listed the hospital on its darknet leak site on February 4, 2026, threatening to publish the data if a ransom was not paid. However, Epworth HealthCare conducted a thorough investigation with external cybersecurity experts and found "no verified evidence of any impact to our systems or data." Cybersecurity researchers have corroborated this, assessing that 0APT is likely a "fake" ransomware operation. The group's modus operandi involves posting a high volume of victims without providing credible proof of a breach, instead using empty files or random data streams. This tactic relies on psychological pressure and the threat of reputational damage to extort payment, representing a shift from technical intrusion to pure intimidation.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Cybersecurity researchers reveal that the '0APT' ransomware group is a fake operation using bluffs and psychological tactics to extort victims, as seen in a recent failed attempt against Australia's Epworth HealthCare.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> fake-ransomware-group-0apt-bluffs-australian-hospital-in-extortion-attempt</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fake-ransomware-group-0apt-bluffs-australian-hospital-in-extortion-attempt/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/fake-ransomware-group-0apt-bluffs-australian-hospital-in-extortion-attempt.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Russia's APT28 Exploits Office Zero-Day (CVE-2026-21509) Just Days After Patch</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/russian-apt28-exploits-microsoft-office-zero-day-cve-2026-21509/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/russian-apt28-exploits-microsoft-office-zero-day-cve-2026-21509/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Russia's APT28 Exploits Office Zero-Day (CVE-2026-21509) Just Days After Patch</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Russian state-sponsored threat group APT28, also known as Fancy Bear, has been observed actively exploiting a critical Microsoft Office zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2026-21509, a mere three days after Microsoft released an emergency patch on January 26, 2026. The vulnerability, a security feature bypass in Office's OLE handling, allows for remote code execution without user interaction when a malicious document is opened. The campaign, dubbed "Operation Neusploit," targets government, military, and transport organizations across Central and Eastern Europe with spear-phishing emails containing malicious RTF documents. The attack deploys two malware variants: a lightweight Outlook backdoor called 'MiniDoor' for email theft and a new dropper named 'PixyNetLoader' which loads a Covenant C2-based payload for long-term access. CISA has added the flaw to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, urging immediate patching.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Vulnerability, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Russian APT28 (Fancy Bear) is exploiting a critical Microsoft Office zero-day, CVE-2026-21509, in a widespread phishing campaign targeting European government and military entities just days after a patch was released.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> russian-apt28-exploits-microsoft-office-zero-day-cve-2026-21509</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/russian-apt28-exploits-microsoft-office-zero-day-cve-2026-21509/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/russian-apt28-exploits-microsoft-office-zero-day-cve-2026-21509.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Notepad++ Update Hijacked in Sophisticated Supply Chain Attack by Chinese APT</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/notepad-plus-plus-update-hijacked-in-supply-chain-attack-by-chinese-apt/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/notepad-plus-plus-update-hijacked-in-supply-chain-attack-by-chinese-apt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Notepad++ Update Hijacked in Sophisticated Supply Chain Attack by Chinese APT</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A sophisticated software supply chain attack, attributed with medium confidence to the Chinese APT group Lotus Blossom (aka Billbug), has compromised the update mechanism of the popular Notepad++ text editor. The campaign, which ran from June to December 2025, involved hijacking the application's update traffic to selectively redirect high-value targets to malicious servers. Instead of a widespread attack, the threat actors focused on specific organizations in government, finance, and IT across Southeast Asia and other regions. Compromised users were served a malicious installer that deployed a previously unknown backdoor called 'Chrysalis' and, in some cases, a Cobalt Strike Beacon. The breach did not affect the Notepad++ source code but compromised the distribution server, highlighting the significant risk of supply chain attacks even in trusted open-source software.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Threat Actor, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A sophisticated supply chain attack attributed to the Chinese APT group Lotus Blossom compromised the Notepad++ update infrastructure, selectively delivering a backdoor named 'Chrysalis' to high-value targets.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> notepad-plus-plus-update-hijacked-in-supply-chain-attack-by-chinese-apt</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/notepad-plus-plus-update-hijacked-in-supply-chain-attack-by-chinese-apt/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/notepad-plus-plus-update-hijacked-in-supply-chain-attack-by-chinese-apt.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: BridgePay Payment Gateway Hit by Ransomware, Causing Nationwide Outages</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/bridgepay-payment-platform-confirms-crippling-ransomware-attack/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/bridgepay-payment-platform-confirms-crippling-ransomware-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> BridgePay Payment Gateway Hit by Ransomware, Causing Nationwide Outages</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. payments platform BridgePay Network Solutions has confirmed it suffered a ransomware attack that initiated a "system-wide service disruption" on February 6, 2026. The attack has crippled the company's ability to process payments, causing significant downstream impact on its clients, which include retailers, restaurants, and municipal governments across the country. Many merchants have been forced to switch to cash-only operations. BridgePay has engaged cybersecurity experts and is collaborating with the FBI and the U.S. Secret Service. While the company stated that an initial forensic investigation shows no evidence that usable payment card data was compromised, it warned that the restoration process could be lengthy. The identity of the ransomware group responsible for the attack has not yet been disclosed.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> U.S. payment gateway BridgePay Network Solutions confirms a ransomware attack caused a system-wide service disruption, preventing merchants nationwide from processing card payments.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> bridgepay-payment-platform-confirms-crippling-ransomware-attack</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/bridgepay-payment-platform-confirms-crippling-ransomware-attack/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/bridgepay-payment-platform-confirms-crippling-ransomware-attack.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: KillSec Ransomware Group Claims Attack on Nigerian Tech Startup Getly</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/killsec-ransomware-gang-targets-nigerian-startup-getly/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/killsec-ransomware-gang-targets-nigerian-startup-getly/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> KillSec Ransomware Group Claims Attack on Nigerian Tech Startup Getly</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The ransomware group known as KillSec has claimed responsibility for a cyberattack on Getly, a Nigerian technology startup. On February 9, 2026, the group posted the claim on its platform, stating it had breached the company and exfiltrated sensitive data. KillSec has threatened to leak the stolen information if its unspecified ransom demands are not met. Getly, which operates the `getly.app` domain, has not yet publicly commented on the alleged breach, and the claims have not been independently verified. The incident highlights the global reach of ransomware gangs and the increasing risk they pose to startups and small businesses in emerging markets, not just large enterprises.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The KillSec ransomware group claims to have breached Nigerian tech startup Getly, threatening to leak sensitive data if their demands are not met. The attack is currently unverified.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> killsec-ransomware-gang-targets-nigerian-startup-getly</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/killsec-ransomware-gang-targets-nigerian-startup-getly/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/killsec-ransomware-gang-targets-nigerian-startup-getly.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Australia Post Phishing Scam Harvests Credit Card and OTP Data</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/widespread-phishing-campaign-impersonates-australia-post/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/widespread-phishing-campaign-impersonates-australia-post/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Australia Post Phishing Scam Harvests Credit Card and OTP Data</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A widespread phishing campaign is actively targeting Australians by impersonating Australia Post. Cybersecurity firm MailGuard intercepted the scam on February 9, 2026, which uses emails with the subject line "Parcel Awaiting Instructions." The emails claim a delivery has failed due to an incomplete address and trick recipients into clicking a link to pay a small, fraudulent shipping fee of 1.99 AUD. The link leads to a sophisticated, multi-stage credential harvesting site designed to look like an official Australia Post portal. The site first captures the victim's full credit card details and phone number, and then, in a final crucial step, prompts for the one-time passcode (OTP) sent to their mobile. This allows the attackers to authorize fraudulent transactions immediately. The sender's email address is a clear giveaway, and users are advised to be vigilant.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Phishing, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A widespread phishing campaign impersonating Australia Post is using fake delivery notifications to lure victims to a site that harvests credit card details, phone numbers, and one-time passcodes (OTPs).</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> widespread-phishing-campaign-impersonates-australia-post</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/widespread-phishing-campaign-impersonates-australia-post/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/widespread-phishing-campaign-impersonates-australia-post.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: AI Supply Chain Attack: Hundreds of Malicious 'Skills' on ClawHub Marketplace Steal Credentials</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/malicious-ai-skills-proliferate-on-clawhub-marketplace/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/malicious-ai-skills-proliferate-on-clawhub-marketplace/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> AI Supply Chain Attack: Hundreds of Malicious 'Skills' on ClawHub Marketplace Steal Credentials</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A significant software supply chain attack is targeting users of the OpenClaw AI assistant through its community marketplace, ClawHub. Security researchers have discovered hundreds of malicious 'skills'—add-ons that extend the AI's functionality—that have been published by threat actors. These skills masquerade as useful tools, such as wallet trackers or content summarizers, but their installation instructions trick users into downloading malware. The primary payloads include the Atomic Stealer infostealer for macOS and other backdoors and keyloggers for Windows. The attack leverages the trusted, open-source nature of the marketplace, which lacked a formal review process for submissions. In response to the discovery by KOI Security and SlowMist, the OpenClaw team has partnered with VirusTotal to automatically scan all skills uploaded to ClawHub to prevent further abuse.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Malware, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A major supply chain attack on the ClawHub marketplace for the OpenClaw AI assistant has been found to distribute hundreds of malicious 'skills' designed to install malware like Atomic Stealer.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> malicious-ai-skills-proliferate-on-clawhub-marketplace</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/malicious-ai-skills-proliferate-on-clawhub-marketplace/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/malicious-ai-skills-proliferate-on-clawhub-marketplace.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: 'Bloody Wolf' APT Deploys NetSupport RAT in Espionage Campaign</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/bloody-wolf-apt-targets-russia-and-uzbekistan-with-netsupport-rat/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/bloody-wolf-apt-targets-russia-and-uzbekistan-with-netsupport-rat/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> 'Bloody Wolf' APT Deploys NetSupport RAT in Espionage Campaign</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Security researchers have uncovered an active spear-phishing campaign attributed to the threat actor 'Bloody Wolf' (also tracked as Stan Ghouls). The campaign targets organizations primarily in Uzbekistan and Russia, with a focus on manufacturing, finance, and IT sectors, though government and other entities have also been targeted. The attackers use phishing emails with password-protected ZIP archives containing a malicious LNK file. When executed, this file downloads and installs the legitimate remote administration tool, NetSupport RAT, which gives the attackers full control over the victim's system. The motives appear to be mixed, pointing towards both financially motivated cybercrime and state-aligned cyber espionage. This campaign marks a shift in tooling for the group, which previously used the STRRAT malware.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Cyberattack, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The 'Bloody Wolf' (Stan Ghouls) threat actor is conducting a spear-phishing campaign against entities in Russia and Uzbekistan, using the NetSupport RAT for espionage and financial gain.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> bloody-wolf-apt-targets-russia-and-uzbekistan-with-netsupport-rat</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/bloody-wolf-apt-targets-russia-and-uzbekistan-with-netsupport-rat/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/bloody-wolf-apt-targets-russia-and-uzbekistan-with-netsupport-rat.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: China-Linked UNC3886 Hits All Major Singapore Telcos in Coordinated Zero-Day Attack</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/singapore-telcos-hit-by-coordinated-unc3886-espionage-campaign/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/singapore-telcos-hit-by-coordinated-unc3886-espionage-campaign/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> China-Linked UNC3886 Hits All Major Singapore Telcos in Coordinated Zero-Day Attack</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Singaporean authorities have revealed that all four of the nation's major telecommunication providers were targeted in a sophisticated and coordinated cyber espionage campaign. The attack is attributed to UNC3886, a Chinese-linked advanced persistent threat (APT) group known for targeting critical infrastructure. The attackers exploited a zero-day vulnerability in the telcos' perimeter firewalls to gain initial access. Once inside, the group stole a limited amount of technical data and used advanced techniques to evade detection. While the attackers have not yet penetrated the core networks, officials noted their capability to deploy tools that could disrupt internet and telecommunications services. In response, Singapore has launched one of its largest-ever coordinated cyber defense operations, involving government agencies and the affected telcos working together to hunt for the intruders and harden national infrastructure.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Cyberattack, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Singapore's major telecommunication providers were all targeted in a coordinated cyber espionage campaign by the China-linked APT group UNC3886, which exploited a zero-day firewall vulnerability.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> singapore-telcos-hit-by-coordinated-unc3886-espionage-campaign</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/singapore-telcos-hit-by-coordinated-unc3886-espionage-campaign/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/singapore-telcos-hit-by-coordinated-unc3886-espionage-campaign.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: European Commission Probes MDM Breach Following Ivanti Zero-Day Exploits</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/european-commission-probes-breach-of-mobile-device-management-system-ivanti/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/european-commission-probes-breach-of-mobile-device-management-system-ivanti/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> European Commission Probes MDM Breach Following Ivanti Zero-Day Exploits</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The European Commission is investigating a cyberattack on its mobile device management (MDM) system that exposed staff data. The incident's timing is critical, as it follows the recent disclosure of two severe zero-day vulnerabilities (CVE-2026-1281 and CVE-2026-1340) in Ivanti's Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM) product, which the Commission uses. These flaws allow unauthenticated remote code execution. While the Commission has not officially confirmed the link, other government agencies in the Netherlands and Finland have already disclosed breaches related to these specific Ivanti vulnerabilities. The Dutch Authority for the Protection of Personal Data had employee data accessed, and a Finnish government agency reported a breach that could affect up to 50,000 users. Security watchdog Shadowserver has identified over 50 compromised Ivanti EPMM servers globally, indicating a widespread and active exploitation campaign.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Data Breach, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The European Commission is investigating a staff data breach of its mobile device management (MDM) system, which occurred after the disclosure and widespread exploitation of two critical Ivanti EPMM zero-days.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> european-commission-probes-breach-of-mobile-device-management-system-ivanti</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/european-commission-probes-breach-of-mobile-device-management-system-ivanti/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/european-commission-probes-breach-of-mobile-device-management-system-ivanti.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: BeyondTrust Patches Critical 9.9 CVSS RCE Zero-Day in Remote Access Tools</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-9-9-cvss-zero-day-vulnerability-disclosed-in-beyondtrust-products/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-9-9-cvss-zero-day-vulnerability-disclosed-in-beyondtrust-products/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> BeyondTrust Patches Critical 9.9 CVSS RCE Zero-Day in Remote Access Tools</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>BeyondTrust has patched a critical zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2026-1731, affecting its self-hosted Remote Support (RS) and Privileged Remote Access (PRA) products. The flaw is a pre-authentication remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability with a CVSS score of 9.9, indicating extreme severity. It allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands on a vulnerable appliance by sending a specially crafted network request, requiring no user interaction. This could lead to a full server compromise. The vulnerability affects RS versions 25.3.1 and earlier, and PRA versions 24.3.4 and earlier. BeyondTrust has already secured its cloud instances, but is urging all on-premise customers to upgrade to the patched versions immediately. The flaw was discovered and responsibly disclosed by a security researcher.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> BeyondTrust has patched a critical 9.9 CVSS zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2026-1731, in its self-hosted remote access products that allows for unauthenticated remote code execution.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> critical-9-9-cvss-zero-day-vulnerability-disclosed-in-beyondtrust-products</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-9-9-cvss-zero-day-vulnerability-disclosed-in-beyondtrust-products/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/critical-9-9-cvss-zero-day-vulnerability-disclosed-in-beyondtrust-products.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: CRITICAL: Ivanti Patches Two Actively Exploited RCE Zero-Days in EPMM</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ivanti-patches-two-critical-actively-exploited-rce-flaws-in-epmm/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ivanti-patches-two-critical-actively-exploited-rce-flaws-in-epmm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CRITICAL: Ivanti Patches Two Actively Exploited RCE Zero-Days in EPMM</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Ivanti has released urgent security patches for two critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerabilities, CVE-2026-1281 and CVE-2026-1340, affecting its Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM) solution, formerly MobileIron Core. Both flaws are rated 9.8 out of 10 on the CVSS scale and are confirmed to be actively exploited in the wild as zero-days. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit these vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code on an affected appliance, granting them access to sensitive mobile device management data. Given the active exploitation, administrators are urged to apply the temporary RPM script patches immediately while awaiting a permanent fix in the upcoming version 12.8.0.0.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Urgent security alert: Ivanti has patched two critical, actively exploited RCE zero-day vulnerabilities (CVE-2026-1281, CVE-2026-1340) in its EPMM product. Immediate patching is required.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ivanti-patches-two-critical-actively-exploited-rce-flaws-in-epmm</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ivanti-patches-two-critical-actively-exploited-rce-flaws-in-epmm/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/ivanti-patches-two-critical-actively-exploited-rce-flaws-in-epmm.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA KEV Alert: Critical SmarterMail RCE Flaw (CVE-2026-24423) Actively Exploited in Ransomware Attacks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-smartermail-flaw-fueling-ransomware-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-smartermail-flaw-fueling-ransomware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA KEV Alert: Critical SmarterMail RCE Flaw (CVE-2026-24423) Actively Exploited in Ransomware Attacks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in SmarterMail, CVE-2026-24423, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog. The flaw, which has a CVSS score of 9.3, allows for unauthenticated RCE and is being actively weaponized by ransomware groups. The vulnerability exists in the `ConnectToHub` API endpoint, enabling attackers to execute arbitrary commands with system privileges. SmarterTools has released a patch (build 9511), and CISA has mandated that federal agencies apply it by February 26, 2026. This marks the third SmarterMail vulnerability added to the KEV list in two weeks, indicating a concentrated effort by threat actors to target the platform.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Ransomware, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA adds critical SmarterMail RCE vulnerability CVE-2026-24423 to its KEV catalog due to active exploitation in ransomware campaigns. Learn how to detect and mitigate this flaw.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-smartermail-flaw-fueling-ransomware-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-smartermail-flaw-fueling-ransomware-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-smartermail-flaw-fueling-ransomware-attacks.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Nationwide Outage: BridgePay Payment Gateway Confirms Ransomware Attack Crippled Production Systems</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-attack-cripples-bridgepay-payment-gateway-causing-nationwide-outages/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-attack-cripples-bridgepay-payment-gateway-causing-nationwide-outages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Nationwide Outage: BridgePay Payment Gateway Confirms Ransomware Attack Crippled Production Systems</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>U.S. payment gateway provider BridgePay Network Solutions has confirmed a ransomware attack was the cause of a massive service outage that began on February 6, 2026. The attack took down numerous production systems, including the BridgePay Gateway API, virtual terminals, and hosted payment pages, disrupting credit and debit card processing for merchants across the United States in sectors like retail, hospitality, and government. Many businesses were forced to revert to cash-only operations. BridgePay has engaged the FBI and U.S. Secret Service. While the company states that an initial investigation suggests no usable payment card data was exposed due to encryption, a timeline for full service restoration has not been provided, and the process is expected to be lengthy.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Cyberattack, Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> BridgePay Network Solutions, a major U.S. payment processor, confirms a ransomware attack is behind a nationwide outage affecting merchants in retail, hospitality, and government.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ransomware-attack-cripples-bridgepay-payment-gateway-causing-nationwide-outages</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-attack-cripples-bridgepay-payment-gateway-causing-nationwide-outages/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/ransomware-attack-cripples-bridgepay-payment-gateway-causing-nationwide-outages.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA Issues Directive 26-02, Mandating Removal of End-of-Support Edge Devices from Federal Networks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-removal-of-unsupported-edge-devices-from-federal-networks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-removal-of-unsupported-edge-devices-from-federal-networks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Issues Directive 26-02, Mandating Removal of End-of-Support Edge Devices from Federal Networks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has issued Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 26-02, a mandate requiring U.S. federal civilian agencies to identify, and ultimately decommission, all network edge devices that have reached their end-of-support (EOS) date. The directive addresses the 'disproportionate and unacceptable risks' posed by unpatched hardware and software, which are frequently targeted by advanced threat actors. The BOD establishes a multi-phase timeline: agencies have three months to inventory devices on CISA's EOS list, 12 months to decommission devices already past their EOS date, and 18 months to replace all identified EOS equipment. This move aims to reduce the federal government's attack surface and drive down technical debt.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 3 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA issues Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 26-02, compelling U.S. federal agencies to remove all end-of-support (EOS) network edge devices to mitigate security risks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-mandates-removal-of-unsupported-edge-devices-from-federal-networks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-removal-of-unsupported-edge-devices-from-federal-networks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/cisa-mandates-removal-of-unsupported-edge-devices-from-federal-networks.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Notepad++ Supply Chain Attack Attributed to Chinese APT 'Lotus Blossom' (Billbug)</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/notepad-plus-plus-supply-chain-attack-attributed-to-chinese-apt-group-lotus-blossom/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/notepad-plus-plus-supply-chain-attack-attributed-to-chinese-apt-group-lotus-blossom/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Notepad++ Supply Chain Attack Attributed to Chinese APT 'Lotus Blossom' (Billbug)</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A sophisticated supply chain attack that hijacked the update mechanism of the popular Notepad++ text editor has been attributed with medium confidence to 'Lotus Blossom' (also known as Billbug), a China-linked advanced persistent threat (APT) group. The attack, which ran from June to December 2025, compromised Notepad++'s hosting provider, allowing the attackers to selectively redirect update traffic for older, vulnerable versions of the software. The threat actors deployed a custom backdoor named 'Chrysalis' and utilized a multi-stage infection chain involving Metasploit and Cobalt Strike. The Notepad++ developer has since secured the update infrastructure and patched the vulnerability in version 8.8.9.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Threat Actor, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A sophisticated supply chain attack on Notepad++ has been attributed to the Chinese APT group Lotus Blossom (Billbug), which deployed a custom 'Chrysalis' backdoor.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> notepad-plus-plus-supply-chain-attack-attributed-to-chinese-apt-group-lotus-blossom</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/notepad-plus-plus-supply-chain-attack-attributed-to-chinese-apt-group-lotus-blossom/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/notepad-plus-plus-supply-chain-attack-attributed-to-chinese-apt-group-lotus-blossom.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: EDR-Killer Malware Weaponizes Decade-Old EnCase Driver in BYOVD Attacks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/attackers-weaponize-decade-old-encase-driver-to-terminate-edr-products/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/attackers-weaponize-decade-old-encase-driver-to-terminate-edr-products/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> EDR-Killer Malware Weaponizes Decade-Old EnCase Driver in BYOVD Attacks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Threat actors are using a new EDR-killing malware that leverages a 'Bring Your Own Vulnerable Driver' (BYOVD) technique to disable endpoint security products. Researchers at Huntress discovered the malware during an intrusion that began with compromised SonicWall SSL VPN credentials. The attackers abuse `EnPortv.sys`, a legitimate but long-revoked kernel driver from Guidance Software's EnCase forensic toolkit. Despite its certificate being revoked in 2010, a gap in Windows' driver signature enforcement allows it to be loaded, granting the attackers kernel-level privileges. The malware uses these privileges to terminate 59 different processes associated with major EDR vendors like CrowdStrike, SentinelOne, and Microsoft, clearing the way for ransomware deployment.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Ransomware, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new EDR-killing malware uses a 'Bring Your Own Vulnerable Driver' (BYOVD) technique, abusing a revoked driver from EnCase ('EnPortv.sys') to disable security products.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> attackers-weaponize-decade-old-encase-driver-to-terminate-edr-products</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/attackers-weaponize-decade-old-encase-driver-to-terminate-edr-products/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/attackers-weaponize-decade-old-encase-driver-to-terminate-edr-products.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: U.S. Finalizes Ban on Chinese and Russian Tech in Connected Vehicles, Forcing Massive Supply Chain Overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-finalizes-rules-to-ban-chinese-and-russian-tech-from-connected-vehicles/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-finalizes-rules-to-ban-chinese-and-russian-tech-from-connected-vehicles/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> U.S. Finalizes Ban on Chinese and Russian Tech in Connected Vehicles, Forcing Massive Supply Chain Overhaul</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The United States has finalized new regulations from the Commerce Department that will ban hardware and software from China and Russia in connected vehicles sold in the U.S. The rules are designed to mitigate national security risks, preventing foreign adversaries from collecting sensitive data or manipulating vehicle functions. The ban will be phased in, starting with software for the 2027 model year and extending to hardware by 2029. The auto industry is facing what is being called 'one of the most consequential and complex auto regulations in decades,' forcing a massive and difficult overhaul of their deeply embedded global software and hardware supply chains.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Supply Chain Attack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The U.S. has finalized new rules to ban hardware and software from China and Russia in connected vehicles, citing national security risks and forcing a major supply chain shift.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> us-finalizes-rules-to-ban-chinese-and-russian-tech-from-connected-vehicles</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-finalizes-rules-to-ban-chinese-and-russian-tech-from-connected-vehicles/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/us-finalizes-rules-to-ban-chinese-and-russian-tech-from-connected-vehicles.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: ShinyHunters Bypasses MFA Using Vishing; Breaches Panera Bread, Match Group, Harvard University</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/shinyhunters-group-bypasses-mfa-in-widespread-social-engineering-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/shinyhunters-group-bypasses-mfa-in-widespread-social-engineering-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> ShinyHunters Bypasses MFA Using Vishing; Breaches Panera Bread, Match Group, Harvard University</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The cybercrime group ShinyHunters is conducting a large-scale data breach campaign by using voice-phishing (vishing) and social engineering to defeat multi-factor authentication (MFA). Attackers impersonate internal IT staff, tricking employees into visiting a credential harvesting site and providing their username, password, and real-time MFA code. This allows the attackers to enroll their own device and gain persistent access. Recent high-profile victims include Panera Bread (5.1 million records leaked), Match Group (Tinder, Hinge), Bumble, and Harvard University's alumni department (115,000 records exposed). The group, operating as 'Scattered LAPSUS$ Hunters,' has reportedly prepared infrastructure to target over 100 additional organizations.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Phishing, Data Breach, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The ShinyHunters cybercrime group is using sophisticated voice-phishing (vishing) attacks to bypass MFA and breach major companies like Panera Bread, Match Group, and Harvard University.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> shinyhunters-group-bypasses-mfa-in-widespread-social-engineering-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/shinyhunters-group-bypasses-mfa-in-widespread-social-engineering-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/shinyhunters-group-bypasses-mfa-in-widespread-social-engineering-attacks.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: APT28 Exploits Patched Office Flaw (CVE-2026-21509) in Espionage Campaign Days After Fix</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apt28-exploits-freshly-patched-office-flaw-in-espionage-campaign/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apt28-exploits-freshly-patched-office-flaw-in-espionage-campaign/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> APT28 Exploits Patched Office Flaw (CVE-2026-21509) in Espionage Campaign Days After Fix</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Russian state-sponsored group APT28 (Fancy Bear) is actively exploiting a recently patched Microsoft Office vulnerability, CVE-2026-21509, just days after an emergency fix was released. The espionage campaign, dubbed 'Operation Neusploit,' targets government, military, and transport organizations in Europe with sophisticated phishing lures. The flaw is a security feature bypass that attackers trigger with malicious RTF documents. The multi-stage infection chain deploys backdoors like 'MiniDoor' for email exfiltration and a C++ implant called 'BeardShell,' using legitimate cloud services like filen.io for C2 to evade detection. Microsoft released an out-of-band patch on January 26, 2026, and organizations are urged to apply it immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Vulnerability, Phishing</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Russian APT28 (Fancy Bear) is actively exploiting the recently patched Microsoft Office vulnerability CVE-2026-21509 in a widespread espionage campaign targeting Europe.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> apt28-exploits-freshly-patched-office-flaw-in-espionage-campaign</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apt28-exploits-freshly-patched-office-flaw-in-espionage-campaign/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/apt28-exploits-freshly-patched-office-flaw-in-espionage-campaign.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Global Cybersecurity Regulations Tighten as Hong Kong, Europe Push Stricter Breach Reporting Rules</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/global-cybersecurity-regulations-tighten-with-new-mandates-in-hong-kong-and-europe/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/global-cybersecurity-regulations-tighten-with-new-mandates-in-hong-kong-and-europe/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Global Cybersecurity Regulations Tighten as Hong Kong, Europe Push Stricter Breach Reporting Rules</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A global trend towards stricter cybersecurity regulation is accelerating. Hong Kong has announced plans to revive amendments to its Personal Data Privacy Ordinance (PDPO) to include mandatory data breach reporting and administrative fines. This follows recent moves in the U.S. that mandate rapid incident disclosure for critical infrastructure and public companies. Concurrently, enforcement of Europe's NIS2 directive and the Digital Operational Resilience Act (DORA) is intensifying, compelling financial services and critical sector organizations to adopt more dynamic, decision-driven incident response frameworks and standardized reporting. The European Commission has also proposed a new Cybersecurity Act (CSA2) to harmonize ICT supply chain security.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A global trend towards stricter cybersecurity regulation is accelerating, with new mandatory data breach reporting rules planned in Hong Kong and escalating enforcement of NIS2 and DORA in Europe.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> global-cybersecurity-regulations-tighten-with-new-mandates-in-hong-kong-and-europe</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/global-cybersecurity-regulations-tighten-with-new-mandates-in-hong-kong-and-europe/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/global-cybersecurity-regulations-tighten-with-new-mandates-in-hong-kong-and-europe.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: China-Linked APT 'Amaranth-Dragon' Targets Southeast Asian Governments with New RAT</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/chinese-apt-amaranth-dragon-targets-southeast-asian-governments/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/chinese-apt-amaranth-dragon-targets-southeast-asian-governments/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> China-Linked APT 'Amaranth-Dragon' Targets Southeast Asian Governments with New RAT</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A China-linked cyber-espionage group, newly dubbed 'Amaranth-Dragon,' has been conducting targeted campaigns against government and law enforcement agencies across Southeast Asia. A report from Check Point Research reveals the group has significant operational and toolset overlaps with the notorious APT41. Amaranth-Dragon has demonstrated agility by rapidly weaponizing new vulnerabilities, such as a flaw in WinRAR (CVE-2025-8088), less than ten days after its disclosure. The group uses phishing emails and legitimate cloud services like Dropbox for initial access, deploying custom loaders and the Havoc C2 Framework. More recently, they have added a new Telegram-based RAT, 'TGAmaranth RAT,' to their arsenal.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Malware, Phishing</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new China-linked APT, Amaranth-Dragon, is targeting government and law enforcement in Southeast Asia, showing overlaps with APT41 and rapidly weaponizing new vulnerabilities.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> chinese-apt-amaranth-dragon-targets-southeast-asian-governments</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/chinese-apt-amaranth-dragon-targets-southeast-asian-governments/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/chinese-apt-amaranth-dragon-targets-southeast-asian-governments.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: European Commission Contains Cyberattack on its Mobile Device Management (MDM) System</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/european-commission-contains-cyberattack-on-mobile-device-management-system/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/european-commission-contains-cyberattack-on-mobile-device-management-system/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> European Commission Contains Cyberattack on its Mobile Device Management (MDM) System</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The European Commission disclosed on February 5, 2026, that it had identified and contained a cyberattack against its central infrastructure for managing mobile devices. The attack, detected on January 30, was reportedly contained and the system cleaned within nine hours. The Commission stated that the incident may have resulted in unauthorized access to some staff names and mobile numbers, but there is no evidence that any mobile devices themselves were compromised. The incident comes shortly after the Commission proposed a new, comprehensive cybersecurity package (CSA2) to strengthen security across the EU.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cyberattack, Incident Response, Mobile Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 3 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The European Commission disclosed it had identified and contained a cyberattack on its central mobile device management (MDM) infrastructure, which may have exposed some staff data.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> european-commission-contains-cyberattack-on-mobile-device-management-system</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/european-commission-contains-cyberattack-on-mobile-device-management-system/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/european-commission-contains-cyberattack-on-mobile-device-management-system.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Incident Response</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Malicious VS Code Extension 'ClawdBot Agent' Deployed ScreenConnect RAT via Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/malicious-clawdbot-agent-in-vs-code-marketplace-deployed-rat-malware/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/malicious-clawdbot-agent-in-vs-code-marketplace-deployed-rat-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Malicious VS Code Extension 'ClawdBot Agent' Deployed ScreenConnect RAT via Marketplace</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A malicious extension named 'ClawdBot Agent' was discovered in the official Visual Studio Code Marketplace, impersonating a popular AI coding assistant to trick developers. The trojanized extension was fully functional, helping it evade suspicion while its malicious payload executed in the background upon VS Code launch. The attack chain fetched a remote configuration file that initiated the deployment of a weaponized version of the legitimate remote support tool, ConnectWise ScreenConnect, effectively turning it into a Remote Access Tool (RAT). This gave attackers full remote control over compromised developer machines. The extension was quickly removed by Microsoft, but the incident highlights the growing risk of supply chain attacks targeting developer ecosystems.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Malware, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A malicious VS Code Marketplace extension, 'ClawdBot Agent,' impersonated an AI assistant to trick developers into installing a RAT, giving attackers full remote control.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> malicious-clawdbot-agent-in-vs-code-marketplace-deployed-rat-malware</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/malicious-clawdbot-agent-in-vs-code-marketplace-deployed-rat-malware/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/malicious-clawdbot-agent-in-vs-code-marketplace-deployed-rat-malware.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: EU Proposes Revised Cybersecurity Act to Bolster Supply Chain Security &amp; ENISA's Role</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/european-commission-proposes-revisions-to-strengthen-eu-cybersecurity-act/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/european-commission-proposes-revisions-to-strengthen-eu-cybersecurity-act/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> EU Proposes Revised Cybersecurity Act to Bolster Supply Chain Security &amp; ENISA's Role</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The European Commission has introduced a new cybersecurity package that includes a proposal for a revised Cybersecurity Act (CSA) and targeted amendments to the NIS2 Directive. The initiative aims to strengthen the EU's collective resilience against cyber threats by establishing a framework for ICT supply chain security, promoting 'cyber-secure by design' principles through certification, and enhancing the role of ENISA, the EU's cybersecurity agency. The amendments to NIS2 seek to clarify rules on jurisdiction and streamline ransomware incident data collection. Once adopted, member states will have one year to transpose the new provisions into national law.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Supply Chain Attack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The European Commission has proposed a revised EU Cybersecurity Act and amendments to the NIS2 Directive to strengthen ICT supply chain security, promote 'secure by design', and enhance ENISA's role.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> european-commission-proposes-revisions-to-strengthen-eu-cybersecurity-act</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/european-commission-proposes-revisions-to-strengthen-eu-cybersecurity-act/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/european-commission-proposes-revisions-to-strengthen-eu-cybersecurity-act.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: CISA Adds Critical SmarterMail RCE Flaw to KEV Catalog Amid Active Ransomware Attacks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-smartermail-rce-in-ransomware-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-smartermail-rce-in-ransomware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Adds Critical SmarterMail RCE Flaw to KEV Catalog Amid Active Ransomware Attacks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in SmarterTools' SmarterMail, CVE-2026-24423, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog. The flaw, which allows for unauthenticated RCE, is being actively weaponized by ransomware operators. The vulnerability stems from a missing authentication check in an API endpoint, enabling attackers to execute arbitrary commands on vulnerable email servers. CISA has directed all federal agencies to apply patches by February 26, 2026, and strongly urges all organizations using the affected software to update immediately to mitigate the significant risk of compromise.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Ransomware, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA warns of active ransomware attacks exploiting a critical unauthenticated RCE vulnerability (CVE-2026-24423) in SmarterMail. Learn about the flaw and apply patches immediately.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-smartermail-rce-in-ransomware-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-smartermail-rce-in-ransomware-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://cyber.netsecops.io/images/og-image/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-smartermail-rce-in-ransomware-attacks.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>