<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:05:28 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: React2Shell RCE Flaw (CVSS 10.0) Under Mass Exploitation by State Actors and Cybercriminals</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/widespread-exploitation-of-critical-react2shell-vulnerability-triggers-urgent-patching/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/widespread-exploitation-of-critical-react2shell-vulnerability-triggers-urgent-patching/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> React2Shell RCE Flaw (CVSS 10.0) Under Mass Exploitation by State Actors and Cybercriminals</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A critical, unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in React Server Components, tracked as CVE-2025-55182 and dubbed 'React2Shell,' is being actively and widely exploited. With a CVSS score of 10.0, the flaw allows attackers to take full control of vulnerable servers, including those using popular frameworks like Next.js. Microsoft and Google have observed hundreds of compromises, with threat actors ranging from Chinese state-sponsored espionage groups to financially motivated criminals. Attackers are deploying Linux backdoors like KSwapDoor, crypto miners such as XMRig, and stealing cloud credentials for Azure, AWS, and GCP. Urgent patching is required as exploitation began as early as December 5, 2025.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Cyberattack, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> CVE-2025-55182, React2Shell, React Server Components vulnerability, Next.js exploit, remote code execution, KSwapDoor malware, UNC6600, CVSS 10.0, cybersecurity alert, patch management</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Urgent alert on CVE-2025-55182 (React2Shell), a critical 10.0 CVSS RCE vulnerability in React Server Components actively exploited by nation-states and criminals. Learn how to detect and mitigate the threat.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> widespread-exploitation-of-critical-react2shell-vulnerability-triggers-urgent-patching</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/widespread-exploitation-of-critical-react2shell-vulnerability-triggers-urgent-patching/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: AI Adoption Fuels 'Massive' Cloud Attack Surface Expansion, Palo Alto Networks Report Warns</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/palo-alto-networks-report-ai-driving-massive-expansion-of-cloud-attack-surface/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/palo-alto-networks-report-ai-driving-massive-expansion-of-cloud-attack-surface/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> AI Adoption Fuels 'Massive' Cloud Attack Surface Expansion, Palo Alto Networks Report Warns</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Palo Alto Networks' 2025 'State of Cloud Security Report' reveals that the rapid adoption of AI is creating an unprecedented expansion of the cloud attack surface. The study, surveying 2,800 security leaders, found that 99% of organizations have had their AI systems attacked in the last year. The use of generative AI in coding is producing insecure code faster than security teams can remediate it, creating a significant risk gap. API attacks have surged by 41% year-over-year, and lenient identity and access management (IAM) remains a top vulnerability. The report calls for a unified, platform-based approach to cloud security to counter AI-weaponized threats.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cloud Security, Threat Intelligence, Policy and Compliance</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> cloud security report, AI security, Palo Alto Networks, cloud attack surface, API attacks, generative AI risks, IAM security, CNAPP</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Palo Alto Networks' 2025 cloud security report finds that rapid AI adoption is creating a massive surge in cloud risks, with 99% of organizations reporting attacks on their AI systems.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> palo-alto-networks-report-ai-driving-massive-expansion-of-cloud-attack-surface</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/palo-alto-networks-report-ai-driving-massive-expansion-of-cloud-attack-surface/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: French Interior Ministry Confirms Cyberattack Compromised Email Servers</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/french-interior-ministry-confirms-cyberattack-on-email-servers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/french-interior-ministry-confirms-cyberattack-on-email-servers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> French Interior Ministry Confirms Cyberattack Compromised Email Servers</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The French Ministry of the Interior has confirmed its email servers were compromised in a cyberattack detected between December 11 and 12, 2025. Interior Minister Laurent Nuñez stated that attackers stole staff email passwords, allowing them to access an unknown number of document files. While the government is still assessing the scale, a hacker group named 'Indra' has claimed, without evidence, to have exfiltrated police files on 16.4 million citizens. In response, the ministry is rolling out two-factor authentication and resetting passwords. The attack on the high-value government target, which oversees national police and security, has raised speculation of nation-state involvement, with groups like APT28 being considered.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Cyberattack, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> French Interior Ministry hack, cyberattack France, government data breach, Indra hacker group, APT28, email server compromise, MFA, Laurent Nuñez</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The French Ministry of the Interior confirms a major cyberattack compromised its email servers, leading to a data breach. Attackers stole credentials and accessed files, with investigations ongoing.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> french-interior-ministry-confirms-cyberattack-on-email-servers</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/french-interior-ministry-confirms-cyberattack-on-email-servers/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA Adds Actively Exploited Fortinet SSO Flaw to KEV Catalog, Urges Immediate Patching</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-actively-exploited-fortinet-sso-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-actively-exploited-fortinet-sso-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Adds Actively Exploited Fortinet SSO Flaw to KEV Catalog, Urges Immediate Patching</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a critical Fortinet vulnerability, CVE-2025-59718, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, indicating active attacks in the wild. The flaw, rated 9.1 CVSS, allows an unauthenticated attacker to bypass FortiCloud single sign-on (SSO) authentication on multiple products, including FortiOS and FortiProxy, by sending a crafted SAML message. Security firm Arctic Wolf observed attackers exploiting the flaw within days of its disclosure to export device configurations and harvest credentials. CISA has mandated that federal agencies patch by December 23, 2025, and strongly advises all organizations to apply updates or disable the feature immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> CVE-2025-59718, CISA KEV, Fortinet vulnerability, FortiCloud SSO exploit, authentication bypass, FortiOS patch, Arctic Wolf, cybersecurity alert</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA adds critical Fortinet SSO bypass vulnerability CVE-2025-59718 to its KEV catalog due to active exploitation. Learn how to patch affected FortiOS, FortiProxy, and FortiWeb devices now.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-adds-actively-exploited-fortinet-sso-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-actively-exploited-fortinet-sso-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New 'ConsentFix' Phishing Attack Hijacks Microsoft Accounts, Bypassing MFA via Azure CLI Abuse</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-consentfix-phishing-attack-bypasses-mfa-to-hijack-microsoft-accounts/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-consentfix-phishing-attack-bypasses-mfa-to-hijack-microsoft-accounts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New 'ConsentFix' Phishing Attack Hijacks Microsoft Accounts, Bypassing MFA via Azure CLI Abuse</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A novel and sophisticated phishing attack dubbed 'ConsentFix' allows attackers to hijack Microsoft accounts without stealing passwords or bypassing multi-factor authentication (MFA). Discovered by Push Security, the browser-native attack tricks users into completing a fake verification process that involves copying a URL containing a sensitive OAuth authorization code from their browser's address bar and pasting it into the attacker's phishing page. The attacker then uses this code to authenticate as the user via the legitimate and trusted Microsoft Azure Command-Line Interface (CLI). Because the Azure CLI is a first-party app, it bypasses many consent restrictions, granting the attacker full account access. The technique is active and circumvents even phishing-resistant authentication like passkeys.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Phishing, Cloud Security, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> ConsentFix attack, ClickFix, OAuth phishing, Azure CLI exploit, MFA bypass, Microsoft account hijack, Push Security, browser-native attack</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new 'ConsentFix' phishing attack bypasses MFA to hijack Microsoft accounts by tricking users into pasting an OAuth authorization code, which is then used with the trusted Azure CLI.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> new-consentfix-phishing-attack-bypasses-mfa-to-hijack-microsoft-accounts</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-consentfix-phishing-attack-bypasses-mfa-to-hijack-microsoft-accounts/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New Zealand Launches Massive Public Alert, Warning 26,000 Citizens of Lumma Stealer Malware Infections</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-zealand-warns-26000-citizens-of-lumma-stealer-malware-infections/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-zealand-warns-26000-citizens-of-lumma-stealer-malware-infections/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New Zealand Launches Massive Public Alert, Warning 26,000 Citizens of Lumma Stealer Malware Infections</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>In a first-of-its-kind campaign, New Zealand's National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) is emailing approximately 26,000 people to warn them of potential infection by the Lumma Stealer malware. The potent information-stealing software targets Windows devices to covertly harvest sensitive data, including passwords, browser credentials, banking details, and cryptocurrency wallets. Officials have confirmed that some of the stolen credentials were linked to government and banking systems, heightening the risk of fraud. The NCSC's mass notification directs affected individuals to a government website with instructions for malware removal and improving account security.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Phishing, Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Lumma Stealer, New Zealand malware, NCSC alert, information stealer, password theft, cybersecurity New Zealand, Windows malware, data breach</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> New Zealand's National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) warns 26,000 citizens of potential infection by Lumma Stealer, a potent info-stealing malware targeting Windows devices for sensitive data.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> new-zealand-warns-26000-citizens-of-lumma-stealer-malware-infections</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-zealand-warns-26000-citizens-of-lumma-stealer-malware-infections/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: MITRE Extends D3FEND Cybersecurity Framework to Operational Technology (OT)</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/mitre-extends-d3fend-cybersecurity-framework-to-operational-technology-ot/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/mitre-extends-d3fend-cybersecurity-framework-to-operational-technology-ot/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> MITRE Extends D3FEND Cybersecurity Framework to Operational Technology (OT)</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>MITRE has officially extended its D3FEND cybersecurity framework to include Operational Technology (OT), providing a standardized knowledge base of defensive techniques for cyber-physical systems. Announced on December 16, 2025, the NSA-funded initiative aims to create a common language for securing critical infrastructure in sectors like energy, manufacturing, and defense. As OT systems become increasingly connected to IT networks, D3FEND for OT provides a structured ontology of countermeasures tailored to the unique components and risks of industrial environments, mapping defensive techniques to threats against controllers, sensors, and actuators.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Industrial Control Systems, Policy and Compliance, Security Operations</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> MITRE D3FEND, D3FEND for OT, Operational Technology security, ICS cybersecurity, cyber-physical systems, critical infrastructure protection, defensive cybersecurity, NSA</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> MITRE extends its D3FEND cybersecurity framework to include Operational Technology (OT), creating a standardized knowledge base for defending critical infrastructure and industrial control systems.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> mitre-extends-d3fend-cybersecurity-framework-to-operational-technology-ot</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/mitre-extends-d3fend-cybersecurity-framework-to-operational-technology-ot/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Apple and Google Issue Global Warnings Over Mercenary Spyware Attacks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apple-and-google-warn-global-users-of-mercenary-spyware-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apple-and-google-warn-global-users-of-mercenary-spyware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Apple and Google Issue Global Warnings Over Mercenary Spyware Attacks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Apple and Google have issued a new round of threat notifications to users across the globe, warning them of targeted attacks by state-sponsored and mercenary spyware groups. Google's alert on December 3rd specifically called out the continued operations of Intellexa, a sanctioned surveillance vendor, and its 'Predator' spyware, which is being delivered via new zero-day exploits. Google warned several hundred users in countries like Pakistan, Egypt, and Saudi Arabia. Apple also sent a batch of warnings on December 2nd to users in over 150 countries, continuing its policy of notifying high-risk individuals such as journalists and activists who are prime targets for such sophisticated surveillance.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Malware, Mobile Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> mercenary spyware, Predator spyware, Intellexa, Apple threat notification, Google spyware warning, state-sponsored hacking, zero-day exploit, mobile security</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Apple and Google issue a new wave of global threat notifications, warning high-risk users of attacks by mercenary spyware groups like Intellexa and its 'Predator' spyware.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> apple-and-google-warn-global-users-of-mercenary-spyware-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apple-and-google-warn-global-users-of-mercenary-spyware-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Push Security Launches Tool to Block Malicious 'ClickFix' Copy-Paste Attacks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/push-security-launches-tool-to-block-clickfix-malicious-copy-paste-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/push-security-launches-tool-to-block-clickfix-malicious-copy-paste-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Push Security Launches Tool to Block Malicious 'ClickFix' Copy-Paste Attacks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Push Security has launched a new 'malicious copy-and-paste detection' feature to combat the rapidly growing threat of 'ClickFix' style attacks. Announced on December 17, 2025, the browser-based tool is designed to stop social engineering attacks where users are tricked into copying malicious code from a website and pasting it into a terminal or command prompt. With reports of a 517% surge in such attacks, the new feature works by analyzing copy events in the browser, blocking malicious scripts from being copied to the clipboard, and effectively disarming the attack before the payload can be executed by the user.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Security Operations, Phishing, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Push Security, ClickFix attack, malicious copy and paste, browser security, social engineering, phishing prevention, cybersecurity tool</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 3 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Push Security launches a new malicious copy-and-paste detection feature to block 'ClickFix' social engineering attacks, where users are tricked into running malicious code from their browser.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> push-security-launches-tool-to-block-clickfix-malicious-copy-paste-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/push-security-launches-tool-to-block-clickfix-malicious-copy-paste-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: 'Operation MoneyMount-ISO' Phishing Campaign Deploys Phantom Stealer via Malicious ISOs</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/operation-moneymount-iso-phishing-campaign-deploys-phantom-stealer/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/operation-moneymount-iso-phishing-campaign-deploys-phantom-stealer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> 'Operation MoneyMount-ISO' Phishing Campaign Deploys Phantom Stealer via Malicious ISOs</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A financially motivated, Russian-language phishing campaign dubbed 'Operation MoneyMount-ISO' is actively targeting finance and accounting departments to deploy the Phantom information-stealing malware. According to researchers at Seqrite Labs, the attack uses emails with fake payment confirmations that contain a malicious ISO disk image file. This technique is designed to bypass email security controls. When the user opens the ISO, it mounts a virtual drive with a disguised executable. Running this file triggers a memory-resident infection chain that deploys Phantom Stealer, which then harvests browser credentials, crypto wallets, and other sensitive data for exfiltration.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Phishing, Malware, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Phantom Stealer, Operation MoneyMount-ISO, ISO phishing, Seqrite Labs, information stealer, malware campaign, finance department attack, email security</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A Russian-language phishing campaign, 'Operation MoneyMount-ISO,' uses malicious ISO files to deploy Phantom Stealer malware, targeting finance departments to steal credentials and crypto wallets.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> operation-moneymount-iso-phishing-campaign-deploys-phantom-stealer</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/operation-moneymount-iso-phishing-campaign-deploys-phantom-stealer/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Storm-0249 Evolves: Access Broker Now Deploys Ransomware with Advanced Stealth Tactics</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/access-broker-storm-0249-shifts-to-advanced-ransomware-delivery/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/access-broker-storm-0249-shifts-to-advanced-ransomware-delivery/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Storm-0249 Evolves: Access Broker Now Deploys Ransomware with Advanced Stealth Tactics</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The initial access broker (IAB) known as Storm-0249 is evolving its tactics, moving beyond simply selling network access to actively participating in malware deployment. According to ReliaQuest, the group now uses more sophisticated techniques, including DLL side-loading and fileless PowerShell execution, to facilitate ransomware attacks directly. Their methods involve social engineering victims into running malicious commands (`ClickFix`), which fetch and execute PowerShell scripts from spoofed domains. A key technique is dropping a trojanized version of a SentinelOne security agent DLL to run malware under the guise of a trusted process. This evolution signifies a dangerous trend where IABs are becoming more integrated into the ransomware deployment process, increasing their threat level.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Ransomware, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The threat actor Storm-0249 is evolving from an initial access broker to a direct ransomware enabler, using advanced tactics like DLL side-loading and the 'ClickFix' social engineering method.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> access-broker-storm-0249-shifts-to-advanced-ransomware-delivery</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/access-broker-storm-0249-shifts-to-advanced-ransomware-delivery/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: 18 Million+ Records Exposed in Massive Breaches at 700Credit and Prosper Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/financial-data-breaches-at-700credit-and-prosper-expose-18-million/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/financial-data-breaches-at-700credit-and-prosper-expose-18-million/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> 18 Million+ Records Exposed in Massive Breaches at 700Credit and Prosper Marketplace</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Two severe data breaches in the financial and automotive sectors have compromised the personal and financial data of over 18 million people. Fintech company Prosper Marketplace reported a breach affecting 13 million individuals, exposing Social Security numbers, bank details, and passport information after attackers accessed its databases between June and August 2025. Separately, auto-dealership service provider 700Credit disclosed that a supply-chain attack via a third-party partner exposed names, addresses, and Social Security numbers of 5.8 million people. The 700Credit breach stemmed from a vulnerable API that was exploited over a two-week period. Both companies are now notifying affected individuals and offering credit monitoring services.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Supply Chain Attack, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Learn about the major data breaches at Prosper Marketplace and 700Credit that have exposed the personal and financial information of over 18 million individuals, including Social Security numbers and bank account details.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> financial-data-breaches-at-700credit-and-prosper-expose-18-million</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/financial-data-breaches-at-700credit-and-prosper-expose-18-million/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: URGENT: Apple and Google Patch Actively Exploited WebKit Zero-Days Used in Sophisticated Attacks</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apple-google-patch-actively-exploited-webkit-zero-day-flaws/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apple-google-patch-actively-exploited-webkit-zero-day-flaws/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> URGENT: Apple and Google Patch Actively Exploited WebKit Zero-Days Used in Sophisticated Attacks</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Apple and Google have issued urgent security updates to address two critical zero-day vulnerabilities in the WebKit browser engine, identified as CVE-2025-43529 and CVE-2025-14174. Both flaws are being actively exploited in the wild, with Apple describing the attacks as "extremely sophisticated" and targeting specific individuals. The vulnerabilities, which include a use-after-free and a memory corruption issue, could allow attackers to achieve arbitrary code execution simply by tricking a user into visiting a malicious website. The flaws affect a vast range of products, including iPhones, iPads, Macs, and Google Chrome on Mac. CISA has added CVE-2025-14174 to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, mandating immediate patching for federal agencies.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Mobile Security, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Apple and Google have released emergency patches for two critical zero-day vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-43529, CVE-2025-14174) in WebKit that are being actively exploited. Update your devices immediately.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> apple-google-patch-actively-exploited-webkit-zero-day-flaws</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/apple-google-patch-actively-exploited-webkit-zero-day-flaws/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: SoundCloud and Pornhub Confirm User Data Exposure in Separate Breaches, One Via Third-Party</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/soundcloud-and-pornhub-disclose-user-data-breaches/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/soundcloud-and-pornhub-disclose-user-data-breaches/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> SoundCloud and Pornhub Confirm User Data Exposure in Separate Breaches, One Via Third-Party</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Both SoundCloud and Pornhub have confirmed security incidents exposing user data. SoundCloud suffered a direct breach of an ancillary service dashboard, resulting in the exfiltration of email addresses and public profile information for up to 28 million users (20% of its user base). The company states passwords and financial data were not affected. Separately, Pornhub announced that historical analytics data of some Premium members was exposed due to a breach at its former third-party analytics vendor, Mixpanel. The notorious hacking group ShinyHunters has claimed the Mixpanel breach and is attempting to extort Pornhub, alleging they stole a massive database of user search and watch history.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Supply Chain Attack, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> SoundCloud and Pornhub have disclosed separate data breaches. SoundCloud's breach exposed user emails, while Pornhub's data was leaked via a compromise at former third-party vendor Mixpanel.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> soundcloud-and-pornhub-disclose-user-data-breaches</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/soundcloud-and-pornhub-disclose-user-data-breaches/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA Orders Federal Agencies to Patch Actively Exploited Critical GeoServer XXE Flaw</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-orders-patch-for-actively-exploited-geoserver-xxe-vulnerability/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-orders-patch-for-actively-exploited-geoserver-xxe-vulnerability/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Orders Federal Agencies to Patch Actively Exploited Critical GeoServer XXE Flaw</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a critical XML External Entity (XXE) injection vulnerability in OSGeo GeoServer, CVE-2025-58360, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog. The flaw, which has a CVSS score up to 9.8, allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to read arbitrary files, perform Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) attacks, or cause a denial-of-service. Due to evidence of active exploitation, CISA has mandated that all Federal Civilian Executive Branch agencies patch the vulnerability by January 1, 2026. All organizations using the popular open-source geospatial data server are strongly urged to apply the available updates immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Threat Intelligence, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA has added the critical, actively exploited GeoServer XXE vulnerability CVE-2025-58360 to its KEV catalog, mandating federal agencies to patch. Learn about the risks and remediation steps.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-orders-patch-for-actively-exploited-geoserver-xxe-vulnerability</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-orders-patch-for-actively-exploited-geoserver-xxe-vulnerability/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Active Attacks Exploit Critical Fortinet SSO Bypass Flaws to Gain Admin Access</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fortinet-sso-bypass-vulnerabilities-under-active-attack/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fortinet-sso-bypass-vulnerabilities-under-active-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Active Attacks Exploit Critical Fortinet SSO Bypass Flaws to Gain Admin Access</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Security firm Arctic Wolf has observed active exploitation of two critical authentication bypass vulnerabilities in Fortinet products, CVE-2025-59718 and CVE-2025-59719. Both flaws, rated 9.1 in severity, allow an unauthenticated attacker to bypass FortiCloud single sign-on (SSO) by forging a SAML message, granting them administrative access to affected devices. The attacks, observed since December 12, 2025, target the default 'admin' account. The vulnerability is present if the FortiCloud SSO feature is enabled, which can be activated automatically when registering a device. Patches are available, and administrators are urged to upgrade immediately or disable the vulnerable SSO feature.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Cyberattack, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Active attacks are exploiting critical Fortinet SSO authentication bypass vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-59718, CVE-2025-59719). Learn how to detect and mitigate these flaws to prevent administrative takeover.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> fortinet-sso-bypass-vulnerabilities-under-active-attack</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/fortinet-sso-bypass-vulnerabilities-under-active-attack/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: FreePBX Patches Critical Auth Bypass and RCE Flaws; Update VoIP Platforms Immediately</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-authentication-bypass-and-rce-flaws-patched-in-freepbx/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-authentication-bypass-and-rce-flaws-patched-in-freepbx/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> FreePBX Patches Critical Auth Bypass and RCE Flaws; Update VoIP Platforms Immediately</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The popular open-source VoIP platform FreePBX has been updated to fix several serious security vulnerabilities, including a critical authentication bypass (CVE-2025-66039) with a 9.3 CVSS score. This flaw, present in a non-default configuration, allows an attacker to bypass the admin login and potentially achieve remote code execution. Other patched high-severity issues include multiple authenticated SQL injection flaws (CVE-2025-61675) and an arbitrary file upload bug (CVE-2025-61678). These could be chained to upload a web shell and take full control of the server. Administrators are urged to update their FreePBX instances to the latest versions to mitigate these risks.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Industrial Control Systems</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Critical vulnerabilities, including authentication bypass (CVE-2025-66039) and RCE, have been patched in the FreePBX VoIP platform. Administrators should update immediately to prevent system compromise.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> critical-authentication-bypass-and-rce-flaws-patched-in-freepbx</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-authentication-bypass-and-rce-flaws-patched-in-freepbx/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Pro-Russian Hacktivists NoName057(16) Escalate DDoS Attacks Against NATO-Aligned Nations</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pro-russian-hacktivist-group-noname05716-intensifies-ddos-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pro-russian-hacktivist-group-noname05716-intensifies-ddos-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Pro-Russian Hacktivists NoName057(16) Escalate DDoS Attacks Against NATO-Aligned Nations</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The pro-Russian hacktivist group NoName057(16) is escalating its distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) campaign against organizations in European countries that support Ukraine. The group targets government, logistics, and telecommunications sectors. Their operations are powered by the 'DDoSia Project,' a crowdsourced botnet of volunteers who are paid in cryptocurrency for participating in attacks. The group, believed to have links to Russian state entities, uses a resilient two-tiered command-and-control infrastructure, making it difficult to disrupt. Despite law enforcement efforts, NoName057(16) remains a persistent threat, conducting politically motivated cyber operations to support Russian interests.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Cyberattack, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Learn about the escalating DDoS campaigns by the pro-Russian hacktivist group NoName057(16), who are using their 'DDoSia' botnet to target organizations in NATO-aligned nations.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> pro-russian-hacktivist-group-noname05716-intensifies-ddos-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pro-russian-hacktivist-group-noname05716-intensifies-ddos-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New 'PyStoreRAT' Malware Spreads Via Fake OSINT and AI Tools on GitHub</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pystorerat-malware-targets-developers-via-fake-github-repos/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pystorerat-malware-targets-developers-via-fake-github-repos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New 'PyStoreRAT' Malware Spreads Via Fake OSINT and AI Tools on GitHub</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new malware campaign is distributing an information-stealing Remote Access Trojan (RAT) called 'PyStoreRAT' through fake GitHub repositories. Threat actors create repositories for what appear to be legitimate OSINT, AI, or DeFi tools, artificially inflating their popularity with fake stars and forks. After gaining a user's trust, the attackers push a malicious update containing PyStoreRAT. The malware is designed to evade detection, establish persistence, and steal sensitive data, with a particular focus on cryptocurrency wallets. It can also download secondary payloads like the Rhadamanthys infostealer and propagates via USB drives, posing a significant threat to developers and security researchers.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Supply Chain Attack, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new malware campaign is spreading PyStoreRAT via fake GitHub repositories disguised as OSINT and AI tools, targeting developers to steal cryptocurrency wallets and other sensitive data.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> pystorerat-malware-targets-developers-via-fake-github-repos</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pystorerat-malware-targets-developers-via-fake-github-repos/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Akira Ransomware Claims Attack on Medical Supplier Fieldtex, Breaching Data of 238,000</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/akira-ransomware-hits-fieldtex-exposing-data-of-238k/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/akira-ransomware-hits-fieldtex-exposing-data-of-238k/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Akira Ransomware Claims Attack on Medical Supplier Fieldtex, Breaching Data of 238,000</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>U.S. medical supply company Fieldtex Products has reported a data breach impacting 238,615 individuals after its network was compromised in August 2025. The notorious Akira ransomware group has claimed responsibility for the attack, asserting it stole 14 GB of sensitive corporate data, including employee, customer, and financial records. The exposed personal information includes names, dates of birth, health insurance member IDs, and health plan details. The incident, reported to the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services, underscores the persistent threat of ransomware targeting the healthcare sector and its supply chain.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Akira ransomware group has claimed responsibility for a data breach at medical supply company Fieldtex Products, exposing the health information of over 238,000 people.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> akira-ransomware-hits-fieldtex-exposing-data-of-238k</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/akira-ransomware-hits-fieldtex-exposing-data-of-238k/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: React Server Components Hit with New DoS and Information Leak Flaws After 'React2Shell' Patch</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-dos-and-info-leak-vulnerabilities-in-react-server-components/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-dos-and-info-leak-vulnerabilities-in-react-server-components/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> React Server Components Hit with New DoS and Information Leak Flaws After 'React2Shell' Patch</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Following the recent patch for the critical 'React2Shell' RCE flaw, three new vulnerabilities have been discovered in React Server Components (RSC). Two of the flaws, CVE-2025-55184 and CVE-2025-67779, are high-severity Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerabilities (CVSS 7.5) that can crash a server with a single malicious HTTP request. The third, CVE-2025-55183, is a medium-severity information disclosure flaw (CVSS 5.3) that could allow an attacker to retrieve server-side source code, potentially exposing hardcoded secrets. The React team has released new updates to address these issues, urging developers to upgrade their packages immediately amidst heightened scrutiny of the RSC architecture.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Three new vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-55184, CVE-2025-67779, CVE-2025-55183) have been found in React Server Components, leading to DoS and info leaks. Developers should upgrade dependencies immediately.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> new-dos-and-info-leak-vulnerabilities-in-react-server-components</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-dos-and-info-leak-vulnerabilities-in-react-server-components/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>