<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:21:54 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: URGENT: CISA Orders 7-Day Patch for Actively Exploited FortiWeb Zero-Day</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> URGENT: CISA Orders 7-Day Patch for Actively Exploited FortiWeb Zero-Day</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Fortinet has disclosed a critical OS command injection zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2025-58034, in its FortiWeb Web Application Firewall (WAF) that is being actively exploited in the wild. The flaw allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying system. In response to observed attacks, the U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added the vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog and issued an emergency directive mandating federal agencies apply patches within an accelerated seven-day window, by November 25, 2025. Researchers have detected approximately 2,000 attacks leveraging the flaw and warn it could potentially be chained with a recently disclosed authentication bypass vulnerability (CVE-2025-64446) to achieve unauthenticated remote code execution.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Fortinet discloses and CISA mandates urgent patching for CVE-2025-58034, a critical OS command injection zero-day in FortiWeb WAFs that is under active exploitation. Learn about the risks and mitigation steps.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-mandates-7-day-patch-for-actively-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-zero-day-cve-2025-58034/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Patch Now: Microsoft Fixes Actively Exploited Windows Kernel Zero-Day</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-windows-kernel-zero-day-cve-2025-62215-in-november-patch-tuesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-windows-kernel-zero-day-cve-2025-62215-in-november-patch-tuesday/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Patch Now: Microsoft Fixes Actively Exploited Windows Kernel Zero-Day</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>As part of its November 2025 Patch Tuesday release, Microsoft has addressed 63 security vulnerabilities, including a high-severity zero-day flaw in the Windows Kernel (CVE-2025-62215) that is confirmed to be under active exploitation. The vulnerability is a local privilege escalation (LPE) bug with a CVSS score of 7.0, allowing an attacker who has already gained initial access to a system to elevate their privileges to SYSTEM level. Such flaws are critical components in post-exploitation attack chains, enabling threat actors to take full control of a compromised machine. The update also fixes 16 remote code execution (RCE) vulnerabilities and numerous other flaws across the Microsoft product suite. Immediate patching is strongly recommended for all Windows users.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Microsoft's November 2025 Patch Tuesday fixes 63 vulnerabilities, including CVE-2025-62215, a Windows Kernel zero-day that is actively exploited for privilege escalation. Details on the flaw and mitigation.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-windows-kernel-zero-day-cve-2025-62215-in-november-patch-tuesday</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/microsoft-patches-actively-exploited-windows-kernel-zero-day-cve-2025-62215-in-november-patch-tuesday/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Google Chrome Zero-Day Exploited in Wild, CISA Mandates Urgent Patch</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-google-chrome-zero-day-cve-2025-13223/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-google-chrome-zero-day-cve-2025-13223/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Google Chrome Zero-Day Exploited in Wild, CISA Mandates Urgent Patch</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Google has patched a high-severity zero-day vulnerability in its Chrome web browser, CVE-2025-13223, which is being actively exploited in the wild. The flaw is a type confusion error in the V8 JavaScript engine that can be leveraged by an attacker for remote code execution (RCE) simply by luring a victim to a malicious website. Following Google's confirmation of in-the-wild exploitation, the U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) promptly added the vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, mandating that federal agencies apply the update by December 10, 2025. The vulnerability affects Chrome on all major desktop platforms (Windows, macOS, and Linux) and other Chromium-based browsers.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Cyberattack, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA warns of an actively exploited Google Chrome zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2025-13223, a type confusion flaw in the V8 engine allowing for remote code execution. Update to version 131.0.6778.72 or later immediately.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-google-chrome-zero-day-cve-2025-13223</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-google-chrome-zero-day-cve-2025-13223/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Sinobi Ransomware Strikes US Manufacturer and Indian Tech Firm</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sinobi-ransomware-group-attacks-us-manufacturer-croft-and-indian-tech-firm-changepond/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sinobi-ransomware-group-attacks-us-manufacturer-croft-and-indian-tech-firm-changepond/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Sinobi Ransomware Strikes US Manufacturer and Indian Tech Firm</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The 'sinobi' ransomware group has claimed responsibility for two recent cyberattacks targeting organizations in the United States and India. The victims are Croft, a U.S.-based window and door manufacturer, and CHANGEPOND, an enterprise software company headquartered in Chennai, India. Both breaches were discovered on November 19, 2025, occurring within minutes of each other. These incidents underscore the global reach and indiscriminate targeting of ransomware operators, affecting diverse sectors including manufacturing and technology. The attacks highlight the persistent threat posed by ransomware and the importance of robust cybersecurity defenses.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The 'sinobi' ransomware group has claimed responsibility for cyberattacks on US manufacturer Croft and Indian software company CHANGEPOND, demonstrating a global, cross-industry threat.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> sinobi-ransomware-group-attacks-us-manufacturer-croft-and-indian-tech-firm-changepond</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/sinobi-ransomware-group-attacks-us-manufacturer-croft-and-indian-tech-firm-changepond/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: PA Attorney General Confirms Massive Data Breach by Inc Ransom</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pennsylvania-attorney-general-confirms-major-data-breach-by-inc-ransom-group/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pennsylvania-attorney-general-confirms-major-data-breach-by-inc-ransom-group/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> PA Attorney General Confirms Massive Data Breach by Inc Ransom</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Pennsylvania Office of the Attorney General (OAG) has officially confirmed it was the victim of a significant ransomware attack orchestrated by the 'Inc Ransom' group. The attack, which occurred in August 2025, disrupted the agency's operations for three weeks. The threat actors claim to have exfiltrated 5.7 terabytes of highly sensitive data, including Social Security numbers, medical details, and investigative files. The initial access vector is believed to be the exploitation of the 'CitrixBleed2' vulnerability (CVE-2025-5777) on the agency's Citrix NetScaler appliances. The FBI is now investigating the incident, and the OAG is in the process of notifying affected individuals.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Ransomware, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Pennsylvania Office of the Attorney General confirms it was hit by the Inc Ransom group, who exploited CVE-2025-5777 (CitrixBleed2) to steal 5.7 TB of sensitive data and disrupt operations for weeks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> pennsylvania-attorney-general-confirms-major-data-breach-by-inc-ransom-group</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pennsylvania-attorney-general-confirms-major-data-breach-by-inc-ransom-group/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA and Partners Release Guide to Combat Bulletproof Hosting</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-and-fbi-release-guide-to-combat-malicious-bulletproof-hosting-providers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-and-fbi-release-guide-to-combat-malicious-bulletproof-hosting-providers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA and Partners Release Guide to Combat Bulletproof Hosting</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), along with the FBI, NSA, and international partners, has published a comprehensive guide to help network defenders and Internet Service Providers (ISPs) combat the threat of bulletproof hosting (BPH) providers. These services knowingly lease infrastructure to cybercriminals for a wide range of malicious activities, including ransomware, phishing, and malware distribution. The guide, 'Bulletproof Defense,' provides actionable recommendations for filtering malicious traffic, enhancing network monitoring, and improving intelligence sharing to disrupt the criminal ecosystem that relies on BPH for anonymity and resilience.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Threat Intelligence, Security Operations</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA, in partnership with the FBI and NSA, has published a new guide to help organizations mitigate risks from bulletproof hosting (BPH) providers that support cybercrime.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-and-fbi-release-guide-to-combat-malicious-bulletproof-hosting-providers</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-and-fbi-release-guide-to-combat-malicious-bulletproof-hosting-providers/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: AI-Driven Attacks Explode: Malware Emails Spike 131%, Report Finds</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ai-powered-cyberattacks-surge-malware-emails-up-131-percent-report/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ai-powered-cyberattacks-surge-malware-emails-up-131-percent-report/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> AI-Driven Attacks Explode: Malware Emails Spike 131%, Report Finds</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new cybersecurity report from Hornetsecurity highlights a dramatic increase in AI-powered cyberattacks throughout 2025. The analysis of over 72 billion emails revealed that the volume of malware-laden emails grew by 131% year-over-year, while phishing and scam attempts also rose significantly. The report attributes this surge to threat actors' adoption of generative AI, which enables the creation of highly convincing and sophisticated malicious content at scale. In response, 77% of CISOs now view AI-generated phishing as a major threat, and 68% of organizations have invested in AI-powered defenses, signaling a new 'arms race' in cybersecurity.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Intelligence, Phishing, Malware</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A 2025 Hornetsecurity report finds that AI-driven cyberattacks are surging, with malware-laden emails increasing by 131% as threat actors weaponize generative AI for more sophisticated phishing campaigns.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ai-powered-cyberattacks-surge-malware-emails-up-131-percent-report</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ai-powered-cyberattacks-surge-malware-emails-up-131-percent-report/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA Issues 6 New ICS Advisories for Schneider Electric, Shelly, METZ CONNECT</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-publishes-six-new-advisories-for-industrial-control-systems-ics/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-publishes-six-new-advisories-for-industrial-control-systems-ics/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Issues 6 New ICS Advisories for Schneider Electric, Shelly, METZ CONNECT</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>On November 19, 2025, the U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released six new Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories, highlighting multiple vulnerabilities in products from Schneider Electric, Shelly, and METZ CONNECT. The alerts affect a range of operational technology (OT) products, including SCADA systems and power monitoring devices. Four of the advisories are for Schneider Electric products like EcoStruxure and PowerChute. CISA urges administrators in critical infrastructure and manufacturing sectors to review the advisories and apply the recommended mitigations to prevent potential exploitation.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Industrial Control Systems, Vulnerability, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA has released six new Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories detailing vulnerabilities in products from Schneider Electric, Shelly, and METZ CONNECT. Critical infrastructure operators should review and mitigate.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-publishes-six-new-advisories-for-industrial-control-systems-ics</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-publishes-six-new-advisories-for-industrial-control-systems-ics/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA Releases "Be Air Aware" Guides to Combat Drone Threats</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-launches-be-air-aware-guides-to-defend-critical-infrastructure-from-drone-threats/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-launches-be-air-aware-guides-to-defend-critical-infrastructure-from-drone-threats/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Releases "Be Air Aware" Guides to Combat Drone Threats</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>As part of Critical Infrastructure Security and Resilience Month, the U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has released three new guides under its "Be Air Aware™" campaign. These resources are designed to help critical infrastructure owners and operators understand, assess, and mitigate the growing security risks posed by Unmanned Aircraft Systems (UAS), or drones. The guides provide actionable information on detecting suspicious drone activity, implementing detection technologies, and safely handling downed aircraft, aiming to integrate aerial threat considerations into existing security plans.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Industrial Control Systems, Security Operations</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA's new 'Be Air Aware' campaign provides three new guides to help critical infrastructure owners and operators defend against the growing security threats posed by drones (UAS).</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-launches-be-air-aware-guides-to-defend-critical-infrastructure-from-drone-threats</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-launches-be-air-aware-guides-to-defend-critical-infrastructure-from-drone-threats/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: New 'Nova Stealer' Malware Targets macOS Crypto Wallets</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-nova-stealer-malware-targets-macos-users-for-cryptocurrency-wallets/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-nova-stealer-malware-targets-macos-users-for-cryptocurrency-wallets/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> New 'Nova Stealer' Malware Targets macOS Crypto Wallets</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new information-stealing malware, dubbed 'Nova Stealer,' has been discovered actively targeting Apple macOS users. The malware's primary goal is the exfiltration of sensitive data, with a specific focus on cryptocurrency wallets. Nova Stealer operates as a trojan, infecting systems by replacing legitimate, installed applications with malicious versions. When a user launches the compromised application, the malware activates in the background to search for and steal wallet files and other valuable information. This discovery underscores the increasing trend of threat actors developing malware for the macOS platform, challenging the perception of it being inherently more secure than Windows.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Malware, Threat Intelligence, Mobile Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Security researchers have identified 'Nova Stealer,' a new information-stealing malware that targets macOS users by trojanizing legitimate applications to steal cryptocurrency wallets and data.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> new-nova-stealer-malware-targets-macos-users-for-cryptocurrency-wallets</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/new-nova-stealer-malware-targets-macos-users-for-cryptocurrency-wallets/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Mobile Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Google Scrambles to Patch 7th Actively Exploited Chrome Zero-Day of 2025</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-v8-zero-day-cve-2025-13223/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-v8-zero-day-cve-2025-13223/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Google Scrambles to Patch 7th Actively Exploited Chrome Zero-Day of 2025</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Google has released an emergency security update for its Chrome web browser to fix a high-severity zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2025-13223, which is confirmed to be actively exploited in the wild. The flaw is a type confusion weakness in the V8 JavaScript engine, allowing attackers to achieve remote code execution by luring users to a malicious website. This marks the seventh zero-day patched in Chrome this year. The update also addresses a second V8 flaw, CVE-2025-13224. Users are urged to update their browsers immediately to version 142.0.7444.175/.176, and users of other Chromium-based browsers should expect similar patches.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> CVE-2025-13223, Google Chrome zero-day, V8 vulnerability, actively exploited, remote code execution, browser security, emergency patch, Chromium exploit</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Google has issued an emergency patch for CVE-2025-13223, a high-severity type confusion zero-day vulnerability in the Chrome V8 engine that is being actively exploited. Learn about the flaw and how to mitigate it.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-v8-zero-day-cve-2025-13223</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/google-patches-actively-exploited-chrome-v8-zero-day-cve-2025-13223/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Inc Ransom Cripples PA Attorney General's Office, Exfiltrates 5.7 TB of Data</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pennsylvania-attorney-general-confirms-major-data-breach-by-inc-ransomware/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pennsylvania-attorney-general-confirms-major-data-breach-by-inc-ransomware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Inc Ransom Cripples PA Attorney General's Office, Exfiltrates 5.7 TB of Data</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Pennsylvania Office of the Attorney General (OAG) has confirmed it suffered a severe data breach orchestrated by the Inc Ransom ransomware group. The attackers exploited the 'CitrixBleed2' vulnerability (CVE-2025-5777) to gain initial access and subsequently exfiltrated 5.7 terabytes of highly sensitive data. The stolen information includes Social Security numbers, medical details, and confidential investigative files. The attack, which occurred in August 2025, caused a three-week operational disruption for the agency's 1,200 staff members. The OAG has refused to pay the ransom and is working with the FBI on the investigation.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Data Breach, Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Inc Ransom, Pennsylvania Attorney General data breach, CVE-2025-5777, CitrixBleed2 exploit, ransomware attack, government data breach, double extortion</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 7 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Learn about the major data breach at the Pennsylvania Office of the Attorney General, where the Inc Ransom group exploited CVE-2025-5777 to steal 5.7 TB of sensitive data, including SSNs and medical information.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> pennsylvania-attorney-general-confirms-major-data-breach-by-inc-ransomware</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pennsylvania-attorney-general-confirms-major-data-breach-by-inc-ransomware/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: US, UK, and Australia Sanction Russian Bulletproof Hosting Network Aiding Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-uk-australia-sanction-russian-bulletproof-hosting-network-media-land/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-uk-australia-sanction-russian-bulletproof-hosting-network-media-land/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> US, UK, and Australia Sanction Russian Bulletproof Hosting Network Aiding Ransomware</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>In a coordinated action, the United States, United Kingdom, and Australia have sanctioned Media Land, LLC, a Russian bulletproof hosting provider, along with its network of related entities and key individuals. This infrastructure is accused of providing essential services to a wide range of global cybercriminals, including malware distributors, phishing operators, and ransomware groups like the notorious LockBit gang. The sanctions aim to disrupt the foundational services that enable cybercrime by targeting the providers who knowingly support malicious operations. The action highlights a strategic international effort to dismantle the cybercrime economy.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Threat Actor, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> OFAC sanctions, Media Land LLC, Russian cybercrime, bulletproof hosting, LockBit infrastructure, cybercrime sanctions, Aleksandr Volosovik</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The U.S., U.K., and Australia have jointly sanctioned Russian bulletproof hosting provider Media Land, LLC for facilitating ransomware and other cybercrime. Learn about the impact of this international action.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> us-uk-australia-sanction-russian-bulletproof-hosting-network-media-land</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/us-uk-australia-sanction-russian-bulletproof-hosting-network-media-land/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: DoorDash Hit by Data Breach After Employee Falls for Social Engineering Scam</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/doordash-discloses-data-breach-after-employee-social-engineering-scam/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/doordash-discloses-data-breach-after-employee-social-engineering-scam/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> DoorDash Hit by Data Breach After Employee Falls for Social Engineering Scam</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Food delivery giant DoorDash has disclosed a data breach that occurred after an employee was targeted by a social engineering scam. The unauthorized access allowed a third party to view the personal information of customers, delivery personnel ('Dashers'), and merchants. The compromised data includes names, email addresses, phone numbers, and physical addresses. DoorDash has stated that sensitive financial data and government IDs were not accessed. The company has secured its systems, notified affected parties, and established a call center to address user concerns.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Phishing, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> DoorDash data breach, social engineering, phishing attack, customer data leak, cybersecurity incident, employee scam</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Food delivery service DoorDash has disclosed a data breach affecting customers, Dashers, and merchants after an employee fell victim to a social engineering scam. Learn what data was exposed.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> doordash-discloses-data-breach-after-employee-social-engineering-scam</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/doordash-discloses-data-breach-after-employee-social-engineering-scam/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA Adds Actively Exploited Fortinet FortiWeb Flaw to KEV Catalog</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-flaw-cve-2025-58034-to-kev-catalog/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-flaw-cve-2025-58034-to-kev-catalog/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Adds Actively Exploited Fortinet FortiWeb Flaw to KEV Catalog</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a critical OS command injection vulnerability in Fortinet's FortiWeb products, CVE-2025-58034, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog. Citing evidence of active exploitation, CISA has mandated a one-week remediation deadline for Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies under Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01. The vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands on affected devices. CISA strongly urges all organizations using FortiWeb to prioritize patching this flaw to mitigate the threat.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> CVE-2025-58034, CISA KEV catalog, Fortinet FortiWeb vulnerability, command injection, actively exploited, BOD 22-01, patch management</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA has added CVE-2025-58034, a critical and actively exploited command injection vulnerability in Fortinet FortiWeb, to its KEV catalog. Federal agencies must patch within one week.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-adds-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-flaw-cve-2025-58034-to-kev-catalog</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-exploited-fortinet-fortiweb-flaw-cve-2025-58034-to-kev-catalog/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Chicago's St. Anthony Hospital Discloses Data Breach Affecting Over 6,600</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/st-anthony-hospital-discloses-data-breach-affecting-6600-individuals/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/st-anthony-hospital-discloses-data-breach-affecting-6600-individuals/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Chicago's St. Anthony Hospital Discloses Data Breach Affecting Over 6,600</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>St. Anthony Hospital in Chicago has reported a data breach that may have exposed the personal and medical information of more than 6,600 patients and staff members. The incident, which was discovered in February 2025, occurred when an unauthorized party gained access to several employee email accounts. An investigation revealed that the compromised accounts contained sensitive data, including names, Social Security numbers, medical record numbers, and medical histories. The hospital states there is no evidence the data has been misused but is in the process of notifying all affected individuals.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Phishing, Industrial Control Systems</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> St. Anthony Hospital data breach, healthcare data breach, Chicago hospital breach, patient data exposed, PHI breach, email account compromise</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> St. Anthony Hospital in Chicago has disclosed a data breach affecting over 6,600 individuals after employee email accounts were compromised, exposing PII and PHI.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> st-anthony-hospital-discloses-data-breach-affecting-6600-individuals</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/st-anthony-hospital-discloses-data-breach-affecting-6600-individuals/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Supply Chain Attacks &amp; AI-Powered Phishing Surge Across Asia-Pacific, Darktrace Warns</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/darktrace-report-supply-chain-attacks-and-ai-phishing-escalate-in-apj/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/darktrace-report-supply-chain-attacks-and-ai-phishing-escalate-in-apj/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Supply Chain Attacks &amp; AI-Powered Phishing Surge Across Asia-Pacific, Darktrace Warns</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new threat report from cybersecurity firm Darktrace highlights a dramatic increase in sophisticated cyber threats across the Asia-Pacific and Japan (APJ) region. The report, covering the 12 months to July 2025, details a surge in supply chain attacks, business email compromise, and cloud intrusions. State-sponsored groups from China (APT40, APT41) and North Korea (Lazarus/Bluenoroff) are reportedly leveraging generative AI to create more convincing phishing emails, particularly in non-English languages like Japanese. The report also notes the high cost of supply chain breaches and the use of advanced voice-phishing by groups like Scattered Spider.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Intelligence, Supply Chain Attack, Phishing</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Darktrace report, APJ cybersecurity, supply chain attack, AI phishing, APT40, Lazarus Group, Scattered Spider</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 7 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new Darktrace report reveals a surge in supply chain attacks and AI-enhanced phishing in the Asia-Pacific region, with state-sponsored groups like APT40 and Lazarus leveraging generative AI.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> darktrace-report-supply-chain-attacks-and-ai-phishing-escalate-in-apj</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/darktrace-report-supply-chain-attacks-and-ai-phishing-escalate-in-apj/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: China-Aligned APT 'PlushDaemon' Wields 'EdgeStepper' Implant for Network Hijacking</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-aligned-apt-plushdaemon-deploys-edgestepper-network-implant/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-aligned-apt-plushdaemon-deploys-edgestepper-network-implant/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> China-Aligned APT 'PlushDaemon' Wields 'EdgeStepper' Implant for Network Hijacking</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Security researchers have uncovered a new, sophisticated network implant named 'EdgeStepper' used by the China-aligned APT group PlushDaemon. The implant provides the attackers with adversary-in-the-middle (AitM) capabilities, allowing them to intercept and hijack legitimate software updates within a compromised network. EdgeStepper is deployed as part of a larger toolset that includes 'LittleDaemon' and 'DaemonicLogistics' to deliver a Windows implant called 'SlowStepper'. This framework enables the APT group to conduct espionage and deploy additional malware by masquerading as legitimate update traffic.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Malware, Supply Chain Attack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> PlushDaemon, EdgeStepper, SlowStepper, China APT, adversary-in-the-middle, network implant, ESET research</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 7 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Researchers at ESET have discovered 'EdgeStepper,' a new network implant from the China-aligned APT group PlushDaemon, used for adversary-in-the-middle attacks to hijack software updates.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> china-aligned-apt-plushdaemon-deploys-edgestepper-network-implant</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/china-aligned-apt-plushdaemon-deploys-edgestepper-network-implant/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Togo and Mozambique Forge Cybersecurity Pact to Strengthen African Defenses</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/togo-and-mozambique-sign-cybersecurity-pact-to-bolster-african-digital-defense/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/togo-and-mozambique-sign-cybersecurity-pact-to-bolster-african-digital-defense/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Togo and Mozambique Forge Cybersecurity Pact to Strengthen African Defenses</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The nations of Togo and Mozambique have signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to formalize their cooperation on cybersecurity. The agreement, signed during the inaugural International Cybersecurity Week in Mozambique, establishes a framework for their national Computer Security Incident Response Teams (CSIRTs) to collaborate. The partnership will focus on sharing real-time threat intelligence, conducting joint capacity-building exercises, and coordinating operational responses to cyber incidents, aiming to bolster the digital resilience of both nations and the wider African continent.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Togo Mozambique cybersecurity, Africa cybersecurity, cybersecurity MoU, CSIRT cooperation, threat intelligence sharing Africa</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Togo and Mozambique have signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to enhance cybersecurity cooperation, including threat intelligence sharing and joint incident response between their national CSIRTs.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> togo-and-mozambique-sign-cybersecurity-pact-to-bolster-african-digital-defense</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/togo-and-mozambique-sign-cybersecurity-pact-to-bolster-african-digital-defense/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Vendor Breach Exposes Patient Data at Innovative Physical Therapy</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/phishing-breach-at-vendor-exposes-innovative-physical-therapy-patient-data/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/phishing-breach-at-vendor-exposes-innovative-physical-therapy-patient-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Vendor Breach Exposes Patient Data at Innovative Physical Therapy</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Innovative Physical Therapy has notified patients of a data breach that originated from a third-party vendor responsible for practice management. The breach occurred when two vendor employees fell victim to phishing emails, leading to the compromise of their email accounts. Between June 25 and June 26, 2025, an unauthorized party accessed these accounts, which contained the protected health information (PHI) and personally identifiable information (PII) of at least 2,023 patients. The exposed data includes names, Social Security numbers, medical information, and health insurance details.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Supply Chain Attack, Phishing</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Innovative Physical Therapy data breach, vendor data breach, healthcare supply chain attack, phishing, patient data leak, PHI breach</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Innovative Physical Therapy reports a data breach affecting 2,023 patients after a third-party vendor's employees were compromised by phishing emails, exposing PHI and PII including Social Security numbers.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> phishing-breach-at-vendor-exposes-innovative-physical-therapy-patient-data</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/phishing-breach-at-vendor-exposes-innovative-physical-therapy-patient-data/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>