<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Last Day - NEW &amp; UPDATE</title>
    <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/</link>
    <description>All NEW and UPDATE articles from the last day with enhanced metadata</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:10:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cyber.netsecops.io//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: False Confidence: 94% of Firms Claim Supply Chain Resilience, But a Third Neglect Basic Risk Assessments</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/overconfidence-in-supply-chain-security-poses-major-risk-ncc-group-report/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/overconfidence-in-supply-chain-security-poses-major-risk-ncc-group-report/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> False Confidence: 94% of Firms Claim Supply Chain Resilience, But a Third Neglect Basic Risk Assessments</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new report from NCC Group highlights a critical disconnect in enterprise security: while 94% of businesses are confident in their ability to handle a supply chain attack, 34% do not perform regular supplier risk assessments. This widespread overconfidence creates significant vulnerabilities as threat actors increasingly target less secure third-party vendors to compromise larger organizations. The research, which surveyed over 1,000 cybersecurity leaders, comes as ransomware attacks hit record highs and UK authorities report a 130% increase in nationally significant cyber incidents, many originating from the supply chain. Experts warn this misplaced trust is a primary driver of risk, enabling invoice redirection fraud, credential theft, and widespread disruption across entire business ecosystems.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Policy and Compliance, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new NCC Group report finds a dangerous level of overconfidence in supply chain security, with 94% of businesses feeling prepared despite widespread failure to conduct regular supplier risk assessments, creating major vulnerabilities.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> overconfidence-in-supply-chain-security-poses-major-risk-ncc-group-report</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/overconfidence-in-supply-chain-security-poses-major-risk-ncc-group-report/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: UK's Most Costly Cyberattack: Jaguar Land Rover Hack Inflicts £1.9 Billion Economic Damage</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/jaguar-land-rover-hack-costs-uk-economy-1-9-billion/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/jaguar-land-rover-hack-costs-uk-economy-1-9-billion/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> UK's Most Costly Cyberattack: Jaguar Land Rover Hack Inflicts £1.9 Billion Economic Damage</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A report from the Cyber Monitoring Centre (CMC) estimates that the late August 2025 cyberattack on Jaguar Land Rover (JLR) has cost the UK economy £1.9 billion, potentially making it the most expensive cyber incident in the nation's history. The attack forced a complete shutdown of JLR's factories and offices, with full production not expected to resume until January 2026. The economic devastation cascaded through the automotive giant's supply chain, impacting an estimated 5,000 organizations and forcing smaller suppliers to lay off workers. Former NCSC head Ciaran Martin described the incident as a stark reminder of the systemic risk posed by disruptions to critical networks and supply chains.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cyberattack, Supply Chain Attack, Industrial Control Systems</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The cyberattack on Jaguar Land Rover (JLR) has cost the UK economy an estimated £1.9 billion, making it the most expensive cyber incident in British history and highlighting the systemic risk to supply chains.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> jaguar-land-rover-hack-costs-uk-economy-1-9-billion</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/jaguar-land-rover-hack-costs-uk-economy-1-9-billion/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: 18 Minutes to Mayhem: Ransomware Attacks Now Fully Automated, Slashing Defender Response Time</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-automation-cuts-attack-timelines-to-18-minutes/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-automation-cuts-attack-timelines-to-18-minutes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> 18 Minutes to Mayhem: Ransomware Attacks Now Fully Automated, Slashing Defender Response Time</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new report from ReliaQuest reveals a dramatic acceleration in ransomware attacks, with the average time from initial access to lateral movement ('breakout time') plummeting to just 18 minutes. This is a significant decrease from 48 minutes in 2024, driven by the adoption of automation and AI by 80% of Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) groups. The report highlights the Qilin ransomware gang as a prime example, whose platform automates key attack phases like discovery, backup deletion, and encryption. Other groups like LockBit are also integrating AI to enhance their operations, creating a hyper-competitive landscape where speed and automation are paramount. This shrinking response window poses a monumental challenge for security teams, demanding automated detection and response capabilities to counter the threat.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Actor, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 7 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Ransomware attacks have accelerated dramatically, with the average time from initial access to lateral movement now just 18 minutes, driven by automation and AI used by groups like Qilin and LockBit.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ransomware-automation-cuts-attack-timelines-to-18-minutes</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-automation-cuts-attack-timelines-to-18-minutes/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: AI-Fueled Ransomware Pummels Asia-Pacific; Australia Ranks as #2 Target</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ai-powered-ransomware-surges-in-asia-pacific-australia-is-2-target/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ai-powered-ransomware-surges-in-asia-pacific-australia-is-2-target/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> AI-Fueled Ransomware Pummels Asia-Pacific; Australia Ranks as #2 Target</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new report from CrowdStrike reveals that Australia is the second-most targeted nation for eCrime in the Asia-Pacific and Japan (APJ) region, trailing only India. The '2025 APJ eCrime Landscape Report' highlights a surge in ransomware attacks fueled by AI-developed malware and the industrialization of cybercrime through underground markets. From January 2024 to April 2025, 763 organizations in the APJ region were named on data leak sites. The manufacturing, technology, and financial services sectors are the most frequent victims. Emerging RaaS providers like KillSec and Funklocker are leveraging AI to launch high-velocity attacks, contributing to over 120 incidents against these high-value targets.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Intelligence, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Australia is the second-most targeted nation in the APJ region for eCrime as ransomware actors like KillSec and Funklocker leverage AI-developed malware to attack financial and manufacturing sectors, according to a new CrowdStrike report.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ai-powered-ransomware-surges-in-asia-pacific-australia-is-2-target</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ai-powered-ransomware-surges-in-asia-pacific-australia-is-2-target/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: NY Regulator Puts Financial Firms on Notice: You Are Accountable for Your Vendors' Security</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ny-dfs-issues-guidance-on-third-party-cybersecurity-risks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ny-dfs-issues-guidance-on-third-party-cybersecurity-risks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> NY Regulator Puts Financial Firms on Notice: You Are Accountable for Your Vendors' Security</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The New York State Department of Financial Services (DFS) has issued new guidance for financial institutions, emphasizing their ultimate accountability for managing cybersecurity risks originating from third-party service providers (TPSPs). The regulator warned that as firms increasingly rely on cloud computing, AI, and fintech solutions from vendors, their exposure to threats grows. The guidance explicitly states that boards of directors and senior officers must possess sufficient cybersecurity knowledge to oversee and challenge management's third-party risk strategies. DFS Acting Superintendent Kaitlin Asrow stressed that regulated entities cannot outsource their responsibility for protecting consumer data and ensuring operational security.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Regulatory, Policy and Compliance, Supply Chain Attack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The New York State Department of Financial Services (DFS) has issued new guidance holding financial firms accountable for cybersecurity risks from third-party providers, requiring direct oversight from boards and senior officers.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ny-dfs-issues-guidance-on-third-party-cybersecurity-risks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ny-dfs-issues-guidance-on-third-party-cybersecurity-risks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Unit 42 Exposes 'Smishing Deluge' from China and 'Jingle Thief' Gift Card Fraud</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/palo-alto-networks-uncovers-smishing-and-gift-card-fraud-campaigns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/palo-alto-networks-uncovers-smishing-and-gift-card-fraud-campaigns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Unit 42 Exposes 'Smishing Deluge' from China and 'Jingle Thief' Gift Card Fraud</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Researchers at Palo Alto Networks' Unit 42 have detailed two distinct and significant cybercrime operations. The first, a massive smishing campaign dubbed 'The Smishing Deluge,' is attributed to a China-based threat actor and is flooding mobile users globally with malicious SMS messages. The second campaign, named 'Jingle Thief,' is a sophisticated cloud-based operation focused on automating the theft and monetization of gift cards. These findings, highlighted in Unit 42's October Threat Bulletin, showcase the diverse tactics of modern criminals, from large-scale social engineering to highly targeted financial fraud.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Phishing, Threat Intelligence, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Palo Alto Networks' Unit 42 has exposed 'The Smishing Deluge,' a global SMS phishing campaign from China, and 'Jingle Thief,' a separate cloud-based operation that automates gift card fraud.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> palo-alto-networks-uncovers-smishing-and-gift-card-fraud-campaigns</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/palo-alto-networks-uncovers-smishing-and-gift-card-fraud-campaigns/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Healthcare Breaches Seem to Drop, But Government Shutdown Hides True Numbers</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/september-healthcare-breaches-decline-but-data-incomplete-due-to-shutdown/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/september-healthcare-breaches-decline-but-data-incomplete-due-to-shutdown/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Healthcare Breaches Seem to Drop, But Government Shutdown Hides True Numbers</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Official data for September 2025 shows only 26 major healthcare data breaches, the lowest monthly total since 2018. However, The HIPAA Journal cautions that this apparent decline is misleading. A US government shutdown has largely halted the HHS's Office for Civil Rights (OCR) from processing and updating its public breach portal. The 26 reported breaches affected over 1.29 million individuals, with hacking incidents accounting for 98.8% of the exposed records. Experts believe the true number of breaches for September is significantly higher and will be reflected in a surge of reports once the OCR resumes normal operations.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Medium</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Regulatory, Policy and Compliance</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A reported decline in September 2025 healthcare data breaches is misleading, warns The HIPAA Journal, as a government shutdown has paused the HHS OCR's breach portal updates, hiding the true number of incidents.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> september-healthcare-breaches-decline-but-data-incomplete-due-to-shutdown</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/september-healthcare-breaches-decline-but-data-incomplete-due-to-shutdown/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Palomar Health Breach Exposes Highly Sensitive Patient Data, Including Biometrics</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/palomar-health-medical-group-discloses-data-breach-affecting-patients/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/palomar-health-medical-group-discloses-data-breach-affecting-patients/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Palomar Health Breach Exposes Highly Sensitive Patient Data, Including Biometrics</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Palomar Health Medical Group (PHMG), a California-based healthcare provider, has announced it was the victim of a cybersecurity incident that exposed sensitive patient data. The compromised information includes not only names and personal identifiers but also highly sensitive data types such as biometric data, U.S. alien registration numbers, and financial account information. The full scope of the breach, including the number of affected patients, has not yet been disclosed. The national class action law firm Lynch Carpenter is now investigating claims against PHMG, signaling significant legal and financial fallout for the provider.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Data Breach, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Palomar Health Medical Group (PHMG) in California has suffered a major data breach, exposing sensitive patient information including biometric data, financial accounts, and U.S. alien registration numbers.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> palomar-health-medical-group-discloses-data-breach-affecting-patients</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/palomar-health-medical-group-discloses-data-breach-affecting-patients/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: CISA Orders Federal Agencies to Patch New Actively Exploited Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-new-actively-exploited-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-new-actively-exploited-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CISA Orders Federal Agencies to Patch New Actively Exploited Vulnerability</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>On October 22, 2025, the U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) added a new, unspecified vulnerability to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog. This action confirms that the flaw is being actively exploited in the wild by malicious actors. Under Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01, all Federal Civilian Executive Branch (FCEB) agencies are now required to remediate this vulnerability by a specific deadline to protect federal networks. While the CVE identifier was not immediately released, the alert serves as a critical warning to all organizations to prioritize its patching.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Regulatory</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CISA has added a new, actively exploited vulnerability to its KEV catalog, triggering Binding Operational Directive (BOD) 22-01 and requiring federal agencies to patch the flaw to defend against ongoing attacks.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> cisa-adds-new-actively-exploited-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/cisa-adds-new-actively-exploited-vulnerability-to-kev-catalog/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: 50% of Ransomware Attacks in 2025 Hit Critical Infrastructure, KELA Reports</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-industries-face-escalating-ransomware-threat-kela-report/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-industries-face-escalating-ransomware-threat-kela-report/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> 50% of Ransomware Attacks in 2025 Hit Critical Infrastructure, KELA Reports</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new report from threat intelligence firm KELA reveals a stark trend: 50% of all ransomware attacks between January and September 2025 have targeted critical infrastructure. Sectors such as manufacturing, healthcare, energy, and transportation are bearing the brunt of a 34% year-over-year increase in attacks. The report, 'Escalating Ransomware Threats to National Security,' documented 4,701 total ransomware incidents globally in the first nine months of the year, with 2,332 of those hitting critical sectors. The United States remains the most-targeted nation, accounting for 21% of all incidents. The findings have prompted calls to treat cyber resilience as a matter of national defense.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Intelligence, Industrial Control Systems</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A KELA report reveals that 50% of all 2025 ransomware attacks have targeted critical infrastructure sectors like manufacturing and healthcare, with a 34% year-over-year increase in such incidents.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> critical-industries-face-escalating-ransomware-threat-kela-report</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-industries-face-escalating-ransomware-threat-kela-report/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: CrowdStrike: 76% of Organizations Can't Keep Pace with AI-Powered Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ai-powered-ransomware-outpacing-defenses-crowdstrike-warns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ai-powered-ransomware-outpacing-defenses-crowdstrike-warns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> CrowdStrike: 76% of Organizations Can't Keep Pace with AI-Powered Ransomware</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>According to CrowdStrike's '2025 State of Ransomware Survey,' a staggering 76% of global organizations feel their defensive capabilities cannot match the speed and sophistication of AI-powered cyberattacks. Adversaries are now weaponizing artificial intelligence to accelerate every stage of the ransomware attack chain, from malware creation to social engineering, rendering legacy detection methods obsolete. Nearly half of organizations now view AI-automated attacks as their single greatest ransomware threat.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Intelligence, Ransomware, Other</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> CrowdStrike's 2025 ransomware survey shows 76% of organizations feel unable to defend against AI-powered attacks, which are accelerating every stage of the ransomware lifecycle.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ai-powered-ransomware-outpacing-defenses-crowdstrike-warns</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ai-powered-ransomware-outpacing-defenses-crowdstrike-warns/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Other</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: G7 Warns Financial Sector of AI's Double-Edged Sword in Cybersecurity</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/g7-experts-warn-of-ai-risks-in-financial-cybersecurity/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/g7-experts-warn-of-ai-risks-in-financial-cybersecurity/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> G7 Warns Financial Sector of AI's Double-Edged Sword in Cybersecurity</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The G7 Cyber Expert Group (CEG) has issued a statement on the dual role of Artificial Intelligence in the financial sector's cybersecurity landscape. While acknowledging AI's potential to enhance cyber resilience through advanced threat detection, the group warns of significant new risks. These include AI-accelerated vulnerability exploitation, concentration risk from reliance on a few dominant AI providers, and the potential for new, complex attack surfaces. The statement provides seven key considerations for financial institutions to navigate these challenges, emphasizing secure-by-design principles and robust governance.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Cloud Security</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The G7 Cyber Expert Group warns the financial sector about the dual nature of AI, highlighting risks like accelerated exploits and vendor concentration while offering guidance for secure adoption.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> g7-experts-warn-of-ai-risks-in-financial-cybersecurity</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/g7-experts-warn-of-ai-risks-in-financial-cybersecurity/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: UK's NCSC Warns of Doubling 'Nationally Significant' Cyberattacks, Cites Supply Chain Risk</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-ncsc-warns-of-rising-supply-chain-attacks-as-significant-incidents-double/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-ncsc-warns-of-rising-supply-chain-attacks-as-significant-incidents-double/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> UK's NCSC Warns of Doubling 'Nationally Significant' Cyberattacks, Cites Supply Chain Risk</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The UK's National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) has reported a sharp increase in cyberattacks, with 'nationally significant' cases more than doubling in the past year. In response, the NCSC is urging organizations to bolster their incident preparedness. Experts are pointing to vulnerabilities within the digital supply chain as a primary entry point for these attacks, with service providers like helpdesks becoming gateways to core business systems. A recent survey found that nearly a third of UK procurement managers reported a supply chain partner had been attacked in recent months.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Policy and Compliance, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> NCSC warning, UK cybersecurity, supply chain attacks, vendor risk management, third party risk, nationally significant incidents</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 4 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The UK's National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) reports that nationally significant cyberattacks have more than doubled, urging organizations to prepare and focus on supply chain security.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> uk-ncsc-warns-of-rising-supply-chain-attacks-as-significant-incidents-double</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Update Count:</strong> 1</p><p><strong>Update History:</strong> 1 update recorded</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-ncsc-warns-of-rising-supply-chain-attacks-as-significant-incidents-double/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Critical Infrastructure Under Siege: Ransomware Attacks Surge 34%</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-attacks-on-critical-infrastructure-surge-34-percent-in-2025/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-attacks-on-critical-infrastructure-surge-34-percent-in-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Critical Infrastructure Under Siege: Ransomware Attacks Surge 34%</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new report from cyber intelligence firm KELA reveals a staggering 34% year-over-year increase in ransomware attacks targeting critical industries between January and September 2025. These vital sectors, including manufacturing, healthcare, and energy, accounted for half of the 4,701 global ransomware incidents recorded. The United States was the most targeted nation, bearing the brunt of 21% of all attacks. The report identifies a handful of highly active groups, including Qilin, Clop, and Akira, as responsible for a significant portion of the incidents, highlighting a trend towards professionalization in the cybercriminal ecosystem and framing cyber resilience as a national security imperative.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Ransomware, Threat Intelligence, Cyberattack</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A new KELA report finds ransomware attacks on critical infrastructure surged 34% in 2025, with manufacturing and healthcare sectors heavily targeted. Learn about the top threat actors and at-risk nations.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> ransomware-attacks-on-critical-infrastructure-surge-34-percent-in-2025</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/ransomware-attacks-on-critical-infrastructure-surge-34-percent-in-2025/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: JLR Hack's Staggering Cost: £1.9 Billion Hit to UK Economy</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/jaguar-land-rover-hack-costs-uk-economy-1-9-billion/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/jaguar-land-rover-hack-costs-uk-economy-1-9-billion/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> JLR Hack's Staggering Cost: £1.9 Billion Hit to UK Economy</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The late August 2025 cyberattack on Jaguar Land Rover (JLR) is now estimated to have cost the UK economy a staggering £1.9 billion ($2.55 billion), potentially making it the most financially damaging cyber incident in the nation's history. According to the Cyber Monitoring Centre (CMC), the attack forced a near-total shutdown of JLR's production for six weeks, with the disruption cascading through its supply chain and impacting as many as 5,000 other organizations. The British government has since provided a £1.5 billion loan guarantee to support the automaker and its beleaguered suppliers.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cyberattack, Supply Chain Attack, Industrial Control Systems</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The cyberattack on Jaguar Land Rover (JLR) is estimated to have cost the UK economy £1.9 billion, making it the most financially damaging cyber event in the nation's history and impacting over 5,000 suppliers.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> jaguar-land-rover-hack-costs-uk-economy-1-9-billion</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/jaguar-land-rover-hack-costs-uk-economy-1-9-billion/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Industrial Control Systems</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: 'GlassWorm' Strikes: Novel Worm Spreads via VS Code Extensions Using Invisible Code</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/glassworm-worm-hits-vs-code-extensions-in-sophisticated-supply-chain-attack/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/glassworm-worm-hits-vs-code-extensions-in-sophisticated-supply-chain-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> 'GlassWorm' Strikes: Novel Worm Spreads via VS Code Extensions Using Invisible Code</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A highly sophisticated, self-propagating worm named 'GlassWorm' is actively targeting developers through the Microsoft Visual Studio Code and OpenVSX marketplaces. Discovered by Koi Security, the malware has already compromised over 35,800 developer systems. GlassWorm uses a novel technique of hiding malicious code with invisible Unicode characters, making it undetectable in code reviews. Upon infection, it steals credentials like NPM and GitHub tokens to propagate itself to other software packages, drains cryptocurrency wallets, and establishes a resilient, decentralized command-and-control (C2) infrastructure using the Solana blockchain.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Supply Chain Attack, Malware, Threat Actor</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 7 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Discover 'GlassWorm', a new self-propagating worm targeting developers via VS Code extensions. Learn how it uses invisible code, steals credentials, and leverages the Solana blockchain for C2.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> glassworm-worm-hits-vs-code-extensions-in-sophisticated-supply-chain-attack</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/glassworm-worm-hits-vs-code-extensions-in-sophisticated-supply-chain-attack/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Supply Chain Attack</category>
      <category>Malware</category>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Critical Netty Zero-Day Bypasses All Major Email Authentication</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-zero-day-in-netty-library-allows-email-auth-bypass/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-zero-day-in-netty-library-allows-email-auth-bypass/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Critical Netty Zero-Day Bypasses All Major Email Authentication</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A critical zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2025-59419, has been discovered in the widely used Netty Java library, affecting countless applications that handle email. The flaw allows an unauthenticated attacker to perform SMTP injection by embedding carriage return and line feed characters into email commands. This enables them to bypass standard email authentication defenses like SPF, DKIM, and DMARC, making it possible to send highly convincing spoofed emails that appear to originate from trusted domains. A patch is available and should be applied immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Phishing, Patch Management</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A critical zero-day vulnerability, CVE-2025-59419, in the Netty Java library allows SMTP injection to bypass SPF, DKIM, and DMARC, enabling attackers to send perfectly spoofed emails. Patch now.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> critical-zero-day-in-netty-library-allows-email-auth-bypass</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/critical-zero-day-in-netty-library-allows-email-auth-bypass/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Widespread Chaos: AWS US-EAST-1 Outage Takes Down Global Services</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/major-aws-outage-in-us-east-1-disrupts-global-internet-services/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/major-aws-outage-in-us-east-1-disrupts-global-internet-services/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Widespread Chaos: AWS US-EAST-1 Outage Takes Down Global Services</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A major Amazon Web Services (AWS) outage originating in its largest region, US-EAST-1, caused widespread global service disruptions on October 20, 2025. The 15-hour event was triggered by a DNS resolution issue affecting the DynamoDB service, which led to a cascading failure impacting at least 113 other AWS services. The incident affected thousands of companies, including Slack, Roblox, and Venmo, generating over 16 million user outage reports and serving as a stark reminder of the risks associated with cloud service concentration and hidden dependencies.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Cloud Security, Incident Response, Security Operations</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Analysis</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A major AWS outage in the US-EAST-1 region, caused by a DynamoDB DNS failure, led to a 15-hour global disruption, highlighting the critical risks of cloud concentration and the need for resilient, multi-region architectures.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> major-aws-outage-in-us-east-1-disrupts-global-internet-services</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/major-aws-outage-in-us-east-1-disrupts-global-internet-services/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Cloud Security</category>
      <category>Incident Response</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Iran's MuddyWater APT Targets 100+ Governments with Phoenix Backdoor</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/iran-linked-muddywater-apt-targets-governments-with-phoenix-backdoor/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/iran-linked-muddywater-apt-targets-governments-with-phoenix-backdoor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Iran's MuddyWater APT Targets 100+ Governments with Phoenix Backdoor</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The Iranian state-sponsored threat group MuddyWater is conducting a large-scale cyber-espionage campaign targeting over 100 government entities, primarily in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA). According to Group-IB, the attackers are using phishing emails sent from a compromised mailbox, leveraging the NordVPN service for anonymity. The emails contain malicious Word documents that use macros to deploy version 4 of the 'Phoenix' backdoor, a payload designed for foreign intelligence gathering. The campaign highlights the group's return to classic macro-based attack vectors.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Actor, Cyberattack, Phishing</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 6 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The Iranian APT group MuddyWater is targeting over 100 government entities in the MENA region with a new cyber-espionage campaign deploying the Phoenix v4 backdoor via phishing and malicious macros.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> iran-linked-muddywater-apt-targets-governments-with-phoenix-backdoor</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/iran-linked-muddywater-apt-targets-governments-with-phoenix-backdoor/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Actor</category>
      <category>Cyberattack</category>
      <category>Phishing</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Over 75% of Orgs Can't Keep Pace with AI-Powered Attacks, Survey Finds</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/76-percent-of-orgs-cant-match-speed-of-ai-powered-attacks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/76-percent-of-orgs-cant-match-speed-of-ai-powered-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Over 75% of Orgs Can't Keep Pace with AI-Powered Attacks, Survey Finds</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>A new survey from CrowdStrike reveals a stark reality: 76% of global organizations admit they cannot match the speed and sophistication of AI-powered cyberattacks. The 2025 State of Ransomware Survey highlights a dangerous 'confidence illusion,' where leaders believe they are prepared, yet 78% of their organizations were attacked in the past year. With adversaries using AI to accelerate attacks, 89% of security leaders now agree that AI-powered protection is essential to close the widening security gap and defend against modern threats.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Threat Intelligence, Ransomware, Policy and Compliance</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Report</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> A CrowdStrike survey reveals 76% of organizations struggle to match the speed of AI-powered attacks, highlighting a 'confidence illusion' among leaders and the urgent need for AI-driven cyber defenses.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> 76-percent-of-orgs-cant-match-speed-of-ai-powered-attacks</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/76-percent-of-orgs-cant-match-speed-of-ai-powered-attacks/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
      <category>Ransomware</category>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: UK Gov &amp; NCSC Issue Urgent Warning to FTSE 350 Boards on Cyber Resilience</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-government-and-ncsc-urge-businesses-to-bolster-cyber-defenses/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-government-and-ncsc-urge-businesses-to-bolster-cyber-defenses/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> UK Gov &amp; NCSC Issue Urgent Warning to FTSE 350 Boards on Cyber Resilience</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The UK's National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) and government ministers have sent a formal letter to the leaders of all FTSE 350 companies, demanding that cyber resilience be treated as a top board-level priority. The call to action follows the NCSC's latest annual review, which revealed a 50% increase in significant cyber incidents. The letter outlines three practical steps: adopt the government's Cyber Governance Code, enroll in the NCSC's Early Warning service, and mandate Cyber Essentials certification throughout supply chains.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Informational</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Policy and Compliance, Regulatory, Security Operations</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> The UK government and NCSC have issued a formal letter to FTSE 350 companies, urging them to make cyber resilience a board-level priority following a 50% rise in major cyber incidents.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> uk-government-and-ncsc-urge-businesses-to-bolster-cyber-defenses</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/uk-government-and-ncsc-urge-businesses-to-bolster-cyber-defenses/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Policy and Compliance</category>
      <category>Regulatory</category>
      <category>Security Operations</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Patch Now: Critical RCE Flaws in Oracle E-Business Suite Marketing Module</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/oracle-e-business-suite-hit-by-critical-marketing-module-flaws/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/oracle-e-business-suite-hit-by-critical-marketing-module-flaws/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Patch Now: Critical RCE Flaws in Oracle E-Business Suite Marketing Module</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>Oracle has issued urgent patches for two critical, unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerabilities in its E-Business Suite. The flaws, CVE-2025-53072 and CVE-2025-62481, both carry a CVSS score of 9.8 and affect the Oracle Marketing module. An attacker with network access can exploit these vulnerabilities via a simple HTTP request, without any user interaction, to achieve a full takeover of the marketing component. Oracle urges customers using affected versions (12.2.3 through 12.2.14) to apply the October 2025 Critical Patch Update immediately.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> Critical</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, Patch Management, Data Breach</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> Advisory</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> Oracle has patched two critical RCE vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-53072, CVE-2025-62481) with a 9.8 CVSS score in its E-Business Suite Marketing module. Apply the October 2025 CPU immediately to prevent a full system takeover.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> oracle-e-business-suite-hit-by-critical-marketing-module-flaws</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/oracle-e-business-suite-hit-by-critical-marketing-module-flaws/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>Patch Management</category>
      <category>Data Breach</category>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NEW: Pwn2Own Day 1: Hackers Net $522K for 34 Zero-Days in SOHO Devices</title>
      <link>https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pwn2own-ireland-day-1-hackers-earn-522k-for-34-zero-days/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=last</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pwn2own-ireland-day-1-hackers-earn-522k-for-34-zero-days/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Headline:</strong> Pwn2Own Day 1: Hackers Net $522K for 34 Zero-Days in SOHO Devices</p><p><strong>Summary:</strong><br/>The first day of Trend Micro's Pwn2Own Ireland 2025 competition was a resounding success for security researchers, who earned a total of $522,500 for demonstrating 34 unique zero-day vulnerabilities. In a stunning display, every single one of the 17 scheduled attempts against popular SOHO devices—including printers, NAS devices, and smart home products from brands like QNAP, Synology, Canon, and HP—was successful. The highlight was a complex 'SOHO Smashup' that chained eight bugs to compromise a router and a NAS device.</p><p><strong>Severity:</strong> High</p><p><strong>Categories:</strong> Vulnerability, IoT Security, Threat Intelligence</p><p><strong>Article Type:</strong> NewsArticle</p><p><strong>Reading Time:</strong> 5 minutes</p><p><strong>Meta Description:</strong> On Day 1 of Pwn2Own Ireland 2025, security researchers earned $522,500 by demonstrating 34 zero-day vulnerabilities against popular SOHO devices from QNAP, Synology, Canon, and HP with a 100% success rate.</p><p><strong>Article Slug:</strong> pwn2own-ireland-day-1-hackers-earn-522k-for-34-zero-days</p><p><strong>Published Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Created Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><strong>Updated Date:</strong> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:00 GMT</p><p><a href="https://cyber.netsecops.io/articles/pwn2own-ireland-day-1-hackers-earn-522k-for-34-zero-days/">Read Full Article →</a></p>]]></description>
      <category>Vulnerability</category>
      <category>IoT Security</category>
      <category>Threat Intelligence</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>